Previously on the office
I am on a lecture circuit.
I'm going around to all the branches,
And i'm telling them my
secret recipe for success.
I have now memorized all of your names.
Shirty,mole,lazy eye,mexico,baldy.
Then i turn it on and
i say,"prepare yourself
For the uta chain store massacre."
- How's jim?
- We're engaged.
Oh,my god,i'm so happy for you.
Oh,well...thank you.
You rember holly?
She used to work for h.R.
She was the love of my life.
She just left,and i never got closure.
And i feel like i need to
go to nashuand get closure.
Okay. Let's go.
-=Www.Ydy.Com/bbs=-
Proudly presents
Sync:ytet-∂¨„ﬂµ‰ˆÌ
the.Office
season5 episode15
Two
I didn't eat lunch.
I didn't eatallmy lunch.
Hello,everyone.
Oh,ice cream.
Nice,kevin. Looks good.
It...yeah.
Angela,you're more chipper than usual.
I am proud to announce
that there is a new addition
To the martin family.
She's hypoallergenic.
She doesn't struggle
when you try to dress her.
She's a third-Generation show cat.
Her father was in meet the parents.
Needless to say,she
was very,very expensive.
- How much?
- $7,000.
For a cat? I could
get you a kid for that.
Where'd you get that kind of money?
I sold andy's engagement ring on ebay.
Wait,you didn't give it back?
He wouldn't have wanted that.
Her name is prinss lady!
- Seven
grand.- Mm-Hmm.
I gotta see that little bitch.
I have something better than a picture.
Come on.
You have your cats on nanny cam?
Yeah.
I mean,i usually try to take leave
When i get a new cat,
But i'm out of vacation days.
And this company still
doesn't recognize cat marnity.
I e meofanfi,cewhen somebody has
a kid,oh,sure,take off a year.
She's right. I had my second
kid just for the vacation.
Right. Anyways...
I just want to make sure princess lady
Is acclimating well.
She means more to me than anyone.
Anycat,you mean.
And person.
So detour.
We're now adding nashua
to the lecture circuit
So michael can confront
holly and get some closure.
Nashua actually sounded
very excited on the phone.
I don't think they
get a lot of visitors.
Because their offi is only accessible
By cross-Country
skis. Hey-Oh!
I've been driving too long.
- What did you do?
- Stop yelling at me!
- I didn't do anything!
What did you learn in there?
I t you learned things,huh?
Like how to fashion a shiv,hmm?
Hey,what the hell's going on?
D't you tell jim where you were
From ages 14 to 15.
I was kickin' it.
- In juvie.
- What?
Juvie...nile... detention center.
- Where they send teenagers
- Yep. Got it.
What did you do? Huh?
Hey,dwight,sounds like she was 14,
So maybe we wanna go a little easy.
If she's old enough to get married,
She's old enough to follow the law.
What did you do?
My boyfriend dumped
me,so i stole his boat.
I mean,he told me it was his boat.
It was actually his father's.
I just thought it'd be really romantic,
Likethelma and louise,but
with,like,a boat.
And it was the worst year of my life.
And i can't believe that
you guys are making me
Talk about this on my birthday!
I thought you saidyesterday
was your birthday.
Hey,you know what? I got you a cake.
You did?
I want to see the cake.
And...ta-Da!
I hate it.
How do you hate it? It's a cake.
Well,there's no
flowers or toys or--
I mean,there's nothing on it.
Where did you even find
I mean,it doesn't have my name on it.
Do you guys know what my name is?
- My name is kelly!
- Right.
I forgot if there was an "e"
between the "l" and the "y."
I still don't know.
I mean,i don't even
know what the theme is.
What's the theme?!
- Birthday.
- Frostg.
Those aren't themes.
There's always a theme.
Nice job on the cake,bozo.
Okay,you know what,next time,
I'll let you get the cake,
Andiget to scream at the bir
Okay,a little bit more
closer to the sign.
Yeah.
- Do i look okay?
- You look good.
- Hi.
- Hi,can i help you?
Yes,you can.
I am michael scott
Regional manager of the scranton branch.
- Yes,we were expecting you.
- Have a seat.
Thank you.
Um...is holly flax anywhere here?
Actually,she on an h.R. Retreatfi
For the next three days.
She's not here?
But if you need to get in
touch with her immediately,
You could talk to a.J.
He's a salesman here.
A.J. Yeah,he's her boyfriend.
He's just over there.
She has a boyfriend.
I'm so sorry,michael.
How could she do this toe,pam?
She's not doing it to hurt you.
I can't do the
presentation. I can't--
Just...oh...
Thinking about seeing him...
And...thinking about...
Him getting to hold her
and getting to kiss her.
It just--
Oh,god!
Listen,when jim was dating karen,
I didn't want to come to work.
It was awful. I hated it.
- I wanted to quit,but-
I know-- Please...
Come on,i'm going through something.
Okay?
You know,when holly gets back,
Everyone'll tell her
what a great job you did.
And then she'll realize
what she's missing.
Andhen she'll move back to scranton.
And her boyfriend will die.
Yeah. Maybe.
Maybe. One step at a time.
You can do this.
I can do this.
I think there
could be snacks or--
Is that what i think it is?
Good god!
That one ugly cat is
humping princess lady!
No! Awesome!
Stop it,mr. Ash! Bad cat!
That is very bad. You stop it right now!
I swear,he is fixed.
Yeah,i know fixed. That ain't fixed
- No way.
- No,now listen.
You can't let what you see
here sully your image of them.
They are good,decent cats.
I've gotta go. I'll be back in an hour.
Oh,stop that! Oh!
Oh,the other one's watching.
Okay,so all we need is a theme...
And cups and ice and nch and a cake.
Busy.
Hey,what's that show that
she's always talking about?
My god,is this how you are with pam?
Because she must want to
shoot herself in the face.
You know what. I could
use a little help.
You know what. I'm a little busy.
We have a lot to do,
And you are putting up
a very effeminate sign.
Is that what you've
been doing,making a sign?
It's not effeminate. It's festive.
You've been makingthatsign for something
That we can just announce
to the whole office?
Hey,everybody,the party's now at 3:00.
I know,i just read it on the sign.
Good morning,
Viet--
Nashua!
Sales.
Sales is whatbwingsus together today.
How do we deal with clients who say,
"Frankly,my dear,
I don't give a damn about paper,"
And get them to show us the mone
Well,we are going to find out today.
Show of hands.
How many of you are salesmen?
Let's see the salesmen. Ooh,okay.
Well,i know what the
rest of you are thinking.
Wow,yuck. Salesmen are the worst.
They are awful. They are so arrogant.
They think the whole
place revolves around them.
Handsome. Good listeners.
Funny. Mr. Wonderful.
So,okay,you're a
salesman. What's your name?
- A.J.
What kind of name is a.J.?
What,do you race cars?
I'm a salesman. That's
why i raised my hand.
Ooh,ouch. Okay.
Good. You're funny.
Very good and funny. Tell me,a.J.,
Are u dating?
Is there somebody you date?
Yeah. Why,are you interested?
I have a question about
discounts from distributors.
Yep,we will get to you.
Okay,so you're dating somebody.
Um...is it serious?
It's pretty serious. Yes.
Does she ever talk about me?
Oh,god.
Excuse me?
What does this have to do with sales?
It's all connected. Shut up.
Does she ever mention michael scott?
No. What are you talking about?
Does it feel good?
Does what feel good?
Your life.
Oh,wow.
Ahh,legs are sort of giving out.
Long drive in the
car. So let's just--
We'll st continue.
Oh,wow.
Okay...
Michael,get off the floor.
Yeah,yeah...
I can't do this,pam.
Justead-- Just
read the cards.
Michael,you
have to--
No,i'm okay. I'm all right.
Okay...okay.
That was weird,huh?
It's all part of the presentation.
It was confusing,right?
Because confusing situations happen
to us all the time in our jobs
I'm just trying to bridge the gap
Between what just happened,
And the fact that i'm going to be doing
The rest of the presentation.
Sales is like a box of chocolates.
You never know which
vendor you're gonna get.
Forrest gump.
Blazer...freckles... penguin...
K.D. Lang... holly's boyfriend.
These mnemonic devices
help to make a connection,
And then also to help
you memorize names.
I have a chain saw!
Cutting down the competion.
Where is th bad cat?
Oh,you know who you
are. Excuse me,petals.
I'm looking for mr. Ash. He's a bad cat.
Bad,bad cat. Do you hear me?
Bad. Yeahyou were bad.
No,you look at me when i talk to you.
Do you hear me,mr. Ash? You look at me.
'Cause i'm talking to you right now.
This is getting weird.
Is she cleaning the cat with her tongue?
Ooh...
Has this been on the entire time?
I have no idea.
I was looking at pictures of food
On my computer.
Well,sorry i'm late.
I want to get that image out of my head.
The psychological issues
That go behind licking a cat
Are not things i want to go into.
Also,i'm prettyure she
coughed up a hairball.
Don't look up. Don't look up.
- Want some pie?
- No.
I went through holly's things.
What?
I stole the sleeve of her sweater.
Oh,michael.
I also stole something
off of her computer.
A document called "dear michael."
- You did what?!
- I shouldn't have done it.
It just-- I
couldn't help it.
- She never sent
it to you?- No,sh--
She didn't.
I'm gonna read it.
- No.
- Yes.
No,under no circumstances
Can you read that letter.
It's a violation of her trust.
How?
Because she didn't sent it to you.
I know,i know. You're right,you'
I could read it.
No,that
wouldn't--
Yeah,i could read it.
No,you don't have to do that.
- Go get your laptop.
- Okay.
What?
I'm not in love with her.
You have to write my
suggestions down too.
I'm not writing "horse hunt."
I don't evennow what that means.
It's in the name.
Okay,so far our ideal party consists of
Beer,fights to the
death,cupcakes,blood pudding,
Blood,touch football,mating,
Charades,and yes,horse hunting.
You're right-- Forget
horse hunting,it's stupid.
Look,is there a birthday that
you rember that you loved?
Here's one.
It was dark,warm,wet.
A sudden burst of light.
An intense pressure like
i'd never felt before.
Father,dressed in
white,pulls me forward.
- Mother bites the cord.
- Okay,stop.
Forever stop that story.
That's disgusting,and it doesn't count.
So give me another one.
Schrutes don't celebrate
birthdays,idiot.
It started as a depression-Era prac,
And then moved on to an esome tradition
That i look forward to every year.
What about you?
Actually,when i was seven,my dad took me
To the natural history
museum in new york.
And we looked at fossils all day.
And at the end of the day,he got me
A little plastic triceratops.
It was awesome.
That's cool.
Hey,you know what's even
cooler than triceratops?
Every other dinosaur that ever existed!
Didn't see that one coming.
It's deleted.
Well?
She still has feelings for you.
She said that?
Is that what it said? What did it say?
I can't tell you specifically,
But...it's not over.
You're sure?
Okay.
Happy birthday. Surprise!
Hey,it's not a surprise.
It's not a surprise.
This doesn't look good.
What?! You have a cake.
You have a delicious cake
With your name spelled correctly?
- Told you.
- You haven't heard our theme,though.
You don't hear a theme. You see it.
Why is there a chiclet on my cake?
That's the best part.
That represents a
pillow,or a television.
Our theme,if
you will--
Because the fun part
is you get to decide
On an hour of television
or an hour of napping.
That's our theme.
- Cool.
- Yeah?
I love it.
Oh,yes! Okay,good.
So what's it gonna be,kapoor?
Ooh,,can she pick a half hour of each?
- No.
Oh,then pick tv.
- Take a nap.
- Tv.
No,watching tv at work is really cool.
Take a nap.Nothing good is on right now.
Bonnie hunt is on.
You know,i have been
watching tv all week.
I choose nap.
All right. Okay,nap it is.
Everyone out. Get out!
We're gonna be eating cake atur desks.
- Let's go.
- Surprise.
Move it!
Let's go,go,go,go,go. Come on.
I got this.
This is for you.
And... happy birthday,kel.
Thank you.
Okay...
You've got one hour.
I'm too excited to sleep.
Mm,great cake.
Thanks.
Birthday time is over!
Now go make up for
all the work you missed
When you were taking your nap.
Many happy returns.
I feel great.
So good to have closure. Ah!
We should go apologize
to roy or something.
No,we don't need to do that.
Who have i wronged? Who have i wronged?
Oh,oh!
What about that fat guy
from stamford that insulted?
We should find him.
You mean tony.
Jabba the hutt. Pizza the hut.
Fat guys like pizza pepperoni pizza.
Pepperoni tony.
Oh,michael.
,was he fat.
So,so...fat.
You know what,forget it. I know me.
When i saw him,i would never
be able to apologize to him.
Too fat.
www.tvsubtitles.net