This morning, the phone guy comes in,
And he shows michael That
our phones have a p.A. Function.
And then he just left.
This is your captain speaking.
The office will be flying
At an altitude of two stories.
Look out your left-Hand window,
And you will see vance refrigeration.
I am the ghost of salesmen past.
Do not come near me!
Yes, michael scott
for dr. Jocelyn, please.
Hello, doctor.
I was just following up
about my mole again.
No, i was looking online
About sebaceous cysts.
I have not been squeezing it.
Could i stick it with a pin?
Toby flenderson to
the principal's office.
Your mother called.
And it appears that
you wet the bed again.
So you have to get home
to wash your sheets
Because they're yellow and
they're wet With your urine.
And at 6'6" From the university
of north carolina, Jim halpert!
That's pretty funny.
Hey, you know what?
Did i drop my, uh...
- What?
- What the heck...
Is that, uh...
- You find it?
- I didn't.
I'll look somewhere else.
- All right.
Would you like fries with that?
Please drive around.
www.1000fr.com presents
Capture:FRM@од╥Г
Sync:FRS@╧Бок
the office S05 ep14
Hello.
- Good morning.
- Morning.
You ready?
And we're off!
Like a herd of turtles.
Well, pam and i have eloped.
Actually, we just robbed a bank,
And we are on the lam.
No.
seriously, i am on a lecture circuit.
Apparently scranton has the best
sales Of any regional branch,
So david wallace has asked me
To go to all the branches--
Except nashua,
so a little bit raw there--
but i am going to these branches
And i am telling them
my secret recipe for success.
My 11 business herbs and spices
In a sales batter.
that. Well, that is pam.
Pam is coming along as my assistant
And my driver so i can focus.
And i like to pack heavy.
He brought a sled.
No! That is a toboggan.
You never know when you're
gonna find a snowy hill.
So...
every magician has a hot assistant,
And every rock star has a roadie,
And pam is my hot roadie.
Yeah. I love being on the road.
But i especially love
the time-And-A-Half pay,
24 hours a day, for three days.
'Cause i have a mortgage now.
Gotta bring home the bucks.
Yeah--Oh, don't say "bucks."
That's not ladylike.
Here we go!
Okay, so what we do
Is we drive all day
And we stay in hotels
together at night.
- Separate rooms.
- Well, that goes without saying.
I'm gonna say it anyway.
Hey! Look at what
you're wearing again.
Pam, have you ever seen
a magician's assistant?
That's...
- this is a new cardigan.
- Kind of--
Maybe you could
tie it around your waist
Or lose the shirt
underneath or something.
- No.
- Oh--All right.
- Hey, kelly.
- Screw you.
Uh, excuse me.
That is no way to address a superior.
Oh, yeah? Screw you, too.
What was that all about?
You forgot her birthday.
It was yesterday.
- Go ahead.
You do it.
- Okay.
- I insist.
Basically after
phyllis blackmailed angela,
Michael asked them both to step down
From the party-Planning committee
'Cause there was too much drama.
- What he said was--
- Just--Easy.
There was a problem
with having one head Of
the party-Planning committee.
She becomes too powerful,
So he appointed two heads.
- I am a paper salesman.
- Party-Planning is literally
The stupidest thing
- i've ever done in my life.
- This is humiliating.
That's on my side.
So this is fun.
My birthday was yesterday
and everybody forgot.
I got really dressed up and excited,
And no one said a word.
There wasn't even a party.
I think sometimes people are
really mean To the hot, popular girl.
Can i turn on the radio?
No. I need silence or
sam kinison to prepare.
But then you fall asleep
And there's nothing for me to do.
Then listen to your ipod, pam.
- That's dangerous.
- Well, then--Hey.
You know what? Let's just talk.
That's okay. I can--I'm fine.
I'll just play a song in my head.
You nervous about seeing karen again,
Since she was the other woman?
Actually, you were the other woman, so.
No, that was a long time ago.
Is that why you're
wearing makeup today?
No. I'm not even wearing that much.
I hate the idea that
someone out there hates me.
I even hate thinking
that al-Qaeda hates me.
I think if they got to know me,
They wouldn't hate me.
But karen knows me
and she still hates me, so.
- Oh, this is a nice office.
- You don't have to lie.
Through here.
phyllis?
Who's that?
She's out of your league, andy.
For your information, I have been
with lots of beautiful women.
Sexually?
This conversation is over.
I am single now.
What we have here
Is the ultimate smackdown
Between the nard-Dog And crippling
despair, loneliness, and depression.
I intend to win.
We just wanted to say we are very sorry.
Screw you guys. You're dead to me.
If you say "screw you" one more time--
Yeah, screw you, beefer.
- I don't forget your birthday.
- Guys, guys.
- I would never do that.
- Oh. Hey.
- Hey!
- Guys, guys.
We just want to make it up
to you. What can we do?
I guess my only wish
Would be that nothing so terrible Would
ever happen to anyone else ever again.
Oh, god.
- Okay.
- In a way,
it's good that it happened to me
Because at least i can bear it.
What kind of cake
do you want, imbecile?
Ice cream.
Okay, uh, point at the dunder mifflin.
Hello, rolando. How are you?
- Hi.
- Rolando--
I'd like you to meet pam.
She is our receptionist.
You know what? Maybe you guys could
go out On a little friend date sometime.
Uh, you're late.
Everyone's waiting
in the conference room.
Karen will be right here
to take you over.
Okay.
Don't be nervous.
Just picture her naked.
- Stop it, please.
- That's what i do.
- Steal my trick.
- Please, cut it out.
Hey.
Hi, guys.
Oh, my god.
Is that jim's?
- What? Of course not.
- Michael!
Okay.
Oh, man! My head just exploded.
Thank god. For everybody, right?
'Kay.
Wow, you're huge!
That's incredible!
I--God. Sorry.
Sorry, my head is-- I'm just--
I'm trying to figure out The last
time that you and jim had sex and--
Let's just get
this over with, shall we?
Ten. Ten months?
Are you kidding?
Well, i'm not done yet.
Dwight.
This fits in the palm of my hand.
You haven't blown 'em up enough.
Why have you chosen
brown and gray balloons?
They match the carpet.
What is that?
"It is your birthday," period.
It's a statement of fact.
Not even an exclamation point?
This is more professional.
It's not like she discovered
a cure for cancer.
I can't believe how bad this looks.
Are you trying to hurt my feelings?
Because if so, you are succeeding.
Fortunately, my feelings regenerate
At twice the speed of a normal man's.
Okay, good then.
Have you collected
the money from everyone?
- I am working on it.
- How much do you have?
$6.
That's how much
you and i contributed!
- I--
- Damn it, jim!
I said i was working on it.
Trying to see what cds she's got.
It's good to know the deets
About the girl you're wooing.
Feist.
Yes!
No!
Oh, my god.
Oh, no. That is so awful.
That is the worst news.
I have to go. I have to
do a presentation.
I'll talk to you--
This is going to be hard
for me to speak today
Because i just learned
that my father has died.
No, he didn't! He is alive.
And this isn't even a cell phone.
This is a calculator.
But you bought it!
And now you can't return it.
Or can you?
No, you can't.
Yes.
Karen, do you need to go pump?
Not gonna have to do that
Till after i have the baby.
No, i am wondering--
What are you talking about?
I am talking about How you
all need to sell an experience.
Like i sold you one--
The idea that my father had died.
But now we think you're a liar.
Would a liar bring mini mounds bars?
I am a theatrical person.
Growing up, i always thought
i would become an actor
Because i have These
memorization tricks that i use.
for instance,
I learned the pledge of allegiance
By setting it to
the tune of old macdonald.
* i pledge allegiance to the flag of *
* the united states of america *
* and to the republic for which *
* it stands one nation under god *
* with a woof-Woof here *
* and a woof-Woof there *
* here a woof, there a woof *
* everywhere a woof, woof *
Um, you get it.
I don't know you.
But i need to know you
in order to sell to you.
That is why i have asked you To
go around and tell me your names.
I have an amazing pneumonic device
By which i have now memorized
All of your names.
Shirty. Mole.
Lazy eye. Mexico.
Baldy. Sugar boobs. Black woman.
I have taken A unique
part of who you are,
And i have used that
to memorize your name.
Baldy. Your head is bald.
It is hairless. It is shiny.
It is reflective. Like a mirror.
"M." Your name is mark.
- Yes.
- Got it. It works.
- it's very insulting.
- But it works.
I would like you all to give
this a shot. What do you say?
But we already know
each others' names.
Well, then it will be easier for you.
But i--I still think it's worthwhile
To give it a-- Give it a try.
Okay. All right, everyone.
Meeting's over.
Oh, i still have more.
Can i please see you
in my office, please?
She is pregnant. She is knocked up.
"K." Karen.
Pam, let's go.
I can't accept these prices, stanley.
- They just cut our budget.
- Brought you guys some coffees.
Stanley, i know you have
adult onset diabetes
So i put splenda in yours.
Let's see. How many
did i put in there?
* one, two, three, four *
* splendas in your coffee, stanley *
* none in yours, julia *
* 'cause i don't know how you take it *
* but if you'd rather... *
Four splenda. Are you crazy?
Well, no, i actually only put in two.
But that's not how the song goes.
- Are you out of your damn mind?
You bring an angel
like that into this office
And you don't even
set me up with her.
We're not friends.
I didn't think about it.
We are friends.
Stanley, we're friends.
And you let me down.
You really like her, huh?
Yeah.
I really like her with all my heart.
Give me two clients for her.
I grab this,
And i turn it on and i say,
"Prepare yourself For the
utica chain store massacre!"
No, that's--That is
incredibly dangerous.
No, don't worry. The chain is off.
No, it's not.
You know, i think I'm just
gonna distill all of this
And send it in an email to my team.
Email's not scary. This is an
opportunity. Don't--Don't blow it.
So when are you due?
in about a month.
that is wonderful.
Congratulations.
Thank you.
It just all happened so fast.
It's really amazing.
Congratulations, karen.
thanks.
So is there a guy or,
uh--Uh, person,
Or, uh...
sperm machine that did this to you or?
Yes, michael.
- My husband impregnated me.
- Oh, great.
His name is dan.
this is us.
- So dorky.
- Oh, he's cute.
Yeah, he's so cute.
He's a dermatologist.
We met at a bar. Can you believe that?
- What is happening there?
- Oh, yeah. don't even.
That's really dorky.
it's really sweet.
No, it's really dorky.
You were right the first time.
So how are things in scranton?
How's jim?
they're good. Uh, jim's good.
We're engaged.
That's so great. That's great.
Thank you.
Oh, my god. I'm so happy for you.
Old hatreds dissolve
into new friendships.
It's a really wonderful moment.
I have to take care of
a couple of things,
So andy will be
taking over things here.
You're in good hands
And give my best to your mother.
So julia...
let's see.
With regards to, uh, billing,
Should we send bills to you
Or to your boyfriend's house or?
No, it could go straight
to our business address.
Oh, okay. All right.
That makes sense.
How does your boyfriend Deal
with your phenomenal success?
Is he just, like,
Totally threatened by you or?
Actually, i-- I don't have a boyfriend.
really?
Is that--
Wow, that's so weird.
Guys, stop everything.
I'm about to ask out this girl
And i'm completely panicking.
oh, my desk is over...
This gal--
She's really into you?
Yeah. Yeah.
I mean, i've seen her,
like, three times today,
And we love all the same music,
And whenever i walk into a room
She totally looks up.
??say no more.
So. This is how i got squeaky fromme.
No small talk.
Just show her who's the boss.
Just go right in and kiss her.
Okay, it sounds risky.
Have i ever steered you wrong, jim?
Wait, what?
I would give that lecture a solid b+.
Although, for the record, karen--
Kind of mean.
- I like her.
- Really?
No, honestly.
Tell me what you really think.
I'm serious.
i'm really glad i came.
Why?
Because, um...
'Cause i'll never wonder ever again
If i did something wrong and--
Now i have closure.
She's happy and--
I don't know, it feels good.
Thanks for walking me out.
Oh, my pleasure. Yeah, there's all
kinds of weirdoes out here, so.
- you must be freezing.
- I am about to die.
Will you wait here
while i go get my jacket?
Oh, no, it's okay. This is my car.
Okay. Okay.
Well, listen.
You're a new client,
And as one of my new clients,
You will always be taken care of.
And that is the nard-Dog guarantee.
What's a "nard-Dog"?
This is the nard-Dog.
What the hell?
I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
Oh, i--I thought we had this energy,
And i'm a mess,
And i just had my heart broken,
And you came in today
and you're so pretty.
- You're, like, incredibly pretty.
- I just got out of a relationship, too.
It's really hard.
Yeah--Right?!
Yeah. Do you want to talk about it?
Go to a mall or something,
- just walk around?
- No, i-- I don't think so.
Sure, yeah. That's--You're right.
It's too soon.
For--Definitely too soon for me.
So i'm glad we got that out of the way.
I'm gonna be in touch with you
In three months.
I'm gonna call you about that order.
And maybe about that mall walk.
okay.
- Take care, julia.
- Thank you.
Sorry i tried to kiss y--
We lost the account.
Damn it.
dwight schrute.
how old's kelly?
Who is this?
It's moz. Who do you think it is?
Moz doesn't know how to use
a phone, So joke's on you.
Look, i'm at the supermarket,
And they only have numbered candles.
How old is she?
24.
37.
Do you think i'm calling you
For your best approximation?
I'll call you back.
I have here kelly kapoor's
personal and confidential file.
Allow me to share.
"Kelly kapoor spent april 1995
To december 1996
at berks county youth center."
Juvie.
"According to past employers,
It in no way affects her job perform--"
Blah, blah, blah.
Are you asleep?
No.
I'm just thinking about what you said.
About karen, about closure.
You remember holly?
She used to work for h.R.
No, remind me.
Blonde hair.
Nice boobs.
Not too big, not too small.
Perfect boobs.
Of course i remember holly.
She was the love of my life.
What you and jim have
times 100. Just she--
She just left.
And i didn't--
I never got closure, you know?
I never got closure with her.
I haven't talked to her since.
I haven't seen her since.
And i feel like i need to
go to nashua And get closure.
I feel like i need that.
Okay.
Let's go.
I'll just blow off the lecture at rochester.
Yeah.
Screw 'em. Let's do this.
??
???
??For kelly's party.
- I'd like to contribute.
- Oh, great.
There you go.
welcome to www.1000fr.com
www.tvsubtitles.net