Oh, my god!
I can't believe it!
I just won an art contest.
Aah!
Thanks.
I still don't understand why
you wanted me to say that.
Shut up.
I got her! Ooohhh...
not cool, dwight.
Not cool, man.
www.1000fr.com presents
Sync:mzinfo
The office s5e25
Oh no!
I still have the lease On the
michael scott paper company,
So occasionally
i will sneak down here
For a little coffee
and dancing.
I actually dance
all the time.
Tiptoeing around corporate,
it is a ballet.
When i am breaking
all the rules,
I'm break dancing.
And expresso.
Guys, i'm scared.
I'm really scared.
I think i'm growing
into a giant,
Because look at this
normal-Size coffee cup.
Looks so tiny
in my giant hand now.
Anybody want to go to lunch
with me later on?
- I do.
- Okay, how about a woman? Pam?
Oh, i can't do lunch.
I was just sending you an eil.
Jim and i need to leave early today
To meet with our contractor.
Oh, really? Okay.
Just sent it.
What about the rest of you?
At dunder mifflin,
there is a very strict
No-Lunch-With-The-Boss policy.
And i don't know
who instituted it.
I think it started right after
my precessor stepped down.
But at the michael scott
paper company,
I really enjoyed having lunch
with pam and ryan every day.
So rules be damned, I want to
have lunch with these people.
Who else? Who else?
Ryan.
I don't do lunch. I'm doing
five small meals a day now.
Now that i'm back to doing
the job Of a temp again,
I find that food is one thing
i can control.
Okay, anyone?
Anyone at all.
Accounting?
I am accounting on you
to go to lunch with me.
No, i don't want to stay late
to have a two-Hour lunch.
Michael, we have a lot
of work to do.
What?!
- Work.
- Oh, well, god!
What happened to you people?
We are just office drones.
We are office drones.
All we do is work...
is work...
if you don't take out his battery,
He just keeps going all day
Oh, no,
your battery fell out.
I was just learning to love.
Hi, guys.
How are you doing?
Erin,
how many times do i have to tell you? It is
not necessary for you to ask uhow we are doing
Every time you interact with us.
You're right.
I'm sorry.
Now,
how can i help you?
Did somebody here leave a map
in the printer To youngstown, ohio?
Attention, office.
Who here is planning a trip
Tooungstown, ohio?
I will take your silence to mean
That you're all hiding something.
This location is
the superior court--
So if someone's going
to a court, big deal.
It is a big deal.
'Cause there's only a handful of reasons Why
someone would ever go to a courthouse in ohio,
And not be charged
with a crime.
To claim ainheritance
from a deceased relative.
To obtain a learner's permit
At age 14 1/2 instead of 15.
Erin, let me see
your birth certificate.
Sure.
There are other reasons
to go to ohio.
We're getting married today.
So it turnsut it's the closest place
To get a marriage license
Without a three-Day
waiting period.
Tell 'em how it happened.
Okay, so we're going through
all the wedding plans,
And boy, it is complicated.
- And very expensive.
- Very expensive.
'Cause you say you want
a small wedding And that's great.
But then you have to invite--
- You can't leave anyone out.
- No one.
Okay, just get
to the good part.
Right. Oh, so this morning We are
- having breakfast together...
- mm-Hmm.
And i just looked up
from my cereal And i said,
"you know what
i want to do today?
I want to marry you."
I had just woken up.
I didn't look cu.
That's how i knew
heth me eaofntfi icet.
Michael?
Michael,
sorry to bother you.
Are you gonna be working
down here?
- Do you want these down here?
- No work! No work! No work!
I come in here
to relieve frustration. Ooh,
ahh, ahh, ooh!
Well, i like to swim.
That's good.
Ou have a cool place
to come hang--
If you ever want
to come down here,
Door's always open.
Lock's broken, so...
thank you.
Come on in.
Hey, hey, here we go.
- Yeah!???
- There we go.
Now you got it. Now you got it.
Yeah, i do got it.
- Hey, you want some espresso?
- Oh, yeah.
Gotta keep yourself
dehydrated
- That's rule number one.
- Okay.
I love it.
???
Guys,
i believe that i have figured
out What is up your butts.
There's no reason
to be scared.
The bad man is gone.
Charles is gone.
Charles really did a number
on these guys.
They are way too focused
on work.
When i was in charge,
This place was like
dave & buster's.
People just hanging out,
having fun, eatin' apps.
I don't know, it's like...
dave died or something.
Daddy's here, and daddy's
gonna take care of you.
Please don't refer
to yourself as our daddy.
I am your big daddy...
and i am gonna kiss
the boo-Boo.
Widdle andy is afwaid.
- Andy'safwaid?
- Yes.
Are you all afwaid?
- No.
- Daddy's here for you,
my widdle angels.
Okay,
i think that i have figured a way
To get you guys out of your funk.
- What?
- Funk is the problem.
And the solution.
- That makes sense.
- I have taken
my downstairs office,
And i have turned it
into a place to hang out.
A place where unattractive and
attractive people Can get together
to meet, to greet,
To see the ones
that you love.
To love the ones
that you see.
Is this our punishment for not
wanting To have lunch with you?
Why don't you
get over lunch, oscar?
Everybody else is past it.
All work and no play
Makes michael a dull boy.
This is like
a haunted coffeehouse?
No, dwight is confusing you.
It's more of a disco.
A haunted disco!
With coffee,
but without the haunting.
It's a combo dance house
coffee bar?
It is a daytime disco
on the ground floor
Of an industrial office
building.
It's a cafe disco.
Exactly.
So, like, a disco cafe.
No, no.
Not even close.
I can't force you to go down,
but i can entice you.
I'm gonna be down there.
Erin will be down there
from time to time.
And all-You-Can-Eat
espresso.
Well, kevin, i guess
it is just me and you.
- Yeah.
- Holdin' down the fort.
Yeah.
This place is great.
- Thank you.
- Oh, my god, kevin.
I am still on hold.
You were supposed to get the answer
from michael And come back up.
- Sorry.
- This is a no-Work zone.
Please respect the lei.
- Hmm?
- Yeah, respect the lei.
Come.
Kevin, stay.
Kevin, come.
Kevin, come!
Stay, stay.
- Come on, right now.
- Cookie, kevin. Cookie.
There is no cookie, kevin.
- Is there a cookie?
- Mm-Hmm.
- Wha--
- Come on.
Oh, for goodness sakes,
kevin!
There's no cookie.
There's no cookie. Come on!
Come.
I wanted a cookie.
Completely unacceptable.
Now i know what the founders
of philip morris felt like.
You just want to
give people a smooth,
fun way to relax.
And suddenly you're just
some terrible monster.
Here we go.
Ow!
Oh, what the hell.
Hi, jessica.
Is bob in?
Oh, he's on a call.
I'll just duck my head in.
It's pretty important.
He wouldn't want to be disturbed.
Can i give him a message
before he gets off?
Tell him i'm going dancing
downstairs in the storage closet
Between the bathrooms that
used to be a utility shower,
And he should join me there.
I'll let him know.
Mm-Hmm.
Phyllis?
Hey.
- Hey.
I like.
All right.
Back. There you go.
There you gogood.
Ooh, show me some attitude.
Ho ho ho!
- Oh, *** god!
- Oh, no, no, no.
Oh, wow!
What did you do?
- You didn't do that.
You're okay. You're okay.
- Yeah.
Let's lie down. Here we--
You wanna go down?
- alright
- Whoa! Sorry. Ugh!
That's okay.
That solved the problem.
- ???
- Ooh! It's right here.
Hey, hey, hey, hey.
I got your text. Who's philip?
No, no, no.
Who tipped you over?
Was it philip?
It's my back.
It's her back We just--
We need-- Okay, let's--
- Call a doctor.
- You know what,
we're gonna take care of you.
We're gonna get you help.
Come on. Come on.
- Come back.
- No, no, no. This is no good.
Yeah, yeah.
Back injuries are common.
Not as common as knee injuries,
But more common than
than wrist injuries.
I don't need
a history lesson, okay?
What do you think
history is?
Just-- We need to get her out of there
Because no one is going to want to go in there
With a woman writhing around
on the floor.
Wait, wait, wait.
But most importantly,
We need to get her some
medical attention asap. Stat.
Rrroar!
Ramming speed.
Here we go. Here we go.
Out of the way.
Move it or lose it.
- You having fun?
- Oh, my god, what happened?
Oh, just having too much fun.
Phyllis, we're gonna put you in here.
Dwight's gonna take care of you.
What? No. I ought we were going
to the hospital.
If you want to get sick,
you go to a hospital.
Okay, dwight.
Okay, good.
I do not want anybody
to worry.
- What happened to phyllis?
- Ooooh, you know.
Nothing. She's--
We were hanging out
at cafe disco,
And she had a flare-Up
of an existing injury.
But she's a tough old bird, so...
can you please go back to work Instead
of masterminding these situations
Wherein we hurt ourselves.
Okay, fine.
Phyllis did injure herself.
But she injured herself
having fun.
And i don't think she would
trade that memory for anything.
I would like the memory of a day
uninterrupted By this nonsense.
You all took a life
here today.
You did.
The life of the party.
- Erin...
- yes?
I want you to go downstairs,
And i want you to shut it down.
You mean, like, unplug the coffee
machine And bring it up here?
I don't care; bury it.
I hope you're happy.
Okay,
i'm gonna need
two able-Bodied men.
Cafe disco.
More likecrappedisco.
Oh, bad.
There's girls in there.
- Where?
- The other room.
- What other room?
- Down the hall.
- There's girls in there?
- What'd i just say?
- You get me my sandwich?
- Forget the sandwich.
Girls. Girls!
I guess they got
what they want.
I am eating alone.
Might as well be dinner.
Comfy? All right.
All right.
Just relax. Relax, okay?
Dwight. Dwight!
Come on, relax. This shirt
wasn't doing you any favors.
If my assessment is correct,
You grind your teeth?
I do.
No kidding.
She sits three feet from me.
It's the most annoying
thing. Unh, unh.
Like children singing
christmas carols.
Oh, yeah, i'm wanting
the vibe down here.
Ashley, you made it!
You invited someone?
Oh, yeah.
Was i not allowed to do that?
I don't know, i've been here
eight years, And i've never--
Rude.
I'm not sure, but i'm pretty sure
I'm in a Cafe disco
Cafe disco is dead, But i can
still hear the music in my head.
I hear it too, boss.
Better than imagined it.
That feels good, dwight.
Tell me where it hurts.
Right-- Ooh!
Right there.
Oh, yeah. You've got
a knot in your crest.
This remedy has been passed down
in my family for generations
And it always works.
My grandfather was told that diamond
dancer Would never race again.
They were wrong.
He came in ninth
in the apple creek derby.
And his jerky came in third
the following year.
A majestic beast.
So fast, so tender.
Welcome, welcome.
Cafe disco. I am michael scott.
Hey, angela, welcome to--
Stop it.
Angela, angela, angela,
May i interest you in a triple
expresso, Or perhaps a dance?
No. I didn't come down here
to get wet and wild.
I just need you
to sign these.
Oh. All right.
There you go.
- You need to sign them all.
- No, no, no. ???
One signature for every song.
Look, i hate to bethatperson,
But i just don't like
the general spirit of music.
I know, i know. Angela, a lot of
people doubted cafe disco at first,
But it is a magical place.
You have to give it a chance.
If these walls could talk,
they would say,
"This is a magical place.
You are safe here.
We are talking walls.
We're not going to eat you."
No!
This is oil from the gland
of an otter.
It keeps their fur water-Resistant
As well as traps heat.
Now i need you to lie still
for an hour.
An hour?
I can't stay here an hour.
Whoa, whoa, whoa, girl.
Whoa.
Boss, this used to hang
from my windshield,
But it belongs in here.
Hey, thank you, creed.
You really get this place.
No problem. I'll just have no idea
who's driving behind me now.
Look out.
Here we go.
- Ho!
- Yeah!
???
Here we go, okay--
Something's gonna happen.
Here we go. Yeah!
Oh, yeah!
Whoo!
here we go
yeah, Wow
Whoa!
Whoo!
I'm gonna go
with the python.
Oh, but the r
so scary.
No, please...
i find the rattle soothing.
Puts me to sleep.
I think bob's gonna cheat
on me with his new secretary.
What's so funny?
When i say it out loud,
it-It's so silly.
Hey, hey, angela,
no-- No cleaning up!
You are forcing me
to be down here.
Am i not allowed
to have some fun?
No cleaning up.
These are for you.
They're beautiful.
- You ready?
- Yeah.
We should probably stop by.
It would mean a lot to him.
Hey. Hey!
- Hey
- Jim and pam!
Can you believe this?
It's really happening!
You wan dance, dwight?
Ordinarily i would say no.
But you need to move
to reduce lactic acid build-Up.
Also, this song is fantastic.
Mind if i steal my wife?
You can't steal what is
legally your property.
Are those staples?
This dance competition
is not over.
What dance competition? I was just
dancing casually with my friends, ya!
Yeah, right!
You guys are the best
for coming.
You don't have to stay
if you don't want to. I understand.
Oh, we're gonna stay.
Really?
At least for one more dance.
Oh, ho, not me, not me!
Get out of here.
Cafe disco!
Hey! Come on, man!
We're not even on the "y."
- This is so cheesy.
- Yes.
i like cheesy.
Me too.
You know, i think maybe
i want aweddingwedding.
Me too.
- Really?
- Yeah.
Would you like to dance?
No.
???
Women
Stop squirming. Well, stop trying
to poke me With a sharp thing.
You wanted to do this, okay.
Just be brave.
I know, but you're not a professional,
And i'm thinking maybe we should have gone--
I'm doing--
No, i'm doing it for free.
Just, you have to stop squirming
Otherwise i'm gonna mess up.
Are you sure that's not
the gay ear?
- Gayare you 12 years old?
- Well--
- Look, i'm gonna count to three.
- Count to 20.
No, i'm gonna count to three.
One, two, three.
Ow, son of a bitch!
Andy, that was just
the ice.
- it was???
- ???
welcome to www.1000fr.com
www.tvsubtitles.net