What is this?
happy holidays, Dwight.
but do not open it till Christmas.
you are so pathetic.
how long did this take you? three hours?
five minutes, actually.
i am a black belt in gift wrapping.
yeah, no such thing.
they don't give out black belts
for things that are stupid.
well, i hope it was worth it
'cause i'm gonna take it apart
in about five minutes.
i think it'll take you a little
bit longer than that.
really?
if i can skin a mule deer
in less than ten minutes,
i ought to be able to cut my--
www. 1000fr. com presents
capture:frm@summerwind
sync:frs@ирон
the. office. season05. episode10
i'm sorry, it's the
largest one i have.
i will not be the
big guy in the tiny hat.
this is the first Christmas
party i'm throwing
as head of the party
planning committee.
the theme is "night in morocco. "
this isn't your
grandmother's Christmas party.
unless, of course,
she's from morocco,
in which case it's very accurate.
hey, phyllis,
do i need this invite
to get into the party?
- yes.
- awesome.
i think this is going to be
the best Christmas party ever.
Angela. . .
you're going to move this
for the party, right?
it's not our theme.
it's the nativity scene.
all right. . . you can keep your camel,
- sheep, elephant.
- hey.
and the north african king can stay.
everything else goes in the drawer.
i am not gonna judge phyllis
for desecrating Christmas.
there is one person who will, though.
and phyllis just stuffed
him into a drawer.
i need you to get rid of the tree.
- but--
- thank you.
oh i don't think it's blackmail.
Angela just does what i ask her to do
so i won't tell everyone
that she's cheating
on Andy with Dwight.
i think for it to be blackmail,
it would have to be a formal letter.
ah, you brought in
your doll collection.
these are not dolls, Jim.
these are commodities,
the same as gold or oil.
every year i do research to determine
which toy will be the most
popular of the Christmas season.
this year it's a doll--
half girl, half unicorn.
catch phrase: "my horn can pierce the sky. "
pathetic.
i bought out every store in the area
over the last couple of weeks.
and as lazy parents
become more desperate,
i will sell them at an enormous profit.
isn't that right, princess?
that's the Christmas spirit.
i am simply punishing those parents
that would wait till the last
minute to give their child a gift.
and such a genetically improbable one.
look at that. how does that happen?
the king had sex with a unicorn?
a man with a horn had
sex with a royal horse?
yes. oh, hey, is that princess unicorn?
i thought they were all sold out.
- they are now.
- cool.
my horn can pierce the sky
this is equal parts scotch, absinthe,
rum, gin, vermouth, triple sec,
and two packs of splenda.
i call it a one of everything.
oh, my god!
- hit me again!
- all right,
one more time around the block.
it will grant you one wish.
i wish you would stop rubbing
that lamp in that creepy way.
stupid--everybody knows
to ask for 100 more wishes.
dumb.
hey, hey, ange, check it out.
there's a place in france
where the naked ladies dance
really, Andy?
it's Christmas and you're
singing about nudity and france.
there's a hole in the wall
where the men can see it all
Jim, check that out.
what is it?
that is vodka, and i mixed
it with orange juice.
i call it an orange vod-juice-ka.
- wow, that is delicious.
- yeah.
- i can't believe no one's thought of it.
- i know!
belly dancing.
120,180. . . 200.
all right.
ah, thank you so much.
my daughter is gonna love this.
- so glad i could help.
- thanks.
- merry Christmas.
- you too.
fa la la la la la la ka-ching
oh, so this is what
every day would be like
if you hadn't left india.
oh, oh, oh, oh! burnin'.
make way we got a live one!
on fire!
i'm all right.
sorry.
we're back on the fifth.
should we just do it then?
we cannot do it then.
monthly dental appointment.
soft teeth.
what about february 2nd?
uh. . . would you want to
do it on groundhog day?
no, no. i celebrate privately.
that's right.
um, why don't we just do it now?
we'll do it quickly.
now? it's our Christmas party.
- we'll do it quickly.
- what if we can't do it quickly?
what if we can't so it quickly?
what if we can't do it?
do you know how to do an intervention?
hey, shut up.
here we go. everybody gather up.
an intervention,
it's sort of hard to describe.
but really it's--
it's a coming together--
it's a surprise party. . . for people
who are-- who have addictions.
and you get in their face
and you scream at them,
and you make them feel really
badly about themselves.
and then they stop.
it looks like we're gonna
be here for a while,
so why don't you make a little
plate of hummus for everyone?
little triangles of pita
toasted on both sides,
fanned, so you can easily grab them.
- i don't--
- and napkins.
fanned.
okay. . . how do you feel?
- a little better.
- i threw up.
ecch. t. m. i.
fire girl!
- too soon.
- yeah.
okay, you know what i thought we should
do is have a quick intervention,
and then get back to the party.
Michael, we're only allowed to talk
about meredith's work performance.
we cannot ask her to stop drinking.
i am not asking her to stop drinking.
i am imploring her
to quit being an alcoholic.
i'm not an alcoholic.
yeah, obviously you are.
okay, everybody who thinks
that meredith is an alcoholic,
please raise your hands.
aye.
the ayes have it.
i don't care what everyone thinks.
i know i am not an alcoholic.
all right, well,
let's look at this a little
bit closer then. shall we?
when i was in college
i used to get wicked hammered.
my nickname was "puke. "
i would chug a fifth of so-co,
sneak into a frat party. . .
polish off a few people's empties. . .
some brewskis, some jell-o shots.
do some body shots off myself.
pass out, wake up the next morning,
boot, rally, more so-co, head to class.
probably would have gotten expelled
if i'd let it affect my grades,
but i aced all my courses.
they called me "ace. "
it was totally awesome.
i got straight "b"s.
they called me "buzz. "
meredith,
have you ever used alcohol
to alter your mood
or deliberately change
your state of mind?
sure.
do you sometimes have a drink
to celebrate a special occasion
or mark a holiday?
obviously.
have you ever,
under the influence of alcohol,
questioned the teachings
of the mormon church?
where did you get this?
i got it on a web site.
that's not important.
Michael, we should contact some experts.
she don't know what you're doing.
you know what, toby,
one of my employees
is undergoing a crisis.
and i wish for just once
you would take my side on this.
i'm doing your job, man.
hey, are you texting?
yeah, 'cause this is kind of a drag.
alcohol is a drag. yes.
here's what i'd like to do.
i'd like to go around the room
and have us each express to meredith
how her alcoholism has affected us
i'll begin.
this Christmas party is perhaps
the best Christmas party
i have ever been to.
but then you got so drunk
that we had to stop and do this.
that's how your drinking affected me.
anybody else?
another time when meredith's drinking
affected you?
come on, people.
if we don't say anything,
she's not gonna get any better.
yes, kevin.
well, meredith, there was that one time
you bought movie tickets,
and then you got too drunk to go.
so you gave them to me.
and that was really cool.
that's--you didn't--
you weren't hurt by that.
yeah, you said affected by it.
thanks again. you're welcome.
no, that's not what we're going for.
who has a problem with
meredith's drinking?
it has to bother you.
it bothers me, right?
how does it bother you? Dwight?
don't you have anything?
no. i like meredith.
actually, i don't care for meredith.
but i don't believe
in this kind of thing.
in the schrute family,
we believe in a
five-fingered intervention.
awareness, education, control,
acceptance, and punching.
who's gonna tell us
the latest dirty joke?
who is going to tell us what
you watched on television last night?
i am fine.
was john belushi fine?
was bob hope fine?
come here.
if anything ever happened to you,
i would be very angry at myself
for not doing all that i could do.
i know i drink.
i like to party.
i want you to say "i'm an alcoholic. "
i'm not an alcoholic!
you can say it as loudly as you want,
but we're not going to believe you.
i was waiting until later to hand out
this year's gifts from corporate.
i don't think
they're appropriate anymore.
please stop making me do these things.
oh, sorry, it's your job.
it's the season of mercy.
you never showed me mercy
when you were in charge.
why aren't you wearing the hair net?
i lost it.
fine.
okay.
nice.
i don't mind telling you
that i have an addiction.
i do. . . to porn.
all right. no, no, no. no.
that is--the image,
i think we all can agree,
is very disgusting.
but you know what, meredith,
you lit your hair on fire today.
what about tomorrow?
what is going to happen
when you come in to work
and you're dead?
i stab her in the brain
with a wooden stick.
there are several ways
to kill a zombie.
but the most satisfying one
is to stab it in the brain
with a wooden stick.
everyone in this room loves you.
but mark my words,
we are not going to support
your alcoholism anymore.
the next time you light
yourself on fire,
we are not going to help put you out.
oh, as fire marshal, i would have to.
Dwight--
she is a hazard to the other
people of the office.
oh, okay.
i suppose i could do it
if it was a controlled burn
in a well-ventilated area.
yeah, but you're gonna
need a permit for that.
oh, right, that'll take a couple of weeks.
- i can get you one in an hour.
- really?
okay, you know, this-- this is over.
i agree.
Michael, i think you did
the best you could,
but this is bigger than all of us.
enabler.
enabler. enabler.
enabler. enabler. enabler.
it's Christmas,
and we are turning our back
on somebody who's asking for help.
you know what the only thing
i want for Christmas?
i want meredith to get better.
that's my only wish.
but you know what,
my wishes never come true.
so i'm not going to wish that on her.
**
they've been in there for 45 minutes.
i know.
if she wasn't an
alcoholic before, she is now.
that's a halwa shebakia cookie.
they serve it during ramadan.
it's great.
hey.
- what's up?
- you take requests?
- sure.
- please stop.
because we're having
a Christmas party.
i'll be down in a minute.
could you write down the number
of that rehabilitation center
that you mentioned?
sure. wow.
ow.
we just missed poor richard's.
- we did?
- yeah, i thought we were
-going out for a drink.
- oh, shoot.
oh, well, we'll have to go
someplace else then, i guess.
- well, the bog?
- yeah. . .
- cooper's, Kelly's. . .
- we could go there, sure.
- brixx's, carmen's. . .
- yes.
- the fort, Andy gavin's?
-i have a new place.
it must have just opened up.
it--yeah. recently.
yeah. all right. all right.
enough of this Christmas crap.
let's get some party music. yeah!
yeah. oh, there you go.
yeah! that's good.
yeah, that's better.
we're party girls.
hey, sasha, it's daddy.
have you ever heard of
this doll, princess unicorn?
no, no, no.
no, i'm just curious if you heard of it.
this is great.
my ex-wife's gonna be so pissed.
for once, daddy's gonna be a hero.
- 200?
- yo.
hey, i'd like to buy one of your dolls.
oh, that's my last one.
oh, no. i--
no, no, i was gonna--
i was gonna buy that doll.
thanks, man.
i was gonna get the doll.
i was--
not my problem.
but i-- i promised my daughter--
darryl, look, i--
i need that doll.
i need the doll. i'm begging you.
i just--i need it more
than anything in the world.
i need this doll.
darryl, man, i need the doll.
okay, all right, man. don't cry.
it's cool.
i'll let you get it for 400.
i only have 200.
you can owe me.
oh, man, thanks. thanks.
thank you, man.
thank you.
i know, right?
merry Christmas.
oh, thanks. she's gonna--
oh. . .
something wrong with the doll?
no.
it's--it's even, um--
it's even better than the one i wanted.
sunrise rehab?
no! no!
no! i told you no!
- there is no way. no way!
- it's okay.
it's all right.
there is no way! there's no way.
meredith, we're doing this for your own good.
- okay. come on.
- there is no way.
- there is no way!
- here we go. this is gonna be good.
no way. i told you.
we talked about this.
there is absolutely no way!
- there we go.
- there's no way!
no! there is no way! no! no!
- all right, here we go.
- i am not going in there!
- yes, you are. yes you are.
wait a minute, wait a minute,
wait a minute, wait a minute!
- wait a minute. just wait. just wait.
- calm down.
no! oh--
oh, my god! oh, my god!
no! no! no! no!
oh, my god.
come on. shh.
no! there is no way! there is no way!
- here's the door. here's the door.
- there is no way!
- no! no!
- let's start meeting--hello.
- this man is crazy.
- how are you?
- can i help you?
- this man is crazy!
- i have a deposit. alcoholic.
- no! no!
- so do i sign?
- nooooo!
i need you to put
the Christmas tree back up.
it's outside.
i didn't ask you where it was.
i told you where it needs to be.
shut up.
excuse me?
i'm not moving the tree.
face it, the only power
you have over me
is this little secret that
i know you're not gonna tell.
oh, and you wanna know how i know that?
because then you won't be able to plan
your stupid, tacky parties anymore.
so you move the tree.
okay.
Angela's having sex with Dwight.
i caught them doing it after
toby's going away party.
well, don't look so surprised.
- i knew it.
- you did not know it.
i knew some of it.
everyone knew some of it.
it's Christmas.
you knew it.
thank you.
- i knew it.
- she knew it.
as it turns out, you can't just
check someone into rehab
against their will.
they have to do it voluntarily.
and they have to hit rock bottom.
so i think i know what
i need to do at this point.
i need to find ways to push
meredith to the bottom.
um, i think i can do it.
**
all right, everybody's
still here--perfect.
got a little surprise
i've been working on.
Angela, my bride,
i just wanted you to know
that for the rest of our lives,
no matter the cultural milieu,
i will always be there to bring you
some Christmas cheer.
deck the halls with boughs of holly
fa la la la la la la la la
tis the season to be jolly
don we now our gay apparel
fa la la, la la la
troll the little old yule tide carol
roo da da da doo
ra doo doo doo doo doo
i think i'd like to go home now.
sure.
ooh. . . tough room.
come on, i just learned it.
just so you know, protocol
is a little round of applause.
but merry Christmas to all,
and to all a good night!
www. 1000fr. com presents
www.tvsubtitles.net