good morning. can i help you?
yes,i'm from techstar about
a new phone system for you.
i was wondering if i could
talk to michael scott.
i'm sorry.
he's not in right now.
really?
he's never around when i come by.
shoot.
they have new phone systems now that can ring directly to a
salesman,or someone presses star and they go to accounting.
basically,95% of my job.
but i'd like to see a machine
that puts out candy for everyone.
vending machine.
how about i make an
appointment to come back?
that way i know he'll be her
that is a great idea.
great.
um... oh,boy.
let's see,he's really...
michael scott,manager. hi,how are you?
there his.
- nice to meet you.
- great.
yeah. hey,look at that.
i can assure you we don't
need a new system,though.
happy with ours.
hello,may i help you?
jimbo.
jim?
okay.
i'm,uh,i'm gonna bgoing.
what was that?
that was funny.
thatwasfunny.
let's go do it to somebody else.
- =www. ydy. com/bbs=- Proudly
Presents
- =www. ydy. com/bbs=- Sync:
YTET- °îµÂÖí
the office
Season 5 Episode 16
oh,look at that.
cupids and hearts.
really shoving our
faces in it this year.
you doing okay,bud?
i miss stacy.
yeah,i hear ya.
it's been four mon since i wawith holly.
and she was way hotter than stacy.
- so if you think you're
hurting- i can't even imagine.
this is our first and only
valentine's day as fiances.
you're only engednce.
well,present company
excluded,but-
really,jim.
- on cupid's birthday.
- yeah.
she's
so i received my first
valentine from a secret admirer.
"roses are red,violets are blue,"
it's time for your dental
cleaning and maybe a check-up,too.
look at those.
how nice for you.
uphere front andene
teofr. fi ce beautiful.
i think they would
look better right here.
they're very pretty,and i
wouldn't want them to fall.
just about everybody in this
office is single right now,
including me,and everyone is experiencing
an incredible amnt of emotional pain.
especially me,because of my
great capacity for emotion.
and it is my first
valentine's day since holly,
so i think that i am
well-qualified to understand
that these people need to be protected
from having love shoved into their faces.
pam,really?they're back?
i can't see them when
they're on the floor.
they're for her to look at,michael.
- could i have a word with you,champ?
- yes,let's have a word.
yes.
um,jim.
today's a ry difficult day for
a lot of people in this office.
- oh,i'm sorry.
- yeah.
and the sexy looks between you and
pam- the general sexiness,the flowers-
it's creating a bit of a
hostile work environment.
- i understand,yeah.
- it's so sexy it becomes hostile.
oh,i actually thought we
were keeping it pret low-key.
- well,if you guys insist on having your own private little love fest...
- we do.
that none of us can be a part of...
you can't be a part of
our relationship,michael.
then we are going to have our
own private valentine's day party.
- that sounds fun.
- so suck it.
- yeah.
- yes.
hey,everybody.
i just invited jim to suck it,and i am cordially
inviting all of you to a special convention-
a- a lonely hearts
convention this afternoon.
singles only.
yeah!deal with it,pam!
so we may not have someone
in our lives that we love,
but we do have each other.
having trouble finding a vein?
yeah,a little.
how about now?
i've trained my major blood vessels
to retract into my body on command.
also,i can retract my
penis up into itself.
i am about to give blood.
the gift of everlasting life.
the transfer of my
bodily fluids- n wow!
that's a big needle.
- that- you're gonna
need to lie down over here.
okay.
- hello.
- hi,i can't talk right now. i'm sorry.
oh,okay.
i'm really nervous.
yeah. me,too.
yeah?
- when i get nervous i sort of
clam up and- oh,well,that's fine.
it's better for me just to be quiet.
yeah.
- yeah.
- can i point something out to you?
- sure.
- you're actually talking a lot.
yeah?sorry,that's the other thing
i do when i get really nervous.
okay. here we go.
all right,here we go.
oh,god.
just relax.
yep,i'm good.
i feel like a human juice box.
oh,god.
uh,hawaiian blood punch.
oh,that's gross.
type o-cean spray.
god,stop.
stop it.
- i want to pick the movie.
- i get to pick the movie.
um,why don't you guys come
and have lunch with bob and me?
we'll take all afternoon.
michael is terrified of bob.
what do you think?
i have a lot of work
to do this afternoon.
those mines aren't
gonna sweep themselves.
so. we're in.
what?
i looked at the bag.
i looked straight at the bag.
- that's not good.
- could you distract me for a second?
just talk about things that
don't have blood in 'em.
well,okay.
uh-
bags.
- what?that-
sorry,that was bad.
that was mean.
um,a hat.
- a hat.
- a hat with no blood in it.
that is full of soup.
you're cute.
- what?
- you're done.
oh,already?
ah,we did it!
i was so nervous about this i
don't think i ate for three days.
is he okay?
oh,my god. how long was i out?
what?
excuse me,waitress.
where did the lady go?
oh,she left.
okay.
oh,wait a second. wait a second.
that's hers. this is hers.
she ft her glove.
i need her name if i'm
gonna return her glove.
oh,i'm sorry,sir.
we can't give out that information.
what are you doing?
decorating.
i'll help.
now it's just a stupid baby.
yeah. thanks.
it is so nice to go out with another
anything to get out of that office,huh?
i know.
i honestly don't know how you can work w
i and that other jack-ass
and that new jack-ass.
he's talking about
michael,dwight,and andy.
oh,yeah. i understood.
well,here we all are.
alone but together.
no flowers for us.
relationships?
we don't need no stinkin' relationships.
i think we should all go around and tell our
worst relationship story and then get past it.
just blow through it.
yeah?
kelly,what about ryan?
he treated you pretty terribly,yeah?
well,his heart was in the right place.
yeah,but now his heart is in thailand- along
with the rest of his body,having random sex.
okay. sorry.
let's-
who else?
oscar?
i don't think so.
come on. i'm sure there's something
you need to get off your chest.
- thank you. - youanna-
just- anything?
you sure?i'm sure whatever
you did wasn't your fault.
okay,well,we'll-
who else?
everyone here who's bowled
a 280 please raise your hand.
no way. 280?
that's impressive.
okay. noeveryone here who's
bowled under 70 raise their hand.
yikes.
- come on,bob. raise your
hand. - no,bob,not- no!
- what?
- one time. you just love bringing up that one time.
- don't you?
- i do,i do.
jim uses a six-pound ball.
that is a lie.
yes,he bowled five frames with this pink,sparkly
thing until a little girhad to ask for her ball back.
but that girl must have had
monstrous hands because the holes fit.
no,you just have little dainty fingers.
you could always model ladies' jewelry.
nobody asked,bob.
do you risk telling them how you feel?
do you say something that you
can barely admit to yourself?
- oh,god,what
did you do?- so-
wait,not that i approve
of any of it,but-
i was stupid. i told him.
was he into you in,like,a gay way?
moron.
if he was,there wouldn't be a story.
he told me he wasn't gay.
really sad.
i'm not done yet.
oh,my god.
a week later,a friend of
mine calls me up and he says,"
i just saw him in a
gay bar in kansas city.
" oh,no.
well,then it's a happy
ending,because he was gay.
you should call him.
my worst breakup was
actually two breakups.
two different men.
i was in love with both of them,and when
things went bad,they had a duel over me.
yeah,dwight and andy. we were here.
no,this was years ago
when i was living in ohio.
john mark anjohn david.
angela,you had two sets of
different men actually duel over you?
i guess i have.
all right.
who's next?where's andy?
he's on one of his honeymoons.
what?
he made non-refundable
deposits on his honeymoons,
so he's just knockin'
'em off one at a time.
i think today he's hot air ballooning,and
later he's got a couples' massage.
my worst breakup was with stacy.
it was a sunday morning.
we were reading the par.
and i said,"oh,my god.
i think the eagles could
clench the n. f. c. east.
" and she said that we're done.
you know what,ys?
i don't think we need to do this.
you're right. okay,everyone,back to work.
no,no,no,no. i mean,have
this kind of party.
i look around and i see all these beautiful
people who are alone on valentine's,
and i think that there are other
single people out there,too.
we just ne tfind 'em.
there's a girl out there for all of us.
maybe even in this office park.
there has to be a way to get
all these lonely people together.
a net?a giant net?
no,not a giant net.
- a- a- a- what
do you have in mind?
i was thinking maybe like a mixer.
- oh,god. that's a terrible
idea. - old-fashioned meat market.
- no.
- i don't think it is.
lonely people mixing with one another?
breeding?
creating an even lonelier generation?
you're not allowing natural
selection to do its work.
kind of like the guy who
invented the seat belt.
these people need love.
and i am going to get it for them.
who cares if we sell a
little bit less paper today?
a great boss cares more about thhaceppiness
of his employees than anything else.
********
i am going to be cupid,and i am going to
shoot my sparrow at unsuspecting victims,
and they are going to get
hit,and say,"i'm in love!
i was hit by cupid's sparrow.
" funny little bird,but
he gets the job done..
no movement.
ah,still early.
eh,it's not that early.
so how you holding up?
i'm okay. feel a little lopsided 'cause of
all the blood they took out of my right side.
no,no,i meant about being single today.
exactly.
oh,here we go.
- hello.
dwight k. schrute.
why don't you introduce
me to your little friend?
- dwight
- babe alert!
hello,i'm michael scott. welcome
to our little shindig.
oh,hi,i'm lynn.
- lynn,follow me. come on in.
- off we go.
for you,we have one of our top people.
kevin malone.
kevin?come out here. show
your beautiful self.
hello.
so run with the ball.
run with it,kev.
where are you from?
i'm from here.
y-
okay.
well,he only gets better.
- thank you,michael.
- okay.
i can untie any knot.
i'm serious.
name a knot,any knot. go ahead.
uh,i- i
believe you.
you shouldn't believe
everything you hear.
in fact,there are many
knots that i cannot untie.
so where does a woman as charming as yourself
find herself employed on a day such as today?
um,i work at a place that does catalogs
for community colleges and small businesses.
you must use a lot of paper.
oh,god. tons of it.
what's the rule about when
people are in the bathroom?
i think if you ordered hot
food,you're allowed to eat.
damn.
they've been in there
for like ten minutes.
look at that.
bob ordered hot food.
yes.
and i think they gave
him too many fries.
we should help him out.
all right,the circle
drive-in,they show old movies.
it's really cool.
that does sound cool.
i used to go there with my fiancee.
before she left me.
no,i- i mean,before
i left her.
she left me.
stupid!
i think i blew it.
it all happened so fast.
so fast.
so erik,you mentioned before that
you are in tool and dye repair.
i am.
meredith recently had
a total hysterectomy.
so that's sort of a repair.
I right. i'll let you guys talk.
it's going very well. people are mixing.
a lot of hope.
'cause that's what you hate to
see- when hope gets crushed.
sorry.
thought i heard somebody coming in.
um,so... it's not too late.
and the kind of discoun we're talking
about are not- hold on,hold on.
michael,why do you keep
looking at the front door?
- no reason.
- is somebody after you?
why do you always go to that?
has anyone ever been after
anyone in this office?
hey,it just takes one.
nobody's after me.
i just- i met a woman when i was giving
blood and i thought she might come by.
you met a woman when you were
giving blood?that is so romantic.
it's not a big deal,really.
i just- you know,met
mebody. we hardly talked.
i picked up her glove,so i was
hoping i could give it back to her.
oh,my god,that makes
it even more romantic.
this is like a modern-dayenchanted.
it's like a fairy tale.
she could be your soul mate.
oh,not likely.
three billion women on the planet,most of them
live in asia,so the numbers just don't add up.
- it's possible.
- she could be.
believe me,it's nothing.
i hardly even talked to her.
we just- we were lying
there next to each other.
i think our blood bags touched.
here they come.
- what?
- no,just kidding.
seriously,though,that's enough.
well,just cover it with the broccoli.
- oh,great,i have to cover it with-
do you think they dined and dashed?
well,they didn't dine.
so yeah,maybe they just dashed.
i thought we we having a nice time.
we were.
yeah.
- empty.
- mine,too.
oh,boy.
- okay.
- oh,my go
is this the party?
nah.
okay,then.
so where were we?
ah,bowling.
yep,yep. yep.
you didn't eat much there,jimbo.
oh,initially i did.
want some meat?
- oh,sure.
- little piece.
no mushroom,though.
- forgot.
- yeah.
thank you.
i'm sorry we did not have
a chance to talk more.
yeah.
i get very nervous
talking to pretty girls.
seriously.
feel how sweaty my hand is.
that's really sweaty.
are you on email?
oh,yeah.
cool.
- okay,bye.
- bye,kevin.
good valentine's.
so basically the greater volume you decide to
buy in,the greater discount we can give you.
- okay.
- okay?
- what's up?- look,i'm-
i'm gonna go.
before you go,i'd st love to
get a firm commitment on this.
um... you know,maybe sign?
look,we already have a paper supplier.
okay.
well,thanks for wasting my time tonight.
idiot.
god!
you don't deserve her.
thanks,michael.
hey,if anybody
wants to go-
- we can stay a little longer.
- really?
yeah. yeah. sure,michael.
no,this is great.
we'll hanout. absolutely. yeah.
oh,thanks.
michael,it's time.
you know what?you guys-
you guys can head out.
i'm- i'm gonna
soldier on a little bit.
come on.
we'll all go.
yeah. yeah. let's go. yeah. okay.
four months ago,i dated
a woman named holly.
and,um,this is actually the first time that i've
even considered getting back into that arena again.
you know what?
sometimes it's not about whether
cinderella gets her slipper back,
but it's about the fact that the prince
even picked up the slipper at all.
there's a lot of princesses out there.
you know,they have all different
sizes and shapes of feet.
and hands.
so i think... i think
my odds are pretty good.
pardon me. may i have a
chocolate chip cookie?
i gave blood earlier and
i'm still feeling woozy.
of course.
that's weird.
you got a cotton ball and tape
and we've been using band-aids.
i,uh- oh,i
feel so woozy.
i just- it's
band-aids.
ah,damn.
- =www. ydy. com/bbs=- Proudly
Presents
- =www. ydy. com/bbs=- Sync:
YTET- °îµÂÖí
www.tvsubtitles.net