You gonna answer that, kev?
Right. Thanks.
Dunder mifflin.
This is kevin.
Please hold
while i transfer you.
Oscar, your mom.
Charles is having kevin cover
the phones for a while.
How do i say this
diplomatically?
I think kevin is doing
exactly as well
As anyone might have expected
someone like him
To perform in a position
like that.
Please hold.
Andy, phone call.
No, stay there.
Kev, i thought we nailed the
whole transfer thing earlier.
Yeah, i wrote it on my hand.
But then i washed it.
It's transfer, extension,
then transfer again.
Okay.
Andy, get ready.
- transfer, Extension
- Here we go.
- transfer.
- Ah.
Oh, man.
It is 134.
- Kev.
- Kev, come on. Hustle.
- You are murdering
the nard dog.
- this is kev...
Please hold,
and i will transfer you.
- You're bad at this too.
- just Don't answer that call.
Just transfer the damn call.
Your call is very
important to us. Please...
- hey!
- Ho!
Andy bernard.
My maid died.
www.1000fr.com presents
Capture:summerwind
Sync:FRS@mzinfo
The office 520
Today's my first day
at my new job
At michael scott paper company
incorporated.
You know, apple computer
started in a garage.
And we're starting
in a condo.
Soe cealady have a leg up
on apple.
Look,
it's official.
Oh, good,
my hooker's here.
Kidding.
Hi.
Michael, you were
expecting me, right?
Yes, i was.
A you wearing anything
under the robe?
That is inappropriate, pam.
Come on in.
This looks great, michael.
Thank you.
Would you like
some french toast?
Yes, please.
What shape?
- Square is fine.
- All right.
Just wanted to fill you in
on a few details.
As you know, i will be running the branch
while we search For michael's replacement, So
please feel free to come to me
With any questions or concerns.
Yeah.
Where will you be staying
while you're in scranton?
Stay?
In a hotel.
Charles, where were you born?
Actually, i meant questions More about the
day-To-Day operations of the company.
Okay.
Yeah?
How are operations
at the company?
Just day-To-Day.
Okay, let's go over
non-Discretionary cuts. Okay, guys?
thank you
- So...
- can you please stop that?
- What?
- You're breathing very heavily.
- His is how i breathe.
If you have a problem--
- No, it's not.
Okay, jim halpert.
- I need your eyes up front.
- Oh, no, i was just...
no, hey, hey.
I just want to hear, "yes."
Yes.
Good.
As i was saying...
oh, no,
the new boss
do not find jim adorable. Oh.
So what do you say
we get started?
After breakfast.
I'm full.
So how you feeling
about the new company?
I feel good.
Wow.
You excited
about the new mpany?
Yeah, i'm excited
to start the company.
After breakfast.
We did that.
So what's next?
Michael, just stop
for a second.
- Michael, stop for a second.
- No, i'm whipping it.
- No, i know you are.
- Just let go.
- Just let me have the--
- Let go, please.
- Just give me--
- Fine.
Oh, i'm sorry.
I'm sorry.
I can't do this.
This is pathetic, isn't it?
I am such an idiot.
I gave up the only job
i ever loved to do this?
I have egg in my crocs.
I never see him drink.
I never see him eat.
I don't think he even uses
the bathroom.
Oh, he does.
He does.
I feel weak today.
I felt much stronger
yesterday.
Like benjamin button
in reverse.
You know, michael,
when i feel overwhelmed...
i'm not overwhelmed, pam.
I know. No, i'm saying
that when i feel overwhelmed,
Something i like to do
is make a list.
Make a list of things to do
And then start
with the easy stuff.
- Whatever calms you down.
- Okay. First,
work out.
And, hey, look, you did that.
Check.
Eat an enormous breakfast.
- Check.
- Don't patronize me, pam.
I think you
should get dressed.
I'm not getting dressed.
I'm not getting dressed. I have too
many things to do before i get dressed.
I need to find 100 clients.
Michael, that seemsmpossible.
It's totally impossible.
We need to come up With
one realistic thing
that we could do today.
Assemble a sales team.
A dream team.
Great.
Okay, ryan.
No. What? Why?
He's everything i'm not,
and everything i am.
He's the whole package.
No, we're not gonna hire ryan.
Um, oh, vikram!
Best salesman i've ever met.
- Okay.
- He worked
at that telemarketing place.
- We'll find him.
- Okay.
Oh, also, we have a meeting this
afternoon With a potential investor.
- Really? We have
an investor already?
- yeah
Maybe. Barbara kevis.
She invests in local businesses.
And i'm putting together
a little presentation for her.
Michael, that's fantastic.
Yeah, i guess
it's not so bad.
Got a few things cooking.
- Um.
- Hey.
We need to get you dressed.
I have doubts about this too.
But when one person freaks out,
Sometimes it weird makes
the other one calmer.
That's one thing i've learned
about relationships.
I hate that i just used
the word relationship.
Hey.
You look great.
- Let's go.
- All right.
Ah.
You a soccer fan?
Oh. Oh, yeah.
I'm so embarrassed.
You weren't supposed to see this.
This is like my secret obsession.
Well, that makes two of us.
- No way.
- yeah
I hate soccer.
But guess
who doesn't hate soccer?
Charles minor.
I was actually in germany
for the 2006 world cup finals.
Oh. You bastard.
That should have been me.
Yeah, i love the sport.
I love the sport.
- All right, man.
- Cool.
I've never been a kiss-Up.
It's just not how i operate.
I mean, i've always
subscribed to the idea
That if you really want
to impress your boss,
You go in there
and you do mediocre work.
Halfheartedly.
Next on the list,
open the mail.
Oh, wow.
Michael scott paper company.
Okay.
Very official.
"Dear mr. Scott,
"Please be advised
that it is in violation
"Of yourondominium agreement To conduct
a business headquartered "In your residence.
The penalty of forfeiture
of residence..."
No, okay.
It's fine. It's fine.
We're just gonna add,
"find office."
How are we gonna find
an office?
How can we pay
for an office?
??? Song parodies.
Okay, okay.
Achy breakfart.
Great. Let's sing it in the car.
No, no, no.
My stumps.
Likemy humps,
but a guy with no legs.
- Yeah.
- We can do this.
We can do this.
Whoa, and he just goes boom.
- Yeah. Score.
- That's pele.
You know your soccer, man.
I prefer maradona.
Diego maradona
from argentina.
I didn't know we had so many
soccer fans in the office.
I mean, to be fair, i was the
first one To talk about it, but...
what about you, jim?
Are you a fan of the game?
Oh, no. No.
Not really.
Well, it's not for everybody,
i suppose.
That's 'cause i'm more
of a player.
- Yeah?
- Youet.
- Really, jim.
I had no idea
you played soccer.
'Cause you never,
ever talk about it.
- Well, i do. I play.
- Wow.
- You can be so modest sometimes.
- Maybe we should get back to work.
Maybe you and charles should
kick the soccer ball around.
Maybe we will someday.
Maybe you will tonight
after work. What do you say?
That's a great idea, dwight.
Great ideas are just part
of what i bring To the table.
I don't try and be anything
that i'm not.
What do you say, jim?
Huh? Wanna play some soccer?
- Jim, what do you say?
- Hey, anybody else?
- I'm in it to win it.
- Sounds fun.
- Game on.
- Okay.
See you on the field there, bro.
- See you.
- See you on the field.
I can't wait.
Yup, i used to play
soccer in school.
From second
to fourth grade.
I was on the orange team.
- We got vikram.
- You got me.
Where are we going?
We have a meeting
with an investor today.
Yes, we do.
So get excited.
But i have to go
to the bathroom real quick.
If you'll excuse me,
i'll be right back. Okay.
He seems really confident.
- He can be.
- Confidence--
It's the food of the wise man,
But the liquor of the fool.
Hmm.
I'm looking forward to getting
to know you better, vikram.
Hey,
i would like a pair
of size nine, please.
- It's michael.
- I'm swamped, michael.
Happy birthday to sally
in lane 27.
Okay, imagine a company that has
no memory Of your past misconduct
because they have no files.
He's taking a long time.
Is it possible
he's bowling?
I mean, you know him
better than i do.
Yes.
Yes, it's possible.
Well, it has alwa bn
a lifelong dream--
Michael.
What's going on?
- I am--
- Hey, ryan.
- ???
Excuse me.
Yes?
- This wasn't on the list.
- Yes, it is.
- No. It's not.
- Yes. It is.
When did you add this
to the list?
Pam, everyone deserves
a second second chance.
Ryan, just out of curiosity,
How much do you get paid here?
$60,000 a year.
You get paid by the year
at the bowling alley.
What do you make, secretary?
Back to work, shoe bitch.
I told you guys,
i'm really busy here.
Would you like to come to work
For the michael scott paper company?
What size shoes are you guys?
- Uh, nine.
- What are those? A men's ten?
No.
- Look what he's doing.
- What is he doing?
He's stealing 'em.
Okay, okay.
- Oh, my gosh.
- He's already paying
for himself.
Sorry!
- Where is it?
- Right here.
Hey, come on, guys, tse are
prime selling hours, you know.
- Minor...
- oh, there he goes.
- Sees his partner, halpert...
- yikes.
- He looks up, defend doyle...
- oh, man.
He shuts him up. come on
He shuts him up.
- Yeah.
- alright
oh!
Goal.
Man, i can't wait
to play with you.
Oh, it's gonna be the...
worst.
Do you guys wanna hear
about thailand?
- Oh, yeah.
- Sure.
It was indescribable.
Sounds awesome.
What sort of investing
club is this?
Vikram, you ask a lot
of questions, and i like that.
Hey, na.
Hi.
- Na?
- Michael.
People turn to their families All the
time when they need help starting out.
And if my na's investment club can help The
michael scott paper company become a reality,
Then i'm sure that's
what she would have wanted.
Does want.
Well, i'm sure that you must all
have very, very busy schedules,
So i appreciate you meeting
with us here today.
What this is is a business that
i have worked toward My entire life.
Hey.
I have assembled what i believe
to be The most exciting,
sought-After talent
In the industry today.
Ladies and gentlemen,
i present to you the dream team.
From our very own scranton,
pennsylvania, pam beesly.
Pretty pam is always reaching
for the stars,
And someday she may just
surprise us all And grab one.
Meet vikram.
From his humble beginnings as a--
Stay standing--
From his humble ginnings
as a prominent surgeon,
He risked it all to become the
most successful telemarketer
In the lipophedrine industry.
And do not call it
a comeback.
The youngest vice president in
the history of dunder mifflin
And recent bowling alley
employee, ???
??? Of a splash in paper.
- So let's hear it.
- Okay.
I have spent
the last 15 years
Learning the ins and outs
of the paper industry.
With a lean, mean fighting crew
and low overhead,
I thini can perform
the same business
At a much,
much higher rate of profit.
How do you expect to turn
a profit in this economy?
By wanting it more.
By working hard.
What's your mission statement?
My mission is stated as follows:
I will not be beat.
I will never give up.
I am on a mission.
That is the michael scott
guarantee.
Come on, oscar.
What positions
do people play?
- Wing.
- Leg.
Jim, what do you play?
- Left.
- Forward or half?
- Forward, definitely.
- Okay, striker, huh?
- Striker.
- Let's see what you got
in those legs. All right.
- All right, let's do it.
No, no, no.
No, there's supposed
to be the kickoff.
Kickoff.
My strategy is to touch
the ball as little as possible.
Chalk it up to teamwork.
All right.
And i offer same day,
free delivery.
Michael,
i don't know about this.
Nana,
i really think that papa
would want you To do this.
I'm not so sure.
Well, what ist exactly? What--
What specifically?
It doesn't have to be paper.
We could sell medicine
and other...
see, this is what concerns me.
We could just give him a chance.
It's not much money.
Well, this may not be
the right time,
But i need more
than i originally asked for.
It's ???? an investment club.
- Okay.
- I love you, michael. I do.
Okay.
But no.
I mean it. No.
I thought nana raised
some good questions.
What kind of a name
is nana?
It means grandmother.
Oh, sweet jesus.
Look, i'm sorry to do this,
But can you drop me back
at the telemarketing building?
You know, michael,
you want to succeed?
You got to apply the same--
Get him, jim.
Come on, tough d, jim.
- AH!
- Oh, my god.
Oh, wow.
Jim, what the...
phyllis, are you okay?
Are you okay?
No, i swallowed a crown.
Why'd you duck, jim?
- What?
- Yeah, jim, why would an experienced
scer player Like yourself
duck at the very last moment?
Okay, i'm just gonna go get
some ice.
Does that make
you feel better? Huh?
- I-I'm sorry, phyllis.
- Oh, yeah, jim's sorry.
Do you get tnt?
The station? Do you get tnt?
Yeah, i have cable
and satellite as a backup.
Yeah, i know, two not-So-Great
things in a row.
Well, well, stuff happens. Right?
At least we got ryan.
The ry-Guy.
We should call him ry-Bread.
We don't have to call him that.
Unless you like it.
We could call him that.
I can't do this.
What's that?
I had a real job.
I sat ten feet away
from my fiance.
I had health benefits.
I was just feeling impulsive. I should
have gotten a tiny tattoo on my ankle.
Yecch.
I just keep getting bored.
And i let things build up
and build up,
And then i do something
too big.
Like this.
Who does this?
Well, you know what? My mom
always used to say that average people
Are the most special people
in the world,
And that's why god made
so many--
We don't have any money.
We don't have an office.
We don't have anything.
Well, we should make a list.
Lists are good.
Lists are good. Lists are good.
First on the list, let's get
you out of the car. All right?
Okay.
How come out of everyone
in the office,
I'm the only one
who went with you?
Is it because i'm that stupid? I mean, your
own grandmother doesn't even believe in you.
I want you to listen to me.
Because i want to tell you
The situation that
we are both in right now. Okay?
You quit your job.
I quit my job.
We both quit.
Those are the facts.
That's what happened.
Now what are our choices
right now? Because,
you know what, kiddo?
You quit.
- Yeah.
- So what are our options? Well...
we can start this
paper company. We can try.
Or that's it.
That's o only option.
Because we quit.
Pam, i do my best work when
people don't believe in me.
I remember in high school,
My math teacher told me
i was gonna flunk out,
And know whai did?
The very next day,
i went out,
And i scored more goals than anyone
In the history of the hockey team.
See what i mean?
I thrive on this. I thrive on it.
So i'm gonna go inside.
I'm going to make
some calls.
I'm gonna get us an office space,
And i'm going to show you
Why you joined this company,
all right?
You gotta have some extra
space, billy. Work with me here.
There's gotta be
some sort of secret office
That you have lurking around.
Something awesome and free.
And you keep it off the books.
Oh, no, not there.
That would be humiliating.
I did what i had to do.
I stepped in.
I took charge.
That's what being a man is.
And earlier today,
i was freaking out.
Pam stepped up. She was the man.
Don't think
a woman can be a man?
Well, then that's
your stereotype. Not mine.
Okay.
I could work here.
I could see this.
It's right in the middle
of the pap belt.
Are you good?
Yeah, i'm good. You good?
I'm good.
You know what they say.
Keep your friends close.
Michael.
- You're back.
- Yes, i am, charles.
Except this time you have
no legal right to kick me out.
Because i have started my very own paper
company Right here in the building.
If i were you, charles minor,
I would watch your step.
Because the michael
scott paper company
is about to open A big old can
of whoop-Ass on dunder mifflin.
Actually, a six-Pack. We're gonna
open a six-Pack of whoop-Ass.
He looked scared.
welcome to www.1000fr.com
www.tvsubtitles.net