Dunder mifflin. This is pam.
I'm sorry. He's not in yet.
Would you like his voicemail?
Yeah!
Yeah,okay!
12 miles an hour.
Eat that,carl lewis!
Angela made
several 9-1-1 calls
About cars going too fast
in front of the building,
So the police put up a radar gun.
It's actually caused a
bit of a traffic hazard.
Aah!
Wow,13!
No,no.No,there was wind.
I was just jogging.
Dwight,there was wind.
- I want a do-Over.-
No,no,no. It's not your turn.
All right,13 is the new number.
Oscar,go ahead.
I want another try. Here we go!
31! 31!
There was a car.
I was ahead of the car.
31 is my new number.
31 is humanly impossible.
Go,oscar. 31's my numb.
- That's impossible.
- Beat it.
-=Www.Ydy.Com/bbs=-
Proudly presents
Sync:ytet-∂¨„ﬂµ‰ˆÌ
the.Office.Season05
episode11
Today's a big day.
My presence has been requested by
Chief financial officer david wallace.
He says that he wants to
talk about big picture stuff.
And i'll be honest,
I have little or no idea
what that means,so...
Probably bad.
Quick announcement.
New year,new candy.
Whoo-Hoo!
Okay,be careful,kevin.
They're kind of spicy.
Hot tamales.
Yeah.
So maybe just try one at first,
And then if it's
okay,have a couple more.
Excuse me,everyone. Can
i have the floor please?
Um...
This is insanely awkward.
It's kind of the elephant in the room,
So i'll just...
No one has rsvp'd to our wedding yet,
And the deadline was yesterday.
Wait,you still
don't know--
No,no.
Nope.
- Hmm?
- Nothing.
- You still don't
- Why don't
- Let's
- What are you doing?
How about
we just--
I just have to talk to you for a second.
- Andy,has anyone
- Ahh!
No,no one has rsvp'd,
And i don't understand it.
And now you're shutting me out.
And you're not even listening.
And that's really considerate.
- Thank you.
- No,what i'm saying is
- No,no.No,that's not it.
- I know.
Andy still doesn't know
That angela's having
an affair with dwight.
And it's been 17 days.
I mean,eventually he'll figure it out...
When their kids have giant heads
And beet-Stained teeth.
But right now it's just...awkward.
How can he still not know?
- We can't figure that out.
- I can't take it anymore.
Wait,what? You can't take what?
I am telling andy.
No.You n't do that. It
shouldn't come from you.
Who should it come from then?
Angela. Angela.
From angela.Angela.
Are you still having
intercourse with her?
What is wrong with you? She is engaged.
Did you ever have
intercourse in this office?
Are you serious?
Ugh. Where?
Where?
Where,dwight?
Seems like you already know where.
Kevin,you screwed this form up again.
The amount owed goes at the top.
Oh,i'm sorry.
I didn't realize i was
doing something wrong.
If i had,i would've admitted it
And stopped right away.
That's enough.
Because i wouldn't
want an innocent person
Who doesn't know
anything about the form--
What?
That was good.
It jt at the end,you
weren't saying something
That could also apply to the form.
How about "i'm sorry i
did such a whorish job
Filling out this form."
There you go.
That cannot be true!
You're going to charge me a e
To cut my own cake?
Uh,no. No,no,no.
What i'm saying is i
want to cut it myself.
- Trade seats with me.
- No.
I've got a better angle on pam.
I can see everything.
Please stop.
I need a soup spoon.
Rule 17.
Don't turn your back on bears,
Men you have wronged,
Or the dominant turkey
during mating season.
There are 40 rules all
schrute boys must learn
Before the age of five.
Learn your rules
You better learn your rules
If you don't
You'll be eaten in your sleep
What is it?
You've got to tell andy about us.
That is a terrible idea.
- One of your worst.
- Get it over with.
Then we don't have to hide anymore.
You're expanding on your worst idea.
Do you love me or not?
I've already admitted that i do.
Why do you keep making me repeat it?
Because you're engaged to andy.
Well?
- Not yet.
- When?
When what?
You know this can't go on.
- What can't go on?
- We have to put an end to this.
- Seems like
- Come on.
You guys should...
Be hearing what i'm saying.
This is really not how
this is supposed to happen.
Angela said she was gonna tell him.
She's just not ready.
- When will she be ready?
- I don't know.
- Is she crazy in bed?
- Yes.
- Stop.
- How so,specifically?
What? Okay,listen.
- This shouldn't happen at work.
- Eager and flexible.
- And...
- Really?
This shouldn't be coming from his boss.
And we should also consider the fact
That that man has an anger issue.
Too late.
Well,it's not too late,'cause
you haven't done anything.
I am already walking.
Michael,once this gets out,
I don't know how it's gonna go down.
Okay,what does that mean?
Might get ugly.
Jim,this has to get out
So we can all deal with it.
But you're leaving.
- Have a good trip.
- Thanks.
- Andy.
- Yeah?
Walk with me.
Will do,boss man.
Oh,i do not have much time.
Car's all the way over there.
To tell you what i have to tell you.
And just bear in
mind that when i say--
Say these things...
That are bad things that you hear...
In your ears,
This is something that i...
If i were you,that i
wouldn't want to hear.
You're not making any sense.
Well...
No,i'm not.
So i-- I'm not very
articulate today,
So i'll just leave it for another time.
- Another day.
- All righty.
- Which'll be
- Fine. I'm off.
- Have a good meeting.
- Thank you.
Kick wallace's ass.
Okay,i will.
Dwight and angela are
having an affair,so.
I can't hear you through the glass.
Dwight and angela are having an affair.
They've been sleeping
together for some time.
That was the news.
I wanted to let you know.
What? All right.See you later.
- Are you serious?
- Yep.
I knew something bad
was gonna happen today.
You said that yesterday.
Yeah,my neighbor got murdered.
What are you standing for?
If i'm sitting,
I can't disable his neck or his groin.
You're not gonna do anything
to his neck or his groin.
If i'm sitting,i don't
have the option to.
Dwight,i'm in charge
when michael's gone,
And i need
you to sit--
I need to talk to you.
We can talk right here.
I need to talk to you in private.
We're not listening.
Let's go to the conference room.
Is it true?
What have you heard?
That you're sleeping with dwight.
That doesn't sound like me.
Is it true?
Andy,i'm engaged to you.
I mean we just signed off
on our wedding flowers.
Would i have said yes
to formal chrysanthemums
If i didn't want to get married?
And we went through all that
stuff with our wedding cake--
Just answer the question.
Are you sleeping with dwight?
A little bit.
How long has it been going on?
I don't know.
I mean,we were together,
And then he killed sprinkles.
And then we stopped,and...
I don't know exactly
when we started up again.
Who else knows about it?
- Michael.
- Who else?
Let me think about it.
Oh,god.
Come on!
So listen,michael.
Your branch has been doing great lately,
D ur sales staff is reporting
Very strong numbers.
Outperforming last year,in fact.
Um,and i don't know
Exactly how to put this,
But...
What are you doing right?
- Right what?
- Utica,albany
All the other branches are struggling.
But your branch is
reporting strong numbers.
Look,you're not our
most traditional guy,
But clearly something
you are doing...is right.
Ani just-- I need to get
a sense of what that is.
David,here it is.
My philosophy is basically this.
And this is something that i live by.
And i always have,and i always will.
Don't ever for any reason
Do anything to anyone
For any reason ever,no matter what.
No matter
wh--
Where,or who,or who you are with,
Or-- Or where
you are going,
you've been...
Ever...
For any reason whatsoever.
Sometimes i'll start a sentence,
And i don't even know where it's going.
I just hope i find it along the way.
Like an improv conversation.
An improversation.
This is gonna sound
sort of high maintenance,
But could we have it,like,three
degrees cooler in here?
I always think better when it's cooler.
Here's the thing.Michael
is doing something right.
And in this economic climate,
No method of success can be ignored.
It's not really a time for executives
To start getting judgmental now.
It's hail mary time.
Hey,
What say we order up some pasta?
What say we do.
Standard,you know? Nothing fancy.
So,like,missionary?
I said nothing fancy.
Do you love him?
I love you.
Why should i believe that?
Andy,we are at a crossroads here.
And we can either give in
to what people are saying,
That we're not
good together--
Who says that?
Orwe can prove them wrong.
Let's prove them wrong.
Where's dwight?
- You okay,man?
- No.
Not at all,actually.
But thanks for asking. Appreciate it.
You know what?I'd also like
to take this opportunity
To thank all of you for lying
To my face.
And not telling me what's
been going on this entire time.
You are welcome.
Dwight.
Andy.
It's over.
Oh,good. She broke up with you.
No.
It's-- It's over
between you two.
Uh,no way.
I am not giving up.
- You have to.
- No,i don't.
She doesn't love you.
She's marrying me.
Well,i don't know about that
Because she certainly seems to enjoy
Making lovemaking with me.
Angelabernard.
Will never be her name.
It will be her name,
And you will have to call her that.
I don't think so.
Hey,guys,why don't we,uh,
Just cool off a bit?
I'm telling you to back down.
And i'm telling you that
i will never back down.
- Then i'll make you.
- Oh,really?
How are you gonna do that?
Through the use of force.
That is very general
And does not scare me in the slightest.
- I will fight you.
- Nope.
Okay,fine! Good!A duel.
The winner gets angela.
- Fine!
- This is nuts.
- What is your weapon?
Okay,you know what,that's
enough because--
Hey,this is none of your business.
Hey,it is my business
when it happens wk.
Guess what,
- Not happening at work.
- Yes.
- We're gonna do it outside.
- Outside of work.
- None of your business.
- None of your business then.
Good. So what weapon?
- My bare hands.
- That is stupid.
I will use a sword,and i
will cut off your bare hands.
Then i'll get something too.
I'vead two men fight over me before.
Usually it's over which one
gets to hold the camcorder.
Angela,you have to put
a stop to this right now.
I will respect the results of the duel.
- Of course you will.
- I call los.
I will be taking my break at 4:00
In the parking lot.
I will also be taking my break
At the exact same time
and in the same location.
What a coincidence.
So i either get more involved
Or i take a sick day...
Leaving dwight in charge.
Oh,god.
How'd that get there?
There's a star-Shaped thing
taped under the kitchen table.
Thanks,meredith.
So i was in the office,
And i look over to our
accounting division,
And there is kevin malone.
Kevin is wearing a jacket
That i've never seen before.
And i call over to kevin,
"Kevin,is that a tweed jacket?"
And he looks at me and he says,
"Michael,yes,it is a tweed jacket."
And i look back at him and i say,
"I feel the need...
The need for tweed."
So.
It's hard to try and
evaluate yourself,michael,
But i appreciate you trying.
- And thanks for coming in.
- Oh,thank you.
Yes.
Have to say,i am so impressed
With the potential you see in me.
Yeah.
Yeah,finish up.
Come on!
Where are you?
Let's do this thing!
Come on! Come on out!
I can't believe they're
gonna fight over me.
I guess people have fewer
choices as they get older.
Come on!
Hey,has anything happened yet?
- Where are you?
- Mm. It's 4:10.
I don't think he's gonna show.
Oh,come on,man.
Believe in something.
Come on,coward!
Where are you?
Where--
What?
"From the desk of andrew bernard."
A note. Pathetic.
"Dear dwight,
"By now you have received my note.
"How are you? I am well.
"You are no doubt wondering
"why i have left this note.
"It's come to my attention "that
in any physical match with you,
I would surely be bested."
True.
"The soft underbelly of my refined
upbringing is my soft underbelly."
There's andy. He's in his car.
You guys,what is he doing?
Why isn't dwight turning around?
The prius is silent if he keeps
it under five miles per hour.
He deserves the win. Yeah.
"Alas,after much consideration
and deliberation-- "
Oh,my god!
What's happenin'?
Andy's running over dwight with his car.
Whoa-- What
are you--
- Hey! Hey!
- Yeah!
- Oh! Ho!
- Come on  ow!
Ah! Aah!
- You give up?
- Never!
Get out and face me like a man!
I am a man!
I'm a bigger man than you'll ever be!
I would never sleep with
another man's fiancee!
You're not a man!
You don't know how to take care of her!
All you do is dress fancy and sing!
La la la la la la la
What does that mean?
You can't even protect her!
Protect her from what?
Bears,you idiot?
When's the last time you
saw a damn bear in scranton?
Last year,idiot!
Dwight.
Are your legs broken?
No,my right one's falling
asleep a little bit.
Andy,are you all right?
Go away,tuna! I'm winning this.
Yeah,back off. This isn't your fight.
Oh,how ch is this gonna cost?
Oh!
What? Trust fund'll take care of that.
What did you say?I'm
sorry. I couldn't hear you.
I
said--
What?You stupid idiot!
You're like a--You're
like a sasquatch.
- You live in the woods.
- Sasquatches are the strongest animal on the planet!
So fine,call me a sasquatch.
I don't get it.
How could she be sleeping
with you this whole time
And only sleep with me twice?
- What?
She's sleeping with you?
I'm her fiance.
She said she was only sleeping with me.
Yes,hi.My last name is bernard,
And i would like to cancel a
wedding cake that i had ordered.
B-
E-R-
N-
A-R-D.
Yeah.The one shaped like a sailboat.
Yep,that's the one.
Thank you.
Wow,what a day! Ha ha!
I thought i was gonna get chewed out.
But hold on!
Here's an attaboy for you.
What?
Roller-Coaster ride.
Roller-Coast.
Just goes to show,you leave scranton,
Exciting things can happen.
Ahh!
-=Www.Ydy.Com/bbs=-
Proudly presents
Sync:ytet-∂¨„ﬂµ‰ˆÌ
the.Office.Season05
episode11
www.tvsubtitles.net