Hey??Sports.
I heard someone got engaged.You dog!
Ah!God??
Oh.. Nothing can hurt you now.
You are a man in love!
I was there and that dudes are not engaged.
I'm not a big believer in therapy but
???
Big idea
Double wedding,me Angela,you and Holly
No. We would never do that.
And we did it would be with Jim and Pam.
Yeah. We would never do that.
Yeah,so there you go
Michael. I got my bridesmaids dress.
Oh,wow.So quickly
Yeah and you said I could get it in any color I wanted,
so I picked white
Oh. Michael did you tell your mom yet?
No
- No,Not yet
- Why not, why not?
- Wouldn't tell???
- What???
- You love??
- I do
- Call your mom...
- She should be the first????
Yeah???
I'll call???
- let's??
Call her!Call her!Call her!
I don't want
All right. I'll call her.
She is going to freak out
- Speakerphone
- Not...
Hello
Mom. I'm getting married.
No, you're not...
Why do you always do that?
Whenever I'm getting married,
you don't believe me.
Are you getting married?
No
- Are you...?
- I'm not
I'm not getting married
Psych
www.1000fr.Com presents
Capture:FRM@ив╬х
Sync:FRS@Dwight
The office
Season5 Episode06
So I returned
my bridesmaid dress,
And it was on sale,
So I'm out $100.
And i'm out a fiancee.
- Those are customer surveys?
- Yeah.
Um, this is all of them.
Jim, Dwight, Phyllis,
Stanley, Andy...
And, oh...
Oh, it's the receipt
to my bridesmaid dress.
What's that doing there?
I'll take care of
that for you.
Thanks.
Kelly kapoor
Is our dusky, exotic
customer service rep.
And once a year
she will contact our clients
And find out how happy they are
with our salespeople.
Sort of a kapoor's list.
Schindler's list parody.
That's not appropriate.
No.
Those reports affect
our bonuses.
Which is kind of
great for me
because,You wouldn't know
from looking at her,
But pam's a gold digger.
Hey, new york ain't free.
Now get back to work.
Ah.
It's the world's
tiniest bluetooth.
I found it in a japanese
gadget store in the village.
I got one for jim too.
Jim, say something.
Testing, testing.
Hello, everybody.
We wanted to stay
on the phone all day,
But the company has a policy
against Eight-Hour personal calls.
So we're not telling anyone.
Uh,Pam,What do you want
in your coffee?
Sprinkle of cinnamon.
I should go.
All righty, Dwighty,
let's see how you did.
- Bring it on.
- Nooo...
Sorry
- Wow.
- What does it say?
Dwight, your feedback
is horrible.
That's impossible.
A number of your clients
found your personal style
Abrasive and distasteful?
- I sell more paper than anyone.
- No, no, no, no, no.
Wait, is this a joke?
I'm getting that queasy feeling
that sometimes accompanies jokes.
Do I look like
i am joking?
No, but that's
sometimes part of it.
If i were joking,
you'd be laughing.
Do you look like
you are laughing?
Impossible to say.
I can't see myself.
You're not.
Yo, tommy tuna,
- Did you get your scores yet?
- Nope.
I got mine.
They were really good.
I miss him.
You must be really proud.
Yeah, pretty psyched.
Whoa!
That's my mug.
Oh...sorry.
It was just--
It was right here.
Right, well,
It's mine, so,
If you could pour it out
and get another one.
Okay.
Or maybe i could
finish the coffee in here,
And you can use...
Oh, snoopy.
He's funny.
Don't give up snoopy.
That's mine.
That is a great mug.
But it's not my mug.
That is my mug.
So...give it back.
How can you even be sure?
It has my face on it.
Make the face.
No, i don't see it.
Dude, that is my face.
What was that?
Wow.
That was Dwight.
He seems upset
about something.
Describe him exactly.
What color mustard
is his shirt?
Yellow or dijon?
It is more of
a spicy brown, actually.
What are you
mumbling about?
How was your meeting
with michael?
None of your business.
Was it your scores?
Those can't be
my scores, jim.
- For your information...
- mm-Hmm.
I'm being sabotaged.
Of course.
And i'm gonna find that person
and punish them.
Absolutely.
Or you could just be nice
to your customers.
- You're an idiot.
- There's the charm.
Jimbo, let's do this thing.
That is me.
Wish me luck.
- No way.
- Good luck.
Thanks.
I didn't say anything.
- I love you.
- I love you too.
What do you think
i am saying to you?!
Not talking to you.
I've caught Jim talking to himself
several times today.
What a loser.
Get a friend, loser!
Yeah, i'm looking at it
right now.
It's really gorgeous.
You guys do great work.
I found the best "tentist"
on the east coast.
He personally tented giuliani's
first and third weddings.
And I got him.
I got him!
Would you be able to do
the same design,
But with walls of gray?
And a top that's gray too?
Fabulous.
Oh, come on.
- What?
- You too?
Did my scores drop
a little?
Jim, they are a poopy.
Jim?
Are we even sure
that's my file?
No.
Yes,I am sure, Jim.
It--
Well, there's gotta be
an explanation.
- I agree.
- Yeah.
So let's see what
we can find out from reading.
"Jim halpert is smudge
and arrogant."
I think you mean "smug."
- Arrogance.
- Michael, i'm just trying to--
And there's our smudgeness.
I need a decent bonus
Because I'm actually in the process
of buying my parents' house...
So that they can retire.
And if history
tells us anything,
It's that you can't go wrong
buying a house you can't afford.
Pam doesn't know
about the house, so...
Fun surprise.
Pam.
Sorry about that.
I lost you for a second.
So as it turns out,
I may not have done so hot
on my customer reviews this year.
Maybe it's because
you spent the whole year
Flirting
with the receptionist.
A little bit.
Worth it.
Here's what's going to happen.
I am going to have
to fix you.
Manage you two
on a more personal scale.
A--A more micro form
of management.
Jim, what is that called?
- Microgement.
- Boom. Yes!
Now, jim is going to be
the client.
Dwight, you're going
to have to sell to him
Without being aggressive,
hostile, or difficult.
- Let's go.
- All right, fine.
Bbbrrrrring.
Bbrriing.
Hello.
Hello,this is Dwight Schrute from
the Dunder Mifflin paper company.
Wow, that's great
'cause i need paper.
Excellent, then you are
in luck
Because we are having a limited-Time
offer only on everything.
Wow, this is
my lucky day.
Ask him his name.
What is your name, sir?
I am Bill Buttlicker.
Really?
That's your real name?
How dare you?
My family built this country,
by the way!
Be respectful,Dwight.
Please
Yes, Michael.
Would you hold on
one second?
- That's my other line.
- What?
- No--But i--
- Hello.
Yeah.
No, i'm just on the phone
with this stupid salesman.
He's so dumb.
I'm probably just gonna keep him
on the line forever
And not buy anything.
Yeah, okay.
It's up to you
to change his mind.
Sorry.
That was
a family emergency.
Oh, no.
What's wrong?
You know what,
that's private.
Boundaries, dwight.
Come on!
I'm sorry,
mr. Buttlicker.
As i was saying,
- we're having a limited--
- Sorry,you're gonna have to speak up
a little bit louder.
I'm hard of hearing.
He's hard of--
He's an old man, let's go.
Okay, as i was saying,
right now
- We are having--
- You're gonna have to talk louder.
Okay, our prices
have never been lower.
Son, you have
to talk louder.
- Never been lower.
- Louder, son!
Buttlicker, our prices
have never been lower!
- OK!Stop it!
- He--
That is totally inappropriate.
You never yell
at the client.
- You never yell at the client.
- Now, you listen to me,sir.
Here we go.
The three words
I would describe you as
Is aggressive, hostile,
and definitely difficult.
- Please, mr. Buttlicker.
- I'm irate right now!
- Give me the phone.
- Please give me another chance.
- Give me the phone.Give me the phone.
- Mr. Buttlicker--
I have to put you on
with my boss.
Well,I should hope so.
Who is this?
Hello, this is Michael Scott,
regional manager.
Well, this is
William m. Buttlicker.
Hello, mr. Buttlicker.
How may we help you?
Michael,I like the sound
of your voice.
You know
what i'm gonna do?
I'm gonna buy $1 million
worth of paper products today.
Yeah!
See how it's done?
Thank you very much, sir.
I don't think you'll regret it.
- See what i did?
- You are the master.
- There is one condition,Michael.
- Yes?
You have to fire the salesman
that treated me so terribly.
Don't do it,Michael.
It's a million-Dollar sale.
So it's called
the shangri-La tent.
It's two stories,
heated,
And it has a bridal suite
for my bridalal sweet.
It's just really simple.
Really tasteful.
I don't want to be married
in a tent like a hobo.
Hobos live in trains.
Nana Mimi can't be
in canvas that long.
Well,Nana...
Mim--
Okay, look...
This tent is awesome.
And it's in high demand,
so i really think
We should put a deposit down now.
Okay, fine.
You can have your tent,
But only if it's
in a field.
A hand-Plowed field.
Done, and done-Er.
There has to be a barn
that's old enough
That you can see the stars
through the roof slats
When you lay on your back.
And antique tools to look at
when you roll over.
Do you have a specific place
in mind?
No.
But anything within a five to
eight-Mile radius is acceptable.
On it!
Dwight.
Dwight
Get in.
- Are you serious?
- Get in!
- Okay,what are you--
- Shh!
- They might be listening to us.
- What's that?
- They might be listening to us!
- Who's "they"?
Customer service might be
monitoring this conversation.
In this car?
You never know.
Better safe than sorry.
What are you thinking of?
Who stands to benefit
from our downfall?
The mob?
Maybe NASA.
Could be the mob.
But then Dunder Mifflin would need to
be a front for money laundering,
And there's little evidence
of that.
Is there some evidence?
Ooh, cute shoes online.
How many shoes
do you need?
I don't know.
Two?
Maybe three,
if one wears out.
How many shoes
do you need?
I'm not talking to you.
Who are you talking to?
- Pam.
- She's not here,Jim!
No, she's not.
Yes!
I found it.
I found the perfect place.
A local bed and breakfast
on a 60-Acre beet farm.
And even better,
i have an in with the owner.
Oh, yeah,
we work together.
It's Dwight Schrute.
As in schrute farms.
So i'd like to re-Double
my order.
If you could put me down
for, um--
Wait. Shut up.
- I'm sorry?
- Shh!
Do you hear that?
- Hear what?
- Breathing.
Is that you?
Well, i am breathing, yes.
Well, stop.
Hold your breath.
I still hear it.
Who's there?
Kelly, is that you?
Hold on.
I need paper.
- Hyah!
- Aah!
Oh, my god,
you scared me!
Hear anything interesting?
What are you talking about?
I think you know.
You always say that,
and I almost never know.
What are you up to, girl?
Huh?
Phyllis put you up to this?
Stanley?
Are they paying you?
Are you accusing me
of something?
Of course I am.
I know you're the mastermind.
But you're too stupid
to do it by yourself.
- Okay...
- oh!
- Easy.
- Okay.
Let's head back
to the desk.
You just can't come into my nook
and call me stupid.
And maybe it you were a little
bit more nice and polite,
Then people wouldn't give you
such bad customer reviews.
Okay, the reason that i got
bad customer reviews
Is because i didn't!
There is a massive conspiracy
going on here,
And i know you're involved.
Dwight, get out
of my nook!
That's what she said!
Good one.
Hey
Sorry about dwight,
by the way.
Yeah, he's weird.
Well, we all handle it
differently.
I personally choose to handle it
like a normal person, but...
Okay.
Hey, how are you
and Darryl?
Um, we're cool.
Bye.
That was weird.
What was?
Have you ever had
a conversation with kelly
Where she didn't go on for 15 minutes
without taking a breath?
No, actually.
Did you do something to her?
I don't think so.
Well, something's off.
Hey, how's things?
- All right.
- Yeah?
Livin' in the moment.
Do you have any reason to believe
that kelly would be mad at me?
Oh,I don't play
the politics game anymore,Jim.
Can i tell you something?
- I played it full-On in new york.
- Mm-Hmm.
I played it high stakes.
For keeps.
Made it to the top.
But look what it cost.
Can i tell you
what else i learned?
Wait, that's pretty weird.
What?
Andy has a mug
just like that.
Oh, yeah, kelly gave them out
as party favors.
Remember?
You got one.
No.
What party?
Her America's Got Talent
finale party Over the summer.
That's crazy.
It was packed.
I thought everyone
was there.
You were there.
I remember you being there.
I wasn't,
but thank you.
Hey, do you know anything
about this party?
Yes,I said you
definitely should go,
But you wanted
to visit me instead.
I can't be the only one
who didn't...
Dwight...
Let me see
your coffee cup.
No!
- Is that it?
- No. Why?
No.
Okay, i'm gonna assume
that was it.
Here's the thing.
I think you're right.
I think it was Kelly.
I think she's mad at us
for not coming to her party.
Oh, man,I knew it.
- Who are her co-Conspirators?
- Probably just kelly.
Obviously.
I knew it.
- That's what i'm saying.
- Yeah. What?
You were right.
I was--
I was right.
- You were right.
- I was right.
- You knew it.
- I knew it.
You knew it
the whole time, buddy.
I knew it
the whole time,Buddy!
Wow!
Yeah! Whoo-Hoo!
Right,
dwight is loud.
Yeah! I knew it!
Yeah! Ha ha!
Whoo! Boom!
Kelly the whole time!
- Let's get her.
- No, no, no, no.
Dwight,Dwight,Dwight,
let's talk about this.
What's going on?
Why don't you tell us.
Nothing's going on.
Let me paint you a picture.
A little girl
from southern india,
Who, despite being welcomed
into this country,
Will now spend the rest
of her life in prison
For a crime she did commit.
Dwight
I was informed by these gentlemen
That the reports that you filed
may not entirely be accurate.
What?
I--
I don't know
what you're talking about.
This is the first
that i'm hearing about this.
Oh, come on!
You juked the stats,
cupcake.
We called about
a dozen customers,
and they all said that
they gave us great marks.
What's going on?
I love your tie,Michael.
Oh...
Kelly.
I was raped.
You cannot say
"I was raped"
And expect all your problems
to go away,Kelly.
Not again.
Don't keep doing that.
I'll give you one last chance
to come clean.
Just tell me
what happened.
Okay, all right.
Okay,I did it,
all right?
I lied, whatever.
Just fire me.
But you know what?
I did it because you guys
didn't come to my party,
And you said you would try to,
and then you didn't even show up,
And so you're bad friends.
We have our confession.
- I'm calling security...
- don't, don't!
Get away from that,
dwight, please.
You know what, she's got
a point about you too.
You do have a problem
dealing with people.
- See? I wasn't lying.
- You were lying.
- I was lying.
- Yes.
Jim,Dwight,
please excuse us.
But I want to be here
when you fire her ass.
I will call you
when it is time.
I have an enormous amount
of trouble
Trying to get people
to come to my place.
And I hate it.
I can't tell you how much
leftover guacamole
I have ended up eating
over the years.
I don't even know why I make it
in such great quantities.
Here's what
we're gonna do.
We are going to sit here
for a while,
Make it look good.
And maybe you should cry.
Can you make yourself cry?
No problem.
I think you should do that.
Pam beesly?
Hey. What are you
doing here?
Who's that?
It's alex.
It's pam.
I came to kidnap you.
There's free wine and cheese
at the chuck close retrospective--
Let's go.
Oh,that's gonna be great.
Who's chuck close?
Oh,I love chuck close and
his photo-Realist paintings.
But I have to work.
Uh, well, actually
there's something else
I'd love to talk
to you about.
Um, can we go somewhere else
to talk about it?
Okay.
That's it,I want to talk
to this guy.
Put me in his ear.
- Um...
- What's up?
I'm gonna take
a big leap.
And I want to tell you that
I think that you should not
Move back to Scranton.
Wow.
I'm gonna make
a bigger leap here.
He is into you.
Why did you come to New York
in the first place?
Because they have
a great design program,
And I wanted to see
if i was any good at it.
And I wanted to work
on my art too.
Right.
And that's why i think
you should stay here.
'Cause,I mean, you--Really,
you just got here, you know?
And you can't do new york
in three months.
You know,
it has everything.It has...
All the opportunity
is here.
All the--The whole art scene
is in new york.
You know, it would be nuts
to go back to scranton
Without getting
to fully experience it.
Jim's in scranton.
I know,
but all I'm saying is,
If there's even
a teeny tiny part of you
That really wants to be
an artist,
Then I think
you should stay here.
Because you don't want
to wake up in 50 years
And look back and wonder
what could have been.
And that is the end
of my speech.
I planned it all.
Anyway...
I will see you tomorrow.
- I'll see you tomorrow.
- Okay.
Is that the matsuhashi b400?
The world's tiniest
bluetooth.
- May I?
- Don't.
Congratulations on choosing
Schrute Farms for your wedding.
No, we haven't decided
on anything yet.
We're still reviewing
some options,
And it's gonna come down
to the numbers.
Well, then, why don't you
look over some of our materials?
Oh...hmm...
While i describe to you
the excalibur package.
In addition to the breathtaking
natural beauty
And smell of schrute farms,
I can promise you
that our grounds can be catered
To fit your exact
specifications.
I will work tirelessly for you
over the coming months,
And be
at your constant disposal.
Please feel free
To call or stop by any time
of the day or night.
That's very generous.
Well, you,
my good friend.
Have nothing more
to worry about.
This wedding is officially
out of your hands.
Oh, thank the good lord.
Deal!
Okay.
Um, what are we talking,
price wise?
- You already said deal.
- Yeah
Pay him whatever he wants.
Can't argue with that.
Dwight...
You are gonna make us
so happy.
welcome to www.1000fr.com
www.tvsubtitles.net