well, I should go.
All right.I'll tell everybody
here that you say hi.
No,don'T.I'm mad at them.
Why?What happened?
Not one of them called to
congratulate me on our engagement.
That they might be off the hook
for,because i didn't tell them.
What?Why not?
I just didn't,you know,want to deal-
- come on,it won't be that bad.
- Okay,you know what?
Here we go.
Uh,everybody,just wanted
to make an announcement.
- Pam and I are engaged.
- Hi,everyone.
I thought you were already engaged.
- Nope.
- That was roy.
She was engaged to roy.
Thank you,angela.
I got a gift for pam and roy.
- Do I have to get another one?
- Yes.
A little close what'soing on?
***
************
- ******
- *****
- No,nothing.
Nothing,michael.Just saying hi.
The tall guy got engaged.
- To be married?
- Yep.
Sorry.
-=www.ydy.com/bbs=-
Proudly Presents
YTET
- °îµÂÖí
The
office S5E02
pencils down!
Just kidding.Take your time.
today is ethics day.
After they finish the quiz,I'm
gonna run my first meeting here.
It's gonna be in-sane!
No,it's not.I have to
read from the binder.
I got it.I got it.
I took you to an intimate restaurant
then to a suggestive movie
there's nothing left to talk about
unless it's horizontally
let's get ethical,ethical
I wanna get ethical
let's get into ethics,
yeah let me hear dunder mifflin talk
your body talk let
me hear your body talk
All right!
Why are you helping
her?You're not even dating.
She's my friend,and
ultimately my strategy
is to sort of merge
this into a relationship
without her even knowing.
Okay,let's give it up
for miss holly flax!
thanks,michael.
Today we're gonna have a business
ethics seminar,because recently,
without mentioning any names,there
has been some misconduct at corporate.
And we have a very strict ethics
policy,and that employee has been fired.
Oh,come on.He's right there.
He was hired.
- Ooh,check it out,hired guy.
- Nice.
Okay,elephant in the room.
Let's talk about it.
Do I regret what I did?
Of course I do,even though it was an
amazing ride,and I'll give you an example.
Anyone see survivor,season six?
Anyone know joanna on that show?
In new york city,I hooked up with a
girl who looked exactly like that--
- indistinguishable,so...
- okay.
Well done.Good
speech,ryan.You're a good guy.
let's start discussing those questionnaires
that you filled in this morning.
"It is wrong to make personal
calls during work hours?
"Now,some of you marked
that you very strongly agree.
But ideally you would've
selected totally agree."
I thought very strongly agree"
sounded stronger than "totally agree.
"Corporate would like to emphasize that ideally
you would all totally agree with that statement.
Well,I think we can all totally
agree that holly is totally fantastic.
Thank you.
Okay,in fact,""spending a half hour at the
watercooler during work hours is a form of stealing."
- What?
- Yes,it's called time theft,
and it's the same as taking
money from the company.
Can anyonehink of examples of things
that are over-the-line time-wasters?
This meeting.
Can't set them up like that.
why is it okay for smokers
to take breaks all the time?
If I want to go outside and hang out once
an hour,then I'll just take up smoking.
I'll do it.I don't care.
I'll smoke with you.I got
a bag of cigars in my purse.
Stealing office supplies is another big ethical
area that there seems to be some confusion about.
Okay.Can we have a moment?
Can I talk to you for a second?
A lot of good stuff,and you look-
- you look fantastic.
- michael.
- Yeah?
- What should we be working on while you guys are talking?
Do some--do
some work.
People expect a lot
from these meetings--
laughter,sudden twists,surprise endings.
You need to be robin williams
and M.Night shyamalan.
You need to be robin shyamalan.
- Well,I just have to get through the binder.
- Well,it's...just.... you're kind of losing them.
- I am?
- Yeah,don't think about the stakes.
- It'll freak you out.
- Okay.
Well,Michael makes a really good point.
So,uh,let's just open
this up a little bit.
Say my name is lauren,and here
I am shopping in a supermarket,
and I steal a pencil.That's not right.
Lauren,enough with the pencils.
No,I have to go over
pencils and office supplies.
It's part of the ethics thing.
That isn't ethics.
Ethics is a real discussion of
competing conceptions of the good.
This is just the corporate
anti-shoplifting rules.
I'll drop an ethics bomb on you.
Would you steal bread
to feed your family?
- Boom!
- Exactly,andy.
Yeah,I took intro to
philosophy twice-- no big deal.
It's a trick question.The
bread is poisoned.
Also,it's not your real family.
You've been cuckolded by
a stronger,smarter male.
No,that's not how it works.
I would not steal the bread.
And I would not let my family go hungry.
okay,but we should get back to business.
Have any of you ever faced any
ethical dilemmas in the workplace?
anybody?
This is a chance for you to say
something without any repercussions.
Stanley?Oscar,come on.
Pass.
I will go first.
When I discovered youtube,I
didn't work for five days.
I did nothing.
I viewed cookie monster sings
chocolate rain about 1,000 times.
What was the dilemma?
To tell you or not,and I'm glad I did.
I feel very,very good and catharctic."
"I promise you that you are
not going to get into trouble.
You can say anything you want
with total and complete immunity.
- Oh,no,no.
- Yeah.Come on.Anybody?
- Let it fly.-
Okay,once--
once in a while,I--
I'll take a long lunch.
- A siesta.
- time thief.Time thief...fire him.
dwight,you've really never
stolen any company time?
Never.
You are a thief of joy.
- Anybody else?
- Yeah.
Sometimes I download pirated
music onto my work computer.
Who hasn't?Good.Good!What else?
No,no,I'd like to hear more about that.
I once reported oscar to the I.N.S.
Turns out he's clean,but
I'm glad I did it.
- Well,let's keep this party moving on.
- I'll go.
Have you guys ever met bruce
myers,the scranton rep for hammermill?
Bru-u-ce!
Well,for the past six years,I've been
sleeping with him in exchange for discounts
on our supplies and
outback steakhousegift ccat.
Jackpot.
Meredith,that is serious.
I-I mean,not onlythat f interest,But
there's also an exchangof goods.
Exchange of steak.
Have you ever had sirloin steak,honey?
that's crazy.That's crazy talk.
Meredith.
The merenator,""
sleeping with suppliers."
What time do we got?
You know what?That's a good
place to end it,right there.
This,I think,was a great ethics seminar.
She has given us a lot of
wonderful things to think about.
Right,what is wrong-- who's
to say,really,in the end?
I mean,because it is unknowable,but
let's give her a round of applause.
Holly,everybody.Holly.
Get back to work.
great job.
I am truly impressed.
That,uh-- you really pulled that
one out.Classic,classic meeting.
- We should celebrate.
- Michael,
there are some serious
issues with meredith.
I mean,all of you have done things wouldn't have done
myself,but meredith's actions are realver the line.
Yeah.
What you gonna do?
So,regarding the supplier,approximately
how many lhave th?
Liaisons?You mean mee i don't ow.
Once aonor six years,somethin,
ly it's not what she thinks,
nothing unethical happened and
that you just like to sleep around.
Am I in trouble here or something?
No,no.This is just a stupid formality.
No,it's not a formality.
Now,were ese,um,meet-ups just
personal,unreted to business?
No.I wouldn't havne it if it
wasn't for the discount paper.
There's not a lot
ofruruit in those looms.
For the love of god,wee
trying to help you,stupidag.
What ionon't understand
is-- why the steak coupons,
I mean,if you were already
getting the discounted paper?
Well,it's funny.
Maybe it's a girl
thing,but after we did it,
when he would give me those
coupons,I just felt good about myself.
Hey,what's going on here?
I thought I had immunity.
well,unfortunately,immunity or something being
off the record does not really exist workplace.
I mean,I've never heard of anyone whkept
their job after something like this.
Well,I'm not quitting.
Yawn-- four
seconds.
What are you doing?
Oh,you had said that you don't do anything
personal during work time,so I'm just making sure.
Oh,wait a minute.So you're
gonna time me every time I yawn?
That absurd.
Really?
Oh,hey,look,monkey knows how
to use a stopwatch,everybody.
He's
ti--
Personal conversation--
17 seconds.
There is no
wa that was--
One second.
Well,well,holly-lujah.
It's a miracle.You're at your desk.
It's mike-raculous.
Ooh,ooh,reaching.
You'll get there.Anyway,
I was giving it some thought,and there's no
reason that two attractive,good-looking...
intelligent,funny,attractive
people can't,you know,
just sit down and work this
whole meredith thing out.
Sounds g good.
Would you care to
bang it out over lunch?
Oh,I already bought this.
Oh,no.No,no.
Your food is no good here,my lady.
Oh,sorry.
You know what?Let's go
out,dunder mifflin's treat.
actually,you're not a
client,so we'll just split it?
Ethical.
So I've gone over corporate policy.
What do you think?
What do you think of this place?
- oh,it's very nice.
- isn't it?
Yeah,it's kind of business/romantic.
So you're from des moines?
Wow,that sounds so warm.
In summer.
Here too.
You know what my favorite season is?
Maybe we should talk
about meredith first.
Yes.Yeah.Get the boring
stuff out of the way.
Autumn was what I was gonna say.
When the leave change,it's just-- I-I think
it's the most contemplative of seasons.
Okay,so I've gone over
this,and I've thought about it,
and I just don't think there's any way I can write
a report that doesn't end with her being terminated.
Terminator.
I'm from the future.
Yeah.
Hey,andy.
Yo.
By any chance,did you see
battlestar galactica last night?
No,I did not.Is that any good?
Actually not.It is really so-so.
Okay.
I mean,I like all the crazy
monsters and stuff,you know,
like klingons and wookies
and all that,but...
sorry,was there something
you wanted to add,dwight?
Is that anything like the
original battlestar galactica?
You know,it's weird.
It's practically a
shot-for-shot remake.
Really?
Huh,that's cool.
Story's kind of bland.
- It's about this guy named dumbledore calrissian,
- okay.
Who needs to return
the ring back to mordor.
It's really...
that doesn't sound right.
I just don't want my employees thinking
that their jobs depend on performance.
I .
What sort of place is that to call home?
And meredith needs this job.
This is her main source of money.
Well,that's very sweet,but we have to
follow the protocol.Those are the rules.
Okay,new idea-- we don't report
her at all.We just punish her.
We punish her?
Tell her,can't have sex for six months.
I don't think we could enforce that.
I don't know.I saw this
thing-- like a belt with a key.
A chastity belt.
Yeah,it's more of A...
underwear garment that has
little spikes,like,made of--
I think sometimes they're made of
metal.You know what I'm talking about.
You unlock a little
door that-- down...
where you-- where you
put-- where you put the--
he has not stopped working for a second.
At 12:45,he sneezed while
keeping his eyes open,
which I always thought was impossible.
at 1:32,he peed,and I know that because he
did it in an open soda bottle under the desk
while filling out expense reports.
And on the flip side,I've been so busy
watching him that I haven't even started work.
It's exhausting being this vigilant.
I'll probably have to
go home early today.
I am just saying that I don't think
that you understand what I am saying.
No,you are saying that we
should sweep it under the carpet,
accept the discount on supplies,not fire meredith,and
pretend like the whole thing never happened.
Yes.
What am I saying?
Well...
blugh,busted.I
don't--
I'm saying that her behavior
is unethical and a little icky,
and I don't think I want to work in an environment
where that sort of conduct is tolerated.
Well,you have to tolerate a lot
when you're part of a family.
It's not a family.It's a workplace.
I will be honest with you,that
car ride did not go well.
And that was not my fault.
The only reason I am standing out here right now is
because I don't want to take the elevator with her.
And I am holding on to her leftovers.
19 minutes and 48 seconds.
What were we doing for 19
minutes and 48 seconds,dwight?
None of your business.
So I guess I can assume that was..
personal.
Fine.
So maybe you're not
completely ethical after all.
Yes... maybe I'm not.
It's been a little tense.
People are suspicious of me,and my best
friend in the office won't even talk to me.
It turns out being the morality
police does not make you popular.
I should know,because in middle
school,I was the hall monitor,
and the kids used to stuff
egg salad in my locker.
Yeah,I was just hoping
middle school was over.
Kendall from corporate H.R.Is on line
one,and holly's on her way in,too.
What's the only thing
worse than one H.R.Rep?
- Two H.R.Reps.
- You get me.
- Can I sit?
- I don't know.Can you?
Kendall,my main man.
listen,holly,michael,I just got the
report that your branch submitted,
and there's a lot of stuff about
a relationship meredith is having--
yes,that came out during
the ethics seminar.
And let the record show that it was
during the immunity part of the seminar.
Well,I'm not sure these
circumstances warrant any action.
Oh,I think it's pretty
clear it was unethical.
Oh,from what I can gather,it
seems like a gray area.
Look,to be honest,the company's getting a
discount at a tough time in our balance sheet,
and I don't know that the right thing to do
for the company is to turn our noses up at that.
Um,kendall,I understand that the
discount is good for the company,
but I'm just not happy about
the way we're getting it.
I thought it was clear with you,holly.
Your tk was to get signatures from the employees
showing that they completed the training.
- No,I understand.
- good,'cause every other branch has managed to get those to us.
So,if it's not something you can
handle,hat's a different discussion.
- No,I ca...cado
- good.
how do you tell somebody that you
care about deeply,"I told you so"?
Gently?With a rose?
In a funny way,like it's a hilarious jo
or do you just let it go
because saying it would
just make things worse?
Probably the funny way.
Can I have everyone's attention?
Excuse me!May I have
everyone's attention,please?
We need to finish the ethics seminar.
- No way,lady.
- it's a trap.
Everyone,please,I just need your signatures
to show corporate that I gave you the training.
- Don't sign anything.
- Okay,everybody listen up.
If you are not in that conference room
in two minutes,I am going to kill you.
It's a quarter to 5:00,and I
have started to gather my things.
Get in there right
now,or I'm gonna lose it!
Am I getting fired?
Now is really not the time,meredith.
In this next section,we examine the
difference between sick days and personal days.
Sick days are only to be used when an
illness precludes you from doing your job
or can spread to your coworkers.
Personal days,on the other
hand,are much more flexible.
Thank you,meredith.Th waselicio
hey,where's the steak sauce?
I the out.
I got some in my mivan somewhere.
Wait a second.
How does the steak factor in again?
I think she got it as a tip,but I don't
know why she didn't just take cash.
I don't care what she's doing.I
hope she just keeps doing it.
Amen,just keep the ribs coming.
-=www.ydy.com/bbs=-
Proudly Presents YTET - °îµÂÖí
www.tvsubtitles.net