-=http://sfile.ydy.com=-
Proudly presents
Sync:ﬂ«»‚»‚
The
Office Season05 Episode01
WEEK 1 JUNE 30
All right,everybody.
This is your last meal. So eat up.
From this point forward, you
will not use the bathroom.
We need to keep r our starting
weights high so we can lose more.
This summer, corporate is sponsoring a ttle
weight loss contest between the branches.
Whichever branch loses the most
weight gets three extra vacati days.
What should we do with
all these leftovers?
I'm taking the dumplings for my wife.
No,no,no! This is your last
meal. There will be no leftors.
I can bring these to my shelter.
I'm taking my dumplings.
There. Take those home to your wife.
Dwight,dwight!
Michael,it's time!
Hit the scales,everybody.
Just get right on that black platform.
This w. Step it up.
Don't go breaking my scale.
I'm excited to lose
weight for the wedding
Because i really want to have washboard
abs the first time angela sees me naked.
Ex-squeeze me.
No,i will ex-squeeze you.
Okay,everybody, get used to this,
Because we are going to be standing here
briefly every monday for the next seven mondays.
Wait a minute. One more
bite of eclair each.
Hold it in your mouth
if you can't swallow.
Really?Nothin
2,336 pounds.
Y'all need to learn
some portion control.
Wait a minute.
Pam is on the scale.
Ohpam-cake, no,no,no.
We would love your extra poundage, but you are
going to be leaving us next week, so vamoose.
- okay.
- vamoose,pam.
Dunder mifflin family only.
Family only.
All right,got it.
2,210 pounds.
Pam,you weigh 226 pounds?
Almost,kevin.
Not almost though,holly.
I mean,not--
not close to 200.
- math is hard.
- yeah.
Just-- we'll
just keep going.
WEEK1--2210LBS
WEEK 2 JULY 7
I'm totally gonna slaughter
at the weigh-in today.
All i had this weekend to eat was a
chicken breast and a case of diet coke.
- really?
- yeah.
'Cause i haven't eaten
anything since noon on friday.
Okay.
Stanley,come on.
Oh,i forgot something in my
car. I'll see you guys up there.
All right.
I happen to be losing weight
on my own for my own reasons.
The truth is i have lost
a little of my speed.
A little of my fire.
Here's what i used to look like.
Look at those biceps.
We were fighting the power
and eating whatever we wanted.
And arch yr back.
And slowly bring up your head.
Jimbo.
Ah,they moved the shower.
Did you see holly's butt?
Nope,i didn't.
- you know why?
- why?
Because most of the time friends
don't talk about other friends' butts.
I know.
But what have you learned about her?
I learned that she broke her
left leg twice in one year.
I learned that she's
allergic to sesame seeds.
I learned that she has read
lonesome dovethree times.
Nice.
And that her butt refuses quit!
Well,i tried.
You have to-- you
have to agree with me.
- that's insane.i thought you had to pee.
- i'll just go later.
Hey,if you're into yoga, i take a
great bikram class in dickson city.
Oh,thanks,i should check that out.
Also,and no pressure,
the teacher, he's a catch.
Actually,i'm a lesbian.
I'm gay.
I'm not a lesbian.
I don't know why i
said that. Stupid joke.
What's the joke?
There is no joke.
I just said it because i haven't had much luck
lately, and i'm not really looking to date.
So... Maybe i should switch to women.
Oh,you think it's a choice?
Um,i'm gonna head back
to my work area and just--
I'm messing with you,holly.
- i knew that. Okay,bye.
- okay.
- so you have the directions?
- yeah.
- you have a toothbrush?
- yes.
You have a cell phone charger?
I have everything.
Tomorrow i start a three-month design
program at the pratt institute in new york.
I will be a little
fish in the big apple.
What up,212?
Fax this for me.
Come on,man. She goes to
new york in,like,ten minutes.
It's not gonna take her
ten minutes to fax it,jim.
If i don't see you again, good-bye.
Well,actually i'll see you when you give
me the fax confirmation,so never mind.
Ang... Ela.
Ela ela ela under my angerela
ela ela ela eh eh eh--
What?
Hey,check it out.
This is the breakers.
Newport,rhode island.
Huge awesome gorgeous mansion
overlooking the atlantic.
And my dad went to cornell
with the current groundskeeper.
Every little boy fantasizes
about his fairytale wedding.
No,no.
This is where my parents
decided not to get divorced.
******
********i'm on it.
I'll see you later,love.
Oh,we done good in there,half-pint.
Well,that was the last
time,dwight. I mean it.
- monkey--
- no,no.
I have a fiance i very much like.
Pam! Pam!
What happened?
I wrote you a good-bye poem.
It's really long. I left it...
Up in my office. Could you just
please wait till i go get it?
- i should really get going.
- no!
Okay,okay.
Um,the last word is "seagulls."
- i'm sure it was really lovely.
- i took a lot from other poems.
Okay,call me when you get in.
- okay,bye.
- bye.
- all right,call--
- no,michael.
Why haven't i proposed yet?
Uh,actually,pam and i talked about
it, and we just decided that,um,
Well,we didn't want to spend the first
three months of our engagement apart.
And pam's always said she
doesn't want a long engagement.
Something in her past, i guess.
Not really sure of the whole story, but
something about a guy who used to work here.
Okay,no,no,no. No,no,no!
Same places as last week.
- it doesn't matter,michael.
- yes,it does.
No,this is about weight displacement.
We he same weight distribution.
Right here. There we go.
Let's move that up. There we go.
Oh,fancy meeting you here.
All right.
Okay,everybody smile.
You lost 31 pounds.
Yeah!
- all right!
- yes!
I can't believe i'm saying this, but
michael is actually killing it with holly.
And i think i know why.
It's because holly is
kind of a major dork.
I'm mc mike scott, and i am hot she's
dj jazzy flax, and she is the best
All those sucker
branches can suck our fat
Wikka wikka wikka wah tide
WEEK 3 JULY 14
Dunder mifflin. This is ronnie.
I don't really know ronnie.
But i have a feeling i will get to know
her very well over the next few years.
And eventually declare my love for her.
Sorry i'm late.
I accidentally switched my alarm
clock setting to zapf chancery.
Which is my terrible
segue into our course,
Expressive typography in new media.
I'm in the wrong class.
Some of you may remember
from last semester.
I am professor monaghan and...
Looks like i'm boring someone already.
- no,i just-- -
please sit down.
You're shaking. Are you all right?
Just leave me alone!
I am on the third day
of my cleanse diet.
All i have to do is drink maple syrup, len thjue icofe,
Fi ce cayenne pepper,and water for all three meals.
Um,i just bought some
bikinis online,size two. So...
Gonna look amazing
Hi,can i helpou?
I need you to make me 100
copies of this on canary yellow.
Hey,jan.
How's the candle game?
Oh,great,yeah.
Serenity by jan is kicking
ass... And taking names.
You remember last week
when that girl went missing?
Guess whose candles
they used for the vigil?
Cool.
Fice thank god they found her too.
- oh,they found her?
- hey,jan.
Hello,baby! How are you? Good
to see you. Who's your daddy?
You don't know who your daddy is,do you?
No,you don't. Come on,let's go in.
When michael told us that jan was pregnant,
he lead us to believe that he was the father...
By telling us that he was the father.
Hey,oscar.
Who's that woman in michael's
office with the feet?
That's his ex.
Oh,she's very beautiful.
Yes,she is. And clinically insane.
So listen,um, i don't know if your
offer still stands or whatever,
- but uh, you can give your yoga teacher my number.
- okay.
Listen,dummy, it's not that hard.
All you have to do is take the numbers from the
sales report and type them into a master spreadsheet.
A g.d.monkey could do it.
I do not understand why you can't do it.
No! You do not talk to him like that!
But he's an idiot!
He is not an idiot.
Thank you,holly.
He is mentally challenged.
But he's doing a super job here.
Wait,back up.
Do you think that i'm retarded?
Well...
No.uh,dwight--
Oh,holly, that is very offensive.
I'm sorry.
Hey,so...
Since my little lady has such
particular impossible to perceive taste,
I have made non-refundable deposits at
four totally different wedding locales.
Hot air balloons over napa valley.
World-famous walt
disney's epcot center.
Scuba diving wedding in the bahamas.
And the wilkes-barre
marriott, ballroom "c."
Dangerous,tacky,
sharks,haunted-- no.
Hurry,we have to make this fast.
Let's do this thing.
I have a nice comforter and veral cozy
pillows i usually read a chapter of a book,
And it's lights out by 8:30.
That's how i sleep at night.
All right,i am connecting. And...
You are not there.
Did you install it right? How
about this?Go to applications--
I can see you!
- all right!
- this is so cool!
So what is going on,
girl in the computer?
Lunch with a girl from my hall.
Ceramics class.
Then dinner by myself.
I'm gonna watch hgtv, and maybe
go to bungalow 8 with john mayer.
Okay,can you turn the girl off,please?
- i'm trying to get some work done.
- no way,no way!
Pam beesly! Hello!
Hey,everybody,look. Pam! Pam! Say hi!
Say hi to pam.
Don't we all look skinny?
Oh,almost dropped you.
Can you put me down? I'm
getting a little nauseous.
Pam,i would like you to meet ronnie.
We call her
rice-a-ronnie.
She is hilarious. She is wonderful.
A beam of light in
this dark,dark office.
Not really so much.
All she does is plop herself down
there and answer phones all day.
The nerve.
Oh,calm down,weirdo. It's just
a joke. She's such a weirdo!
You know what? My real
beef with her, though,pam?
Is that she can't find those little
colored paperclips that i like so much.
Would you help her findhem,please?
- they're on the supply shelf.
- let's go.
We are following pam
to the supply shelf.
Let us go.
New york is so exciting.
I love my classes. The city's awesome.
Can you give me back to jim now,please?
Okay,everybody, let's suck in our guts.
2,184 pounds
for a grand-- oh!
You all gained five pounds back.
Damn it! Come on!
Oh,my god!
WEEK 4 JULY 21
Come on,bernard.
Here we go. Everybody on.
All right,we're set.
Still good. You guys lost a pound.
You lost one pound.
I wa at the hospital.
I lost four pounds.
I don't know what those other fools
were doing, but i lost four pounds.
Angela,you'll go to the supermarket
and get the new york cheesecake.
Make sure it's the generic one.
It's stanley's favorite.
Yes,i've replaced angela as head
of the party planning committee.
I guess i was just in the
right place at the right time.
How's it going?
- it's going well.
- good.
I have a crazy idea.
What if we did,um,
fruit instead of cake?
Cake? Who suggested cake?
Phyllis.
We lost weight today.
I think it's okay to reward
ourselves once in a while.
Are you kidding me?
We only lost one pound, phyllis.
What is wrong with these people?
They have no will power. I went...
I once went 28 years without having sex.
And then again for seven years.
Does anyone have any idea what the number
one cause of death is in this country?
- shotgun weddings.
- that's not what that is.
Fright. Being scared to death.
No.
Obesity-caused illnesses.
- obesity-caused
illnesses. - thank you.
Holly is right.
People,this is not just about
winning some extra vacation days.
This is about a very cool h.r.initiative
That if we don't follow, we
are all going to die of obesity.
So how much are we gonna lose?
I would like to lose 65 pounds.
Yes! All right. Who else?
Angela,can i put you
down for ten pounds?
No,my doctor wants me to gain weight.
If you gain weight, you will die.
I want you to live forer. I
want us all to live forever.
How? How are we gonna do this?
Cryogenics. Spare me five.
This is how we're gonna do it.
Five pounds. I'm asking each
of you to lose five pounds.
That plus jim's 65 will give us a
very good chance at winning this thing.
All right,i'm taking off.
- booty call.
- nope,just going to see pam.
- here.
- maybe put up some shelves.
Wait a second. I don't want you to end
up with a surprise pregnancy like me.
Okay,thank you for this.
- you want more?
- no.
I don'knceow if there's any one
place that has all these things.
It's not my problem.
"a thousand-year-old church "in
the continental united states.
"there has to be a rainbow.
24-hour veterinarian on call"
That is very important to me.
So i have work to do. Just do it.
Sweetheart.
Just so you know,i don't
care where we get married.
I'll marry you right
here in this building.
I'll marry you in the parking lot.
I'll marry you in the
eye of a hurricane,
In the middle of a snowstorm,
on top of a monsoon.
All i care about is that we're gonna
spend the rest of our lives together.
I know i haven't made this easy on you.
'Cause-- oh,that's
so rude of me.
Have you seen,um, pam's new art?
It's right there. Check it out.
It's a pretty lame party.
Does anyone want to dance?
Collins has pitched a
near-perfect game so far.
And popped up...
Some girl came into pam's room crying
about her roommate stealing her soy milk.
So i'm in here waiting it out.
Stanley, michael's not here.
You can eat a slice
of your birthday cake.
I don't like cake anymore.
Why not,dawg?
Taste changed.
Now all i like is baklava.
Michael,we have a situation.
They should not be in that room.
- that's so lame they didn't invite us.
- you know what we should do?
- we should have a party and not invite them.
- yeah!
Let's go mini-golfing. Yeah?
Oh,hey,could i have a rain
check on the mini golf?
I,u aually have a date tonight.
It'll probably be a
total disaster,but...
Um,i think you'll have fun because
men from scranton are handsome,
And they know how to
show a woman a good time.
Nothat guy who murdered his
mother. He was not so handsome.
Also kevin.
You know what? We're
pretty much done here today.
Why don't you just take off early?
- really?
- yeah.
Oh,that's sweet.
- wish me luck.
- good luck.
Oh,holly doesn't need luck.
Everyone that meets
her instantly loves her.
Party's over!
You are so busted!
Okay,everybody.
Phyllis,did i or did i not say fruit?
- you said fruit,michael.
- and what is that?
Cake.
You know, we're gonna have to try a little
bit harder if we are going to win th thing.
Happy birthday, stanley.
WEEK 5 JULY 28
It's kind of a good
news, bad news situation.
The bad news is we're
not doing very well,
So we really had to starve
ourselves this whole week.
But the good news is that all the other
branches are doing just as bad as we are.
So corporate upped
the prize to five days.
So if we stay fat long enough, we
may actually get a whole month off.
What?
Oh,nothing.
It's just some of us are
taking this really seriously.
I swallowed a tapeworm last night.
It's going to grow up to
three feet inside of me,
And then it eats all my
food so that i don't get fat.
And then after three months, i take
some medicine and then i pass it.
Creed sold it to me. It's from mexico.
That wasn't a tapeworm.
How's my favorite branch doing?
All right.
Ronnie was blecch.
Things were at an all-time sad here.
But then i got an email from ryan
that he was coming back to town.
And i called the temp
agency, and i told them,
"i will pay you any
amount."just give me ryan howard.
Give him to me. I want him. I need him."
And you got a goatee.
I did.
Did you get that after you
helped me move and you saw mine?
Yes. Gooo-atee!
Fire-ed guy!
Hey,kevin.
- that's really funny.
- yeah.
- it's great to see you,kev.
- you too.
I'm keeping a list of everyone who wrongs
me, so when i'm back on top, they'll be sorry.
Kevin just made the list.
Jim.
I wanted to apologize for
how i treated you last year.
I lost sight of myself.
And now that i've quit the rat race,
I realized there's so much more to life than
being the youngest vp in the company's history.
I've even started,um, volunteering.
Giving back to the community.
That's great.
You're talking about your
court-ordered community service?
I don't need a judge to tell
me to keep my community clean.
But he did,right?
- all right.
Well,you lost zero pounds. No change.
On the brighter side,
you gained zero pounds.
Hey,you know what? I can't
do this by myself,people.
Kelly and i are the only ones who have
either passed out or almost passed out.
Damn it,i need these five
days for my honeymoon!
Who is slacking?
Okay,let's just all try
and work harder,okay?
No,i want names!
This is the hardest thing i've
ever had to do in my entire life.
I haven't had a very hard life.
So how was your date?
8.5
I got a red wine stain
on my favorite shirt.
But he's cute,right?
Whofatfi'sce wng?.
Close the door.
- this is your fault.
- no.
Your stupid "friend zone."
I should've been lovers with her first
and then friends. That was terrible advice.
Terrible advice!
You know my seduction method.
I like to get in there
and get my hands dirty.
You sabotaged me. You sabotaged me,man.
Attention! Attention!
We only have a few weeks left, and most
of you are just as fat as the day we began.
How much weight have you lost,dwight?
I am hardly the problem,jim.
No,you're definitely the problem.
This is what i gonna do.
I'm gonna randomly select three names, and
these three people will get liposuction.
Stanley, phyllis,kevin.
And you will be responsible
for your own medical bills.
Kelly.
Oh,hello,ryan. You look well.
I wanted to say i'm sorry for treating
you bad the past couple of years.
I-- i was in my
mid-twenties,and...
I was going through a lot of stuff.
I think i never really processed 9/11.
Um,i want you to know i've changed.
Cool.
We should get a drink later,catch up.
Pick me up around 8:00?
Oh,that is so sweet, um,but
i'm dating darryl still,
And we're,like, crazy in love,so...
I--
cool.
Well,maybe i'll see you around.
- it's a small office.
- yeah.
Hey,phyllis, do you
have a minute? Listen...
I'm really sorry about
what i said before,okay?
I was way out of line.
Yes,you were.
But you know what? I
want to make it up to you.
There is a surefire sale, but
it's tfiwoce-man job. Interested?
Split the commission?
60/40,hmm?
I'll drive.
Dieting's only half of it.
Saunas.
And exercise.
Although i know everybody
lovesgoing to the gym.
Ah,the dreadmill.
Probably the weirdest thing about
pam being gone will be lunch,actually.
But,um,it will force me to become
acquaintances with people i consider...
Coworkers.
Oh,my god. Uh,okay. Everybody just
act normal. Don't say anything.
What?
My ex-girlfriend,
she's right behind you.
- really? Where?
- just hide me.
No,no,don't
look--
Wow,was it the age difference?
Uh,actually,kind of,yes.
I just didn't like eating
dinner that early,so...
Hey,jim.
Um,listen,can i call
you back in a little bit?
I made friends.
Are you insane?
God,what happened?
There was no client.
Dwight drove me to an abandoned warehouse
five miles away and pushed me out of the car.
I had to walk home with
no money and no phone.
And you burned over 1,000
calories walking home,
And this branch just got a little
bit closer to winning the contest.
Phyllis vance, ladies and gentlemen!
You left me in a bad part of town.
Yeah,i took your purse.
What are you worried about?
You look great.
I can definitelyee the difference.
Phyllis vance for david wallace.
WEEK 6 AUGUST 4
NO WEIGH-IN THIS WEEK
"that dunder mifflin
does not discriminate.
"nor does it condone
unhealthy dieting habits "
Or extreme weight-loss strategies as
was clearly stated in the official-- "
Oh,bang boom! Shake! Clargh!
Why,hello,everybody!
- what are you doing?
- fair question.
I say,i say,i say sit down,holly!
I'll take it from here.
I am beautiful.
They are beautiful.
He is beautiful.
This big fat pig is beautiful.
It's my sumo suit.
I just didn't inflate it all the way.
I'm so glad that i
bought instead of rented.
Body image.
We are here because there is
something wrong with society.
See,you're always saying there's
something wrong with society,
But maybe there's
something wrong with you.
If it's me,then society
made me that way.
Now i know a lot of you are probably asking
yourself, "why are you dressed in a plus-size suit?"
Because you're kind
of doing michael klump.
How do you know michael klump?
Because it's your "making
fun of fat people" character.
How dare you!
Michael klump is a
celebration of fat people.
I think of him as more like a monster.
What about,"i say,i
say, i say,i sit on you"?
No,no,no. It
goes-- look.
I say,i say,i say i sit on you!
No,no,no,no! You know what?
Fat people are not monsters.
Why don't you guys have a little
more sensitivity to the subject?
Bang,boom! Case in point.
Look at the outside of
this building. It is ugly.
But you come inside,
and it is beautiful.
Just like this unappealing fat suit.
Inside is a rather handsome,sexy man.
Vamping.
Hey,why don't you just sit down,please?
Eh,i've been sitting all day.
We're doing this because of you, so why
don't you just go stand somewhere else.
Shaved.
- i did.
- why?
So in the ar 2000, fungus and even black
mold was discovered growing in the cave.
Some blame it on the new air
conditioning system that was installed.
Some on the high-powered lights.
Others feel that
fungus is due to--
- nice.
- quiet,please.
- sorry.
Dwight,i would like you to apologize
to this beautiful, beautiful woman
For forcing her to walk five miles,
which for her, is basically a death march.
She should thank me.
Okay,phyllis, thank dwight first.
Why should i have to thank him?
You're right,you're right. Just--
dwight,do it. Just say it,okay?
I apologize for creating a ruse
which forced you to exercise.
Finally! Right?
Okay,phyllis, you must be exhausted
from standin on those gams.
Why don't you have a seat?
Let's all clap at phyllis.
Okay.
Well,michael klump wants to
remind you that corporate--
Their idea,yes,was to
urge you to lose weight.
But more importantly, what
this whole thing is about,
This contest is really about being health and
in order to be healthy, you have to eat,kelly.
Kelly-- that's--
back,back!
Kelly,i want you to
stand up on your chair.
Come on,stand up on your chair.
Stand up, stand up,stand up.
Somebody help her. Here we go.
Okay,i want you to look at her.
She's a beautiful indian woman.
Why? What makes her beautiful?
Everything. She's perfect.
- i like her nails.
- okay, be more specific.
I like her finger nails.
I like her purple dress.
- what about her looks?
- hell of an ass.
What else do people like?
I wonder wt people like about me.
Probably my jugs.
Kelly,will you just agree to stop this
madness and stop trying to kill yourself?
I hateieting. I hate it so much.
I hate this worm inside of me!
I want you to know--
kelly,look at me.
I want you to know
that you are beautiful.
You are truly, truly beautiful.
Give me a hug.
Summer's going great.
Just spent two hours
listening to michael klump.
I have a weird pain in my left
side that i'm convinced is an ulcer.
My girlfriend lives in new york,
and i haven't seen her in ten days.
How's your summer?
WEEK 7 AUGUST 11
- hey,ryan,look.
- yeah?
Shaved off my goatee. I am goatee-less.
We are the goat-less brothers.
Yeah,yep!
All right,excuse me.
How was friday night?
Oh,i had a good time, but it's
been three days and no call.
I even have two tickets to see
counting crows for tonight,so.
He'll call.
Oscar,enough with the girl talk,please.
You guys lost four pounds.
- i say we have a parade.
- excellent.
Good job.
So it turns out tonight is
my nephew's tee ball game,
And i kind of missed
the first three,so...
You've already disappointed him so much.
He can't be expecting a lot from you.
I know. I suck.
Yes,you do.
- dwight says hi.
- i do not.
I do not say hi,pam!
Now he's saying hi even louder.
All right,listen, we're still
good for this weekend,right?
No tee ball games,
recitals, karate tournaments?
- hey,can you got to i.m.?
- okay.
Okay.
Let's meet for lunch.
What are you writing about me?
What --
today?
Yeah,c'mon,we'll meet halfway.You'll
be back for your 4 o'clock class.
I'm gonna write you
both up for not working.
I'm gonna write you up for noworking.
Okay. Well played.
Neither of us will write
the other up for not working.
Where?
The rest stop where that soda exploded
on me.Exit 17,I think.1 o'clock.
Alright.See you then.:)P.S.I
finally finished my summer project.
Yeah?
Did he call?
I just got
off-- kendall?
No,no,did-- i heard you
talking to oscar about that guy.
What happened? Did he call?
Oh,no.
- really?
- no. And you know what?
I even got two tickets to see the
counting crows tonight as a surprise.
Why do guys not call when
they say they're gonna call?
I don't know.
I always call everybody back right away.
But he'll call back, though.
Give him to the end of the day.
- he'll call,he'll call.
- okay.
If he doesn't,he is loco.
Thanks,that's sweet anyways,um,
Seems like we lost to
utica by only eight pounds.
Well,at least everyone lost weight.
That's all that really matters.
Wait,could we have
till the end of the day?
So we're only eight pounds
behi now i know it's a stretch,
But we could weigh ourselves again at the end
of the day and maybe win this thing after all.
Leave it to me,boss.
I can get this whole
office to make weight.
It's gonna be a little toasty in here.
A good old-fashioned sweat lodge.
Andy bernard does not lose
contests. He wins them.
Or he quits them because they're unfair.
Hey,is that healthy food?
Nope.
We're trying to win a
contest here,kelly. Please?
Hey,michael,i just scheduled lunch with a
client, so i might be back a little late.
Okay,that is fine.
Just water,and be back by weigh-in.
- okay?
- perfect.
I hate to even ask because you've been so
accommodating about all the wedding stuff--
Your wish is my command.
Is there any way our first
dance can be to my favorite song?
The little drummer boy.
Of course!
- really?
- yeah.
I mean,it's a great song.
I always thought it was bigger
than christmas anyway, you know?
And you know what? The guys already
know it, so it's easy breezy.
The guys?
I didn't tell you?
Here comes treble, class of '96
was available for our big day, so...
I booked 'em.
I don't
think that--
And they're collectively my best man.
And they're crashing with
us for three weeks, so...
Totally works out.
I don't know if i want your old college
a capella group to be our wedding band.
Okay,i hear you, sweetheart.
But this is a deal breaker.
But you know what? You're
gonna love these guys.
Carl one,carl two, broccoli
rob, sparerib, doobie,lunchbox.
Boner champ. That's me.
Pubie lewis and the news.
Hopscotch, jingle jangle.
Sandwich.
These are the best best man
a guy could ever hope for.
Let's talk about this later. Okay.
This is not halfway.
I did the math. I had to
drive way longer than you.
Montclair would've been closer,
so you have to buy lunch.
What are you doing?
- i just-- i can't
wait. - oh,my god.
Pam,will you marry me?
Oh,my god!
So?
Yes!
God,ugh! Where is jim?
I'm calling it.
Guess that's curtains for the yoga guy.
- oh,really?
- yeah.
I hate to say, i think the
problem with that whole thing...
- yeah?
- was that he was a complete stupid idiot.
Oh,man, i really wanted to see them.
- i know. I love counting crows.
- look at where my seats were.
- wow,really?
- yeah.
That's a shame.
A shame to waste these.
I want to buy them from you.
- michael, you don't have to buy them.
- no,i do.
Trust me. I really do.
Okay.
- okay?
- yeah.
All right.
All right!
Just-- i want you to just
forget about 'em,okay?
Case closed.
Um,can i pay you tomorrow?
I have like a $60 limit on my atm,so...
- yeah.
- is that good?
- what's up,everybody?
- hey,what are you smiling about there,smiley pants?
- you're late.
- wet tuna!
Hey,dwight.
- what's up,meredith?
- nothing.
You're dripping on me.
Darryl,would you do the honors?
- sorry,guys.
- no,no,no,no. I don't want to hear moaning.
This is a good day.
You guys accomplished something big.
You lost a ton of weight literally.
A lot of weight.
And i don't care what
any stupid scale says.
You guys are all gigantic losers.
I don't know about anyone else,
but it was a good summer for me.
I lost seven pounds.
And you know what?
I'm just gonna take
five days off anyway.
WEEK 8 AUGUST 18
I went zip-ling my third
day in costa rica. I...
Guess the harness wasn't
strapped in exactly right.
I broke my neck. And...
I've been in the hospital fiveeeks now.
Still haven't seen the beach.
www.tvsubtitles.net