- Michael?
- Yeah.
Contractions are coming
every 10 minutes.
Just remember to keep breathing.
- My cervix is ripening.
- OK, good.
Jan is about to have a baby
with a sperm donor.
And Michael is preparing
for the birth of a watermelon...
with Dwight.
Now, this baby will be
related to Michael through...
delusion.
- Michael! My water's breaking!
- OK! OK!
What do you do?
I get a call from Jan
and meet her at the hospital.
Right. Highways or surface roads?
I take Quincy Ave to Gibson.
Gibson is covered in potholes.
Car breaks down. Adapt!
I checked the route, no potholes...
It's about adapting
to the circumstances.
- Andy, would you like to have my baby?
- Yes!
No. OK, I'm crowning!
I'm crowning!
All right. Sorry.
Here we go. Here we go!
- The pressure! The pressure!
- Do it! Scream!
Scream it out, scream it out!
Babies are one
of my many areas of expertise.
Growing up,
I performed my own circumcision.
- Just keep pushing... I'm right here.
- Hold me!
- Cradle my head!
- I'm right here!
- I'm screaming, I'm screaming!
- All right.
Just push and breathe.
Numb me up.
I want anesthesia!
- You can't have it. It's too late.
- I don't want natural!
- You have to just push it out!
- OK!
Keep simulating.
Do you have the Sharpie?
- Do you have the Sharpie?
- Yes, I do!
When the baby emerges,
mark it secretly in a kind of a mark
that only you could recognize
- and no baby snatcher can ever copy.
- OK.
- Ready?
- Yes.
It's coming! Here we go!
God!
What was on that?
Butter.
Newborns are slippery.
Nice touch. Good.
Let's try that again.
It is going to be
the happiest day of my life.
Subtitles: - Feygnasse Team -
Synch: So., Collioure
Episode 5x03
"Baby Shower" (1.00)
Hello ladies,
how's my shower going?
- Phyllis, did you get the live storks?
- No.
Damn it, Phyllis!
I'm sorry.
Damn it, Phyllis
It was hard enough
to convince Jan to come.
So are we set for refreshments?
Per your instructions, we have the
personalized M&M's with the baby names.
This is your boy bowl,
with the name "Chevy."
That was me.
And this is the girl bowl,
with M&M's with the name "Astird."
- That can't be right.
- Michael wrote down "Astird."
She said it is the name
of a Viking princess. So...
- Ass... turd.
- I know.
I know. It is beautiful.
No. Thank you.
Is this it? I mean, is this...
Two bowls of M&M's
and some balloons?
You know what,
I think you need to step it up.
I think you need to get the lead out.
Because if I'm not mistaken,
we gave you your wedding shower here.
We all came into this room and gave you,
a golden shower. Well you know what,
where's my golden shower?
It does not matter to me at all,
whether this baby is biologically mine.
I am going to love it.
It's like when the dog nurses
the tiger cub.
Have you seen that video?
It is...
It's so...
bizarre and unnatural,
but...
it happens.
I'm collecting for the baby shower.
- But Phyllis, it's not his baby.
- I know, Kevin.
Why do we have to pay money
to get a gift
for his ex-girlfriend's
unborn sperm bank baby?
Look at it as if you're paying
for the cake, not the baby. Sheet cake.
I do enjoy being the head
of the Party Planning Committee.
I'm no longer under Angela's heel,
and her little grape head
is under mine.
What are you doing?
Don't talk to them.
- Sorry.
- Make the party.
Don't... Make the party, please.
Pump it!
- So you know Stacy, right?
- The one from England.
There's no one from England.
Katie studied in Ireland.
This is Stacy, the one who does
the Maira Kalman-style collages.
- Right, that style.
- So, Stacy and Eric
get to Bogre's DeTech half an hour early
so they don't have to sit on the slab.
Anyway, Bogre's TA
Sarah Kaya comes in.
Wait, who's Sarah Kayacombsen?
No, Sarah Kaya comes in.
Don't interrupt, I have like 30 sec
to finish this and get to DigiPres.
So Sarah Kaya says to Eric,
"No way. You can't reserve seats."
And Stacy gets all up in her face
and Sarah picks up Stacy's new PM pad
and throws it at the light box.
- No... way!
- Yes!
- That's hilarious?
- No, it was horrible!
- Jim, she might get arrested.
- Who, Stacy?
No, Stacy is a boy!
Frustrating. Why can't you just be
in art class with me?
Wait, I gotta go, class starting.
OK, I'll ta...
I'll talk to you later.
That was a good story.
Who's Sarah Kayacombsen?
I got the Nard-puppy for ya.
What's going on here?
It's a baby game where you guess
whose picture is whose.
Check it out.
Who would have thought...
that this little baby
would be marrying that little baby?
That's Phyllis.
Well...
It is. So I hope you two
are very happy together.
Pervert.
- Why would that make me a pervert,
- Well, it does.
- That's me.
- That's not you.
- Yes it is.
- That's mean, come on,
that's...
Ahoy, matey.
Ahoy!
- So, how you doing?
- Good.
Listen.
Jan Levinson is coming in today,
and she is in the...
terminal stages of her pregnancy.
The child of which
I have a vested interest.
It's all kind of weird.
Anyway, she is...
incredibly...
fat and enormous right now...
extremely unattractive.
And you are, on the other hand,
one of the more attractive people
in the office. So...
while she's here I am going
to be acting kind of cold to you.
And I am doing this...
to...
pay respect to her bloated feelings.
- And I'm treating Ryan the same way.
- Of course.
I do not like pregnant women
in my workspace.
They're always complaining.
I have varicose veins, too.
I have swollen ankles,
I'm constantly hungry.
You think my nipples
don't get sore too?
You think I don't need to know
the fastest way to the hospital?
- What do we have here?
- This is my baby.
Really...
Jan had the baby
and Michael wasn't there to mark it.
So the baby could be anybody's.
Except Michael's.
So this is Astird.
Astrid.
Why didn't you call me?
You know,
labor just kind of started
- very suddenly and...
- I could have helped.
Birth instructor thought it wasn't
a good idea for you to be there.
That guy?
He had no sense of humor
and I proved him wrong in so many ways.
You have no idea
what I've been through.
- No, I don't!
- So, let's...
I'm sorry, I thought today
at the baby shower
would be a good time
for the two of you to meet.
Can I hold her?
Yes, yes you can.
You know, I think,
just leave her in the car seat.
I love babies.
I think they are beautiful
in all sorts of different ways.
I try to pick up and hold a baby
every day, if possible, because...
it nourishes me.
It feeds my soul.
Babies are drawn to me,
and I think it's because
they see me as one of them.
But...
cooler.
And with my life
put together a little bit.
If a baby were president,
there would be no taxes,
there would be no war.
There would be no...
government, and...
things could get terrible.
It actually, probably
it would be a better...
screenplay idea
than a serious suggestion.
Ladies and gentlemen,
it is my privilege and honor
to present for the first time
in her life
and in the office:
- As...
- trid.
...trid Levinson.
Hi! Astrid,
this is everybody, look.
This is your family.
You're gonna know them
for the rest of your life.
- Well...
- Well, he may not be here.
Say hello!
OK, here we go.
- Lion King!
- Michael, Michael!
That's... that's too high.
I'll take that.
Come on,
let's get our shower on.
Conference room,
choppity chip chop.
Are you OK?
You seem kind of...
I'm fine, weirdo.
Such an HR weirdo.
Try not to suck all the air
out of there when you walk in.
Ready to play some games?
Let's do it!
The baby's already been born.
So we had games planned
but the baby ruins all of them.
No, the baby doesn't
ruin anything Kevin, OK?
The baby multiplies the fun.
Let's just do
what you were going to do.
Who wants to guess
when the baby will be born?
All right,
how about some presents?
I want to see some presents.
I got this so I can write down
for thank-you notes.
- Thank you. That's very sweet.
- Whatta we got?
We all chipped in
and got you this stroller.
- Thank you.
- She already has a stroller.
This is way worse
than the stroller she came with.
She's got an Orbit,
that's a 1200$ stroller.
1200$ for a stroller?
OK, what else?
1200$ is what I spent
on my whole bomb shelter.
For that kind of money,
this stroller should be indestructible.
Being good isn't always easy
No matter how hard I try
When he started sweet-talking to me
He'd come and tell me
everything is all right
He'd kiss and tell me
everything is all right.
Can I get away again tonight
The only one...
- Hey you!
- Hey! You busy?
Doing laundry for the first time
in like a month.
OK, you gotta hear this.
So, Jan's shower is going on right now,
- she's singing Son of a Preacher Man
- Can't hear anything,
- everyone's just staring at her.
- there's like machines going.
The song is about
losing your virginity next to a church,
and guess what, she's been singing
for the last 20 minutes!
I can't hear anything!
OK, well you know what, I...
- just call me later.
- OK.
I'm not frustrated.
Even if I were in Scranton, Jim and I
would have days like this. We're just...
a little out of sync.
You know, that's all.
Great. I washed my lipstick.
How well I remember
The look that was in his eyes
Stealing kisses from me on the sly
Taking time to make time
Telling me that he's all mine
Learning from each other's knowing
Looking to see how much we've grown.
And the only...
Don't hit the fence.
My child!
Don't get stuck on the barbed wire!
Playtime is over!
So Jan, tell my intended
about the miracle of childbirth.
Actually, I had a tub birth.
And it was really quite amazing.
- You gave birth in a tub?
- It's a really nice transition
from womb to world,
you know, kind of like a big womb.
- So you're in the tub with everything?
- Yeah, the afterbirth floats.
Must be like the tide
at Omaha Beach.
It's actually
really hygienic, Creed.
- I'm done.
- Me too.
This is the birth story.
It was beautiful.
This is a once-in-a-lifetime experience.
And I should have been there. I should
have been there to witness this.
- I could have helped.
- I know you're sad about this.
And I wish that I, but...
Would it help
if you held Astrid for just...
a little bit?
I'm just going to lie down
for 2 minutes. I'm exhausted, so...
Remind me to talk to you
about Astrid's 529. Wake me in 20.
I usually love babies,
but when I held Astrid I just...
felt...
shortchanged.
- Could you take...
- Sure.
Just for a sec.
- Hey guys.
- What's up, Mike?
I need some advice
from one baby daddy to another.
You, a baby daddy?
I, a baby daddy.
When you first became a baby daddy,
did you have an immediate connection
with that baby?
Like, the first time
that you held it,
did you find that
with your baby baby?
Hell yeah.
You know why?
'Cause that was my baby.
- I just saw this baby daddy...
- You should stop
calling yourself "baby daddy".
Why, Darryl? Because
I'm quote white quote unquote?
Because you're not a daddy,
and it's not your baby.
Feel connected
to his baby over there?
It's... That's different.
- You feel connected to this?
- That's not a baby.
You want to hold me,
to see how you feel?
- Could I?
- No.
I was just catching up on my sleep.
I can imagine.
- Where's Astrid?
- I think she's on a sales call.
On a what?
More paper!
She's just on a coffee break.
That's funny.
She's with Angela.
That's good.
Now, I need you to...
I need it to look up here.
Get the baby to look up here, ready?
Look at my finger.
Look.
- Come on, up here!
- Look up here!
- Your hand's in it.
- What? Sorry.
What are you doing?
What's going on?
- Excuse me.
- We're taking a picture.
- She's nature's bounty.
- You don't flash around a newborn baby.
Don't you know that?
- Michael, I need your help.
- I was just going to...
I was going to talk to Holly,
about her hygiene.
She smells like
old tomatoes and dirt.
Come on.
I like to call this...
the bumper test.
- Sure you can't stay a little longer?
- No, you know what?
I really have to go.
All right, everybody,
we're leaving.
Jan and Astrid are leaving.
You know what, where is the stroller
that I came in with?
I took the liberty
of putting it in your trunk.
Thanks, Dwight.
You know what?
There is...
There is one more thing
that you can do for me.
Don't date Holly.
That's... I hate her.
God!
Why would you even ask me to...
I mean, not that it matters,
'cause I don't, but wha...
All right. Fine.
Thanks for the baby shower.
It was great.
- And I'll see you soon.
- All right.
You still gonna be mean to me?
You wanna go out?
Yes.
I didn't feel much
when I held Astrid,
but I got a good feeling from Holly.
Hey, it's Jim.
Leave a message.
Hey, this is Pam.
Hey, it's me.
It is...
5:03.
I figured I'd catch you
walking to your car, but...
- You must be out or something.
- I'll leave a message.
Is it me, or are we
just a little off today?
I guess this is just one
of those days.
It'll get better.
Hope you didn't have
any major laundry issues.
I finished my laundry.
Got all my socks.
Nothing like that time
that crazy guy pushed you.
Remember that time that I helped you
do your laundry and...
that crazy guy came in
and started yelling at you?
Remember we went shopping the next day
to buy me a washer and dryer?
Yet here you are,
back in a Laundromat.
Now, I'm just trying
to help you, Beesly. Be safe.
You're probably upset that
I'm even at a Laundromat right now.
But, don't worry, I'm being safe.
And I'm headed home.
I'm headed to my dorm.
Not home.
Wish you were home.
Anyway...
I miss you.
www.tvsubtitles.net