Are you
swallowing them whole?
You're eating them
so fast,
Are they even touching
your tongue?
Yes.
Brownies, is it?
Humph.
Pastry cubes
made of sugar and fat?
No, thank you.
I'll stick with my jerky.
So why'd you come in here?
To socialize.
And inform.
Ooh, brownies!
I'm taking two
So I can parcel them up
And eat them...
at my leisure later on.
Much healthier.
You taking two?
Yeah, um...but one
of them is for Toby.
Yeah. Why don't you
send that to him in Costa Rica?
Um...I'm just gonna
hand it to him right now.
Okay, weirdo.
Why's that?
Why's that weird?
She said she was gonna
give it to him right now.
She's probably going to
Because they sit next
to each other.
Yeah, they used to.
Toby works here again.
Oh, can you imagine?
Oh, no!
You don't know.
I don't know.
What?
You should probably
just meander back there,
Take a look,see if he's--
See if he's back.
Dare I?
You know what?
I'm going to.
For old time's sake.
Great practical joke,Jim.
Got me to go to the annex.
- Hi,Mi--
- No! God!
No,God,
please no!
No! No!
Nooo!
www.SUBTITULOS.es
-DIFUNDE LA PALABRA-
www.SERIES.es
* TU COMUNIDAD DE SERIES *
The Office s05e08
"Frame Toby"
Look at him.
With his stupid face.
Stupid...tan.
- He looks great.Well-Rested.
- No
He looks worse.
Michael, is everyone okay?
Ohh. Well,I'm afraid not.
Toby Flenderson of H.R.
has made a sudden reappearance.
I don'understand.
Is anyone hurt?
Not on the surface, no.
But I can tell...
People are disturbed,
David.
Michael, you texted me
911-- Call me.
- Yes.
- All in caps.
Do you know what 911 means?
I learned a while back
that if I don't text 911,
People will not
return my calls.
Um...but now people
always return my calls,
Because they think that
something horrible has happened.
Now, what I'm curious about
Is how you were able
to go an entire week
Without knowing a member
of your staff was there
I did not want
to go back to the annex
Because that is where
Holly worked, whom I loved.
Also it's icky
back there.
That's true.
People say it's icky.
Okay.
I have to go.
- David, wait.
- No.
Is there no way
we can get rid of him?
Not without cause,
Michael.
I have cause.
It is because I hate him.
You have to get along
with Toby.
- No.
- Yep.
I don't.
Good-Bye,Michael.
Don't do that.
Oh, come on!
Do you see this?
Disgusting.
So,Tunes, you still gonna
buy your old man's place?
Yeah. I am.
Wait.
How do you know that?
I didn't tell you that.
Uh...no,I was just
walking by your desk.
I saw some emails.
I got peepers
of an eagle.
That's really not cool.
So Jim, you're gonna live
in the same house
That you used to pee
the bed in?
Yeah. I guess technically,
Kev, you're right.
Today's a big day.
Today's the day that I show Pam
the house that I bought for us.
Without telling her.
But it's my parents' house,
the house I grew up in.
And, yeah,I bought it
kind of impulsively.
I mean, the price was good,
And I was helping out
my Mom.
It's got shag carpets.
I mean, you can't blame
my parents-- It was the '70s.
And why would you wanna buy
ugly wood from trees
When you can have paneling and
a painting of some creepy clowns
That is apparently crucial to the
structural integrity of the building?
She's gonna love it.
Right?
Would you guys
all do me a favor
And just not talk about this
until I tell Pam?
- That'd be great.
- Whoa!
You haven't told
the missus about the castle?
You're in for
a spanking, my friend.
Myself and my lady--
No secrets.
Jim, don't listen to Andy.
I think it's romantic.
Oh, thanks,Phyllis.
Where's your place?
Oh, it's on Linden Ave.,
by the Quarry.
Oh...
Cool beans, man.
I live by the Quarry.
We should hang out by the Quarry
and throw things down there.
Definitely, we should.
"To whoever made
the microwave mess"
"The microwave
is a shared kitchen appliance.
"By not cleaning it up,
"You are basically telling whoever follows
"That their time
is less valuable,
"As they will have to scrub
out your disgusting splatter.
Sincerely, disappointed."
That is just obnoxious.
- No kidding.
- Yeah.
Wait, what?
The mess or the note?
The note.
So holier than thou.
I liked it.
Don't you think the person who
left the mess is the obnoxious one?
No...
The note is way more
obnoxious than the mess.
"Sincerely, disappointed."
Get off your high horse,
richy.
Just because someone likes things clean
doesn't mean they're rich.
Nah.
They're rich.
You wanna see some
real high-Caliber acting?
Well,Mr. Kurt Russell,
you are about to be served.
Hey,Toby.
Great to have you
back, man.
Seriously.
Just, uh...
Just a real pleasure
to see you again.
Yeah, thanks,Michael.
You're welcome.
Missed you.
Missed you
as part of our family.
Well, that's--
That's-- Sweet.
I missed you guys too.
So Costa Ric
that was...
Did you have fun?
That must have been fun.
Well, um,
it was amazing.
Really was.
Thanks for asking.
- Um..beaches were pristine.
- Nice peaches?
- Pristine beaches?
- Yeah, uh...
The whole thing
was incredibly cathartic.
Why'd you come back?
Why didn't you stay?
Well, it's actually kind of
hard to meet people out there.
I bet.
For you.
And, uh. Yeah.
Plus, it was hot.
- Hot.
- Why didn't you get an air conditioner?
Should have gotten
an air conditioner for yourself.
Are you all right,
Michael?
Yeah,I am.
I am.
I tried.
I tried to talk to Toby
and be his friend,
But that is like trying
to be friends with an evil...snail.
I feel like
I'm dyin' inside.
I feel like neve campbell
inscream II.
She thinks she can
go off to college and be happy,
And then...
the murder comes back
And starts killing off
all of her friends.
Learned a lotta lessons
from that movie.
This is just one of 'em.
Okay, just summarize.
Okay,Fire-Able offenses
include workplace violence
And sexual harassment.
That's it.
That's it, perfect.
We will get him
to hit on somebody,
And then we'll catch
him in the act.
I love catching people
in the act.
That's why I always
whip open doors.
Me too.
Okay, let's get
this started.
Okay.
What are you doing?
I am the bait.
For what?
Men find me desirable.
No, no, no.
Oh, it's a good day too.
I'm wearing my mustard shirt.
You're the bait
for Toby?
- Mm-Hmm.
- No.
For one thing,
he's not gay.
And if somebody were
to be bait,
It would be
Jim or Ryan,
Or me.
- Men find me desirable.
- Yes.
Sure they do,Dwight.
When it comes down to it,
it's a health issue.
I should've written that.
Mm-Hmm, yeah.
Why aren't you as mad
or interested in this as me?
Oh, totally.
Sorry, are we talking
about the microwave still?
Are you inching
away from me?
No.
Reach your arms out.
I'm always this close.
Camptown lady sing this song
doo-Dah doo-Dah
Hello,Pam.
Jim, may I have a moment
with Pam, please?
Yes.
I just have to take
this call anyway, so--
Oh, ooh,
his mistress!
No,I'm kidding.
Nobody would ever
cheat on you.
You are the complete package,
Pam.
What do you need,Michael?
Okay, what I would
like you to do
Is take this folded note,
And deliver it
to Toby Flenderson.
I want you to just react
to whatever this note elicits.
Do not read it
beforehand.
Can you do that for me?
- Sure.
- Good.
No, no, no,
no, don't--
"Please hug and kiss me,
no matter how hard I struggle.
I am too shy
to tell you that I love you."
Damn it,Pam.
You gave me your word.
Hey,guys,
that's really inappropriate.
What's up?
Um,I got some photos
from,uh,Costa Rica
If you want to see them.
- Yeah, yeah,I'll see 'em.
- Cool.
Toby, can I see those?
Wow.
What's the matter?
You-- You scared?
- Those are fightin' words.
- You mad?
You mad at me?
I hope he doesn't haul off
and just hit ya.
Do you wanna do that?
You wanna hit me?
You wanna punch me?
Hmm?
Huh???
- Punch him,Toby.
- I dare you to.
- Come on.
- Come on,Bam!
What's the matter?
Hit him.
Hit him, chicken.
Yeah, punch him.
Hey, hey, come on,Ryan.
- Whose side are you on?
- Come on, man.
No, do it.
Do it.
- I dare you.
- Punch him as hard as you
- I dare you.Not..
- possibly can, in the face.
Not as hard as you can.
Just a good, solid punch.
Come on, come on.
I'm not going to punch you,
Michael.
Are you really not
going to punch him?
No,why would I punch you?
Son of a bitch.
Shoulda hit him, man.
Guy was asking for it.
Once in a lifetime, man.
I thought you were gonna parcel
those out through the day.
Would you stop it?
You haven't done
anything helpful all day.
There's still one thing
we can do to get Toby fired.
What's that?
Frame him
for using drugs.
- Frame him?
- Yeah.
It's illegal,but everything they do
on the shield is illegal.
I've never framed a man before.
Have you?
I've framed animals before.
I framed a raccoon
for opening a Christmas present.
And I framed a bear
for eating out of the garbage.
Just seems awfully mean.
But sometimes, the ends
justify the mean.
Hello.
I've seen you guys around.
I'm Michael Scott,
Dunder Mifflin.
How you doing?
So I guess you know
why I'm here.
I need to purchase something.
Like a fridge?
No.
Uh--
I wanted--
I wanted to buy
some weed from someone.
- What?
- Grass, weed?
What makes you think
we'd have weed?
I heard you were drug--
I heard you dealt.
Hey, just
hold on one second.
I'm not wearing
a wire, so--
Why would you
even say that?
Hey, it's gonna be $500.
- How much
- $500.
It's a good price.
It's a steal.
How many pounds is that?
It's...
It's two pounds.
I'm losing money
on this, man, just--
Give me the money
- Okay.All right.Walk away
- Walk away.Walk away.
Hey,Pam?
I just wanted
to let you know,
I'm totally on your side with
a whole microwave situation.
Thank you.
I was just back there
to make some cup of soup,
The thing
is still a huge mess.
I know.
Can you believe it?
Yeah, it's crazy.
But I guess the thing is
at some point,
Notes or no notes,
Someone's gonna have to just
get in there and clean it up.
I guess that's why
we have a temp, huh?
Oh, no, trust me.
I would just make it worse.
How would wiping it with
a paper towel make it worse?
I-- I would find a way.
You've seen things
clean before though, right?
I-- Pam,I am hopeless
to that stuff.
I-- I, uh--
- Hi,Michael.
- Hey, hey,hey, hey.
I forgot--
Forgot--
Yes,I repeat:
A drug dealer is on
the premises of Dunder Mifflin.
His name
is Toby Flenderson,
And he recently turned from a
mysterious vacation in Central America.
I have risked a great deal
to tell you this information.
My name is Andy Bernard.
Andrew Bernard, that's my name.
See you soon.
Hi.
We received a call.
I don't know
anything about that.
We were tipped off about
a possible Narcotic situation.
- Here?
- Hey,Pam--
Hey,I got this, okay?
Hello, officers.
Dwight Schrute, former
volunteer sheriff's deputy.
Listen,I may have
inside information
That someone is hiding drugs
in this very office.
Just pretend like we're talking
until the cops leave.
Those are real cops.
Real guns.
Wonder what's going on.
Officers,I reveal
to you the perpetrator.
Hey, what is this?
Search his things.
Sir,could you step
away from your desk, please?
- Why?
- Sir,please step away from your desk.
Hey, what's going on?
You don't have
my permission to do this.
They don't need
your permission,Flenderson.
They've got
the company's permission.
Hey, hey, what are you--
Why are you doing this?
Uh, you know what?
I think this--
This is probably
a misunderstanding.
- Don't search my stuff.
- Sir
I have a reasonable right to privacy.
Save your whing
for the jury there,Flenderson.
- Yeah,let's just cancel this,okay?
- Michael
Sir, did you recently
return from a trip
- To Central America?
- Oh, my god. There was--
- I went to Costa Rica for a few months.
- Oh,no.That was legitimate.
- That was totally legitimate.
- Hey,Check this out.
Oh, god!
That is not mine.
I even...
Turn around please, would you?
- No, no, no, no,God.
- What is going on here?
No, that's--
I don't know what that is...And
- Do you have any weapons?
- I bet he has nothing to do with that.
- Of course not!
Ah.
That's mine.
- No,Michael,No!
- Yes, it's mine.
Some basil.
And salad dressing,
I think.
Salad dressing?
Yeah,it's,uh,
caprese salad.
There's a little bit
of, uh, mozzarella right there.
Are you kidding me?
That's my salad.
So wait a minute.
There's no drugs?
- No.
- Oh, damn it.Come on!
We got a fake tip.
Wait, officers, are you sure you
don't want to interrogate him?
- No.
- You have laws that protect you
In any kind of interrogation.
Why don't you use them?
You must feel pretty good
about yourself right now.
I didn't put caprese salad
in my drawer,Michael.
Did you?
Since when is it illegal
to put caprese salad anywhere?
You know,but the police
could have been out there,
You know,catching real criminals,
Instead of here,
- searching my stuff.
- Are you kidding me?
Are you kidding me?
That you're worried about?
You're worried
about the cops' time.
You think I framed you, and
you're worried about the taxpayer?
Ah, god!
Welcome back,
jerky jerk-Face.
You said you were leaving,
And you made liars
out of all of us.
- I did leave.
-So.. Yes, you did.
And then you came back.
Which makes you
the biggest liar of history.
I don't see
it that way.
You wanna hear a lie?
- What?
- I think you're great.
You're my best friend.
- I can't do this.
- Can't do what?
It's not fair to you.
And it's really
not fair to me.
Wait,What are you saying?
I broke up with Darryl
so I could be with you.
That was your choice.
Don't put that on me.
I'm just going
on a little trip.
Oh, can I come?
It's not that kind of trip.
I'm going to Thailand with some
friends from high school.
Well, a high school.
And if I don't do it now,
I'll never get to go.
And I'll always
resent you for it.
You don't want me
to resent you, do you?
So you're dumping me?
Let's be adults about this.
Let's have sex one more time,
And if you have any extra cash,
that would be amazing.
Okay.
Hey, do you mind if we make
a stop on the way home
- Sure.
- Cool.
What are we doing
at your parents' house?
I have a surprise
for you.
All right.
Ready?
Close your eyes.
And now...
Open your eyes.
Ta-Da!
I don't get it.
I bought it.
It's ours.
Let's go inside.
I'll show you inside.
So if you can believe it,
I did it without a realtor.
So saving
on closing costs is good.
And, uh, we can put all of
the money to de-Shag the carpet.
Which I think will help
The color situation.
Yeah,I am really sorry
about this.
I tried to move it,
But he is really
nailed in there.
Worried about art theft,
I guess.
A lot of art thieves
in this neighborhood.
This is the master bedroom.
But I'm actually
not allowed in here, so.
So I'm still in the process
of converting the garage.
It's got great light
in here.
And I was thinking
it could be perfect
For an art studio.
Look,I know.
I bought this
without asking you.
And it doesn't look great.
I know that.
And if you really hate it,
I totally understand.
- It's just--
- I love it.
You do?
Yeah,I love it.
Really?
???You bought me a house.
Oh, my God.
You bought me a house!
Yeah,I did.
Um,do we have to sleep
in your parents' bedroom?
No.
No,We'll just board that up.
It'll be that weird spare room
that people ask us about.
And the clown?
Yeah,I can't--
Really can't move him.
What is my perfect crime?
I break into Tiffany's
at midnight.
Do I go for the vault?
No,I go for the chandelier.
It's priceless.
As I'm taking it down,
a woman catches me.
She tells me to stop.
It's her father's business.
She's tiffany.
I say no.
We make love all night.
In the morning,
the cops come,
And I escape
in one of their uniforms.
I tell her
to meet me in Mexico,
But I go to Canada.
I don't trust her.
Besides, I like the cold.
30 years later,
I get a post card.
I have a son,
and he's the chief of police.
This is where the story
gets interesting.
I tell Tiffany to meet me
in Paris by the Trocadero.
She's been waiting for me
all these years.
She's never taken another lover.
I don't care.
I don't show up.
I go to Berlin.
That's where
I stashed the Chandelier.
www.tvsubtitles.net