I had no idea when i got into
that car to go to new york
That i was going to be quitting.
I got on the ramp,
And i was like, "two
hours, two hours to go."
Feelin' good.
Crank some tunes.
Should have peed before i left."
- Michael, get to the good part.
- Okay, so.
Get up to building.
Revolving door broken.
So i have to take
the normal door.
Oh, my god.
At least he's in the building.
No. No.
I was so nervous,
it was the wrong building.
I had walked into
the wrong building.
He finally has a story
we really want to hear.
And he knows it.
Okay, focus, focus.
You're in the right building.
You're with the right people.
- What happened?
- I looked at wallace and i said,
"I quit."
And as i turned to leave,
i looked back and i said,
"You have no idea
how high i can fly."
You didn't tell him how
sick of him you were?
Why would i do that?
Well, wouldn't it feel good to
tell him that he's incompetent.
That he's wasted 15
years of your life.
Maybe spit in his face.
You guys have thought about
this a lot more than i have.
I just winged it.
I love a good quitting story.
It makes me feel like i have
control over my own life.
Gives me hope.
Maybe i'll have one
of my own someday.
But i dream.
www.1000fr.com presents
Capture:FRM@¿É°®´óË®Å£
Sync:sxminu
The office s5 ep19
About a week ago, michael
gave his two weeks' notice.
And surprisingly,
There is a very big difference
between michael trying
And michael not trying.
Michael, is that scotch?
Scotch and splenda.
Tastes like splenda,
gets you drunk like scotch.
Clinky clinky clink.
Come on.
Come on, come on.
What am i gonna do?
I'll tell you
what i'm gonna do.
I'm gonna do a little bit
of this, a little bit of that.
I'm gonna stay up all day.
I'm gonna sleep up all night.
I'm gonna give it a--
And i'm gonna stop
worrying about calories.
Maybe you should
go into your office,
Close the door, and make
some calls about jobs.
- I have a job.
- For four more days.
Do you have any
leads on a job?
Pam, what you don't understand.
At my level, you don't just
look in the want ads for a job.
You are headhunted.
Have you called any headhunters?
Any good headhunter
knows that i am available.
Any really good headhunter
will storm your village
At sunset with overwhelming force
And cut off your head
with a ceremonial knife.
Right, 'cause that's
what we're talking about.
I need you to go over
these client lists
and indicate any
wrong or false data.
Your "i need you to"
is my command.
Okay.
- Hey, michael.
- Hey.
Can i talk to you for a minute?
You can talk to me for
as long as you want,
Because i have all
the time in the world.
Oh, god.
Ugh. Phyllis.
I just wanted to, uh,
tell you that--
- Oh! Ah, what's that?
- Oh, hey!
What is this about?
Um, you know,
'cause you're go--
You're leaving and everything.
It's a farewell.
Right.
So i hope i get to work
with you some day again.
Me, too. Me, too.
- Is this wine?
- Ah! Busted, yes.
- I already have wine.
- Oh.
- Hello.
- Hi.
Isaac silby here
for the interview.
Uh, yes. Please have a seat.
It'll be a few minutes.
Thank you.
You interviewing, too?
Mmm. Hmm?
Interviewing?
- For?
- Regional manager.
Yes, i am.
For regional manager, i've
decided to go with an outside hire.
For obvious reasons.
Where you from?
- Philly.
- That's a drive.
Yeah, well, this is one of the
few places that's hiring. It's--
It's brutal out there.
- Pam.
- Mm-Hmm?
When will the new
copier be ready?
I'm working on it, kev.
You said it would
be ready by today.
And it is today.
It'll be ready soon.
Soon could mean anything.
Soon could be three weeks.
Is that what "soon"
means to you?
Sometimes.
Then come back soon.
During the course of business,
A copier goes through something
called "normal wear and tear."
I think it's 75 cents.
That's a lot.
Bandit, no.
No, no, no.
Yesterday they
delivered the new one.
But they didn't set it up.
So my day just got a
little more interesting.
It's monster.Com.
Singular.
Thank you.
You work in paper long enough,
you get to know the players.
Hi, you've reached prince paper.
We are sad to inform you That after
40 years of serving the community,
We are no longer in business.
Thank you for your support
And may god bless you.
Bye!
What am i gonna do?
yeah.
You want me to come
into your office?
Oh, okay.
Okay.
All right.
Uh, close your eyes.
- I'd prefer not to.
- Just close your eyes.
I'm going to start my
own paper company.
You're starting your
- Yeah!
- Why?
Can you believe--
'Cause i know paper.
I know everything there
is to know about paper.
Do you know that the
industry is in decline?
yeah. Oh, god, i practically
invented decline.
- Right.
- Right?
I know paper.
I know how to manage.
I have a name.
Close your eyes.
No, i did that before.
It added nothing.
- Just close 'em.
- Okay.
All right.
"Michael scott paper company."
You want in?
Do you want to
be a part of this?
I am not gonna do this.
- Oh. Obvious--
- And you are not going to, either.
Oh, agreed.
- Mmm, except--
- Here's the thing.
What i wish for you is that
you land a job at a company
That"a," exists,
and "b," has a salary
Because they're set up
to do that kind of thing.
What's up, chuck?
- Jim.
- Hey.
- What are you doing?
- Nothing. Just talking.
Okay. Michael handed in
his two-Week notice.
- Did you also hand in your two-Week--
- I didn't.
No? Okay.
- After you.
- No, i'm staying.
- Okay.
You want me to translate the
german instructions for you?
No, i'm sure they're pretty much
the same as the english instructions.
Typical american arrogance
that got us involved In a war
we never should have been in.
- That's a really--
- World war ii.
Well, fine.
Do the german instructions say
what this is supposed to do?
???
Let me see here.
It is either an incense dispenser
Or a
Ceremonial
Sarcophagus.
My german is pre-Industrial
and mostly religious.
Listen,
this order form--
Instead of saying
"dunder mifflin" at the top,
Is there any way i could
get it to say something else?
Like "michael scott
paper company"?
You-- Oh.
Somebody's been talking
in bed. Pillow talk.
Yeah.
Listen, michael.
Have you really
thought this through?
'Cause it's a pretty big risk.
This is a dream
that i have had since lunch,
And i am not giving up on it now.
yeah.
You could give it
up though, right?
And almost no one would know.
Before you got here,
I'm the one who landed
all of these clients.
Half of 'em, at least.
I can do it again.
I know the market.
I know the price points.
I'm on it.
Don't worry.
So how do i do that?
Well, um, you can scan it.
And then you can
upload the image,
- And then you can copy a new image--
- Could i take a piece of paper
And just tape it with
transparent tape?
Yeah. Good.
- Oh, thank you very much.
- Mm-Hmm.
So that is why i have to
leave at 5:00 on tuesdays.
It's to pick up my
little sisters from school.
We're really tight.
We're like the kardashians.
You know, you can run
this stuff by toby.
- Yeah, i don't like talking--
- Come in.
I'm sorry.
I didn't realize you
were with anyone.
But i just wanted to
bring you the brochure
On that accounting seminar
that i was telling you about.
- Yep.
- Earlier.
I can wait we're in the
middle of something, angela,
- So why don't you just--
- Okay, um, actually, you kndow,
It was so much fun last year.
There was a sundae bar.
I mean, i didn't have any--
You know, to stay trim.
Did michael just let
anybody in his office?
- Yes.
- Yeah.
He was like, "come in."
I am aware of the effect
i have on women.
So you should be
heading back to your desk.
Okay. Bye, charles.
Well, you'll let me know.
Good-Bye.
She's such a special person.
She's turning 50 this year.
Sorry. I'm starting my
own paper company.
-  No way!
- Yeah.
In this climate?
In all climates.
It's going to be worldwide.
And i'm looking for some
talented salesmen to join me.
That's where you come in.
Well, it's a very
intriguing concept, isn't it?
Michael is starting his
own paper company.
What do you think about that?
Your own paper company.
Can you believe it?
Well, we'll see.
We'll see.
well.
It's just a-- It's a nugget
of an idea right now,
- so.
- what?
Potential. Lots of potential. Yes.
What a--Courageous--
- Venture.
- It's--
It's very courageous.
Very exciting.
Umm...Location is hard for me,
with the farm And
the responsibilities so--
With the farm.
You getting to wherever
i'm gonna put my thing.
- Okay, so yeah.
- So think about it.
- Let's put a pin in it for now.
- You know,
i would love to
put a pin in that.
Everyone, can I
have your attention?
This is the moment you've
all been waiting for.
Right?
Little miss thing wants attention.
Meredith--
G-44.
It's not ready, kevin.
I am at a crucial point
Where i have sunk four
hours into that copier.
And i am not gonna let it beat
me like that wireless router did.
- You put a note in my food?
- I made it sterile.
Just to say "sterile"
doesn't make it so.
I am offering you
The opportunity of a lifetime,
oscar, to come work for me.
Do you have a business plan?
A funding request?
- Market research? Financials?
- No.
- You need those things.
- No. No!
Most new businesses,
They don't make a profit
till at least two years.
And then your margins
will be razor-Thin.
Best-Case scenario,
You don't cut yourself a salary
for at least five years.
Can you go five years
without a salary, michael?
- Okay.
- Five years?
Hey. You already have the job.
You don't have to convince me.
It's just not prudent, michael.
Stanley.
Can't you see i'm urinating?
Listen, listen.
Stanley, you don't
need to answer me now.
No.
Just-- I want you
to think about it.
- I am starting my own company.
- No.
Okay, you're not
letting me finish,
And you just lost
out on $1 million.
No, i didn't.
You know what?
I had a great time at prom.
And no one said
"yes" to that, either.
How's it working?
Um, let's see.
It's fine.
I did it.
I learned everything
about this machine.
I know all the buttons,
even the inside ones.
I know all the error messages.
I could do a bound book
In plastic with offset colors.
Which feels...
Hey, hank. You ready?
- Yeah.
- Okay.
- Michael.
- Hmm?
I can't pretend
i haven't seen that.
So i'm gonna ask you
to stand up, walk out,
And you can't take anything.
Okay. I have immunity.
It's my two weeks--
Not if you're starting a competing
paper company, michael.
Hank.
Okay, michael.
Hank?
You really think hank is
going to be loyal to you?
Hank, please escort charles
from the building.
Come on, man,
let's-- Let's go.
I always thought
michael got a bad rap.
He's a good guy,
And he's super funny.
Yeah, maybe i should
tell him before he goes.
He's all the way over there.
Well, here we are.
- I would just like to
- No, no, no, no.
You're done, michael.
All right, then, everybody.
I'm out of here.
What is he doing?
It looks like he's
saying something.
I think he's singing.
I can't believe this
is really happening.
And i feel free.
And just like that,
As mysteriously as he arrived,
He was gone.
The whole office feels darker.
You know?
It's just a sad, dark day.
- Andy, he's gone.
- I know.
You don't have to
kiss his ass anymore.
Michael's like a
movie on a plane.
You know, it's not great,
but it's something to watch.
And then when it's
over, you're like,
"How much time is left
on this flight?
Now what?"
- Michael.
- Shh, shh, shh.
Don't look down.
Look straight up.
- Are those--
- All right, come on. Ow!
- Please.
- These are for employees only.
Angela, kevin,
help me out.
I just need a few things.
Then i'll be gone.
Michael, why is it that you asked
everyone Except me,
angela, creed, and meredith?
I was going to.
I wanted to, but i had
to start somewhere.
And you didn't want
to start with us?
No, of course not.
But now i want everybody.
Jim!
Did you have time to
think about my offer?
I did have a chance
to think about it,
But then i thought
about something else.
So which way are you leaning?
Well, it is tempting, but i am
100% leaning towards passing.
Thanks, jim.
Hey, did anyone see the client list
That michael was supposed
to be working on?
No.
Okay. Let me know if you find it.
Okay.
Listen.
Okay. Okay.
We don't have much time.
Just act normal.
Don't look at me,
people. Stop.
Don't look down.
He's gonna see me.
Not all the way up.
Keep 'em at a normal height, okay?
Hey, this is not michael
scott talking right now.
This is your future.
Hello.
I am your future.
You are older and
you are very happy now
Because you went with
michael scott, right?
So everybody,
come on down,
And let's just crawl
out of here together.
All right?
Come on.
Are you-- Are you
doing your best here?
Are you being the
best that you can be?
All right.
Everybody who's
gonna go with me,
I want you to stomp your foot.
Okay.
All right.
Come on.
You're coming with me.
Come on, phyllis.
Here we go.
- Michael, get up.
- Oh, god. Okay.
All right, all right.
Time to go.
Jim, let's go.
- Come on. Come on!
- Michael, what are you doing?
I think maybe hank should be here.
Hank? No, i don't
need hank, michael.
You're gonna mess with me?
Is that what you're gonna do?
I'll tell you something, charles.
I don't even care,
because i've got nothing to lose.
- Okay.
- Oh, my god. Oh, god!
No! No.
All right.
It's not worth it.
- Oh, no.
- What?
I'm going with him.
What?
- Pam.
- I'm going.
Pam, you can't be serious.
Michael, wait!
I'm coming with you.
You are?
Yeah.
Okay. It's gonna be great.
Great. Uh, except i--
I don't want to be
a receptionist anymore.
Right.
Executive assistant.
Salesman.
All right.
- Okay. Deal.
- Deal.
Okay.
- Well, jim?
- Still no.
- Okay.
- Yeah.
Well, let's go.
Oh, all my stuff is still upstairs.
Are people watching?
Probably.
Michael, it's not how
you leave an office.
- It's how you--
- Jim, jim. Jim.
We're having a
company meeting here.
I will bring all your stuff home.
- Okay.
- All right.
- Well, see ya later.
- Bye.
See ya later.
So we had a personnel change today.
Shouldn't affect
our day-To-Day,
But until we get
a new receptionist,
I want kevin on the phones.
Phones.
Also, there's been
too much wasting time.
- So stanley.
- Yes?
Yeah, i want you
on top of that, okay?
I want you to be my
productivity czar.
Okay? Good.
Um, okay, that's it on my list
So, uh, you know,
no excuses, guys.
Let's get going, okay?
welcome to www.1000fr.Com
www.tvsubtitles.net