HERE ARE OUR FINAL ACTUAL
COSTS FOR THIS YEAR.
OKAY.
AS YOU CAN SEE, WE DID PRETTY WELL.
YES, YES, I CAN SEE...
THAT WE DID INDEED.
WHY DON'T YOU EXPLAIN THIS
TO ME LIKE I AM AN 8-YEAR-OLD.
ALL RIGHT, WELL, THIS
IS THE OVERALL BUDGET
FOR THIS FISCAL YEAR ALONG THE X-AXIS.
YES. RIGHT THERE.
THERE'S THE "X-AXIX."
YOU CAN SEE CLEARLY ON THIS PAGE THAT
WE HAVE A SURPLUS OF $4,300.
??OKAY.
BUT WE HAVE TO SPEND THAT
BY THE END OF THE DAY
OR IT WILL BE DEDUCTED
FROM NEXT YEAR'S BUDGET.
WHY DON'T YOU EXPLAIN
THIS TO ME LIKE I'M FIVE.
YOUR MOMMY AND DADDY GIVE YOU $10
TO OPEN UP A LEMONADE STAND.
SO YOU GO OUT AND YOU BUY CUP AND
YOU BUY LEMONS AND YOU BUY SUGAR.
AND NOW YOU FIND OUT
THAT IT ONLY COST YOU $9.
- SO YOU HAVE AN EXTRA DOLLAR.
- YEAH.
SO YOU CAN GIVE THAT DOLLAR
BACK TO MOMMY AND DADDY,
BUT GUESS WHAT? NEXT SUMMER--
I'LL BE SIX.
AND YOU ASK THEM FOR MONEY,
THEY'RE GONNA GIVE YOU $9,
'CAUSE THAT'S WHAT THEY THINK
IT COSTS TO RUN THE STAND.
SO WHAT YOU WANT TO DO
IS SPEND THAT DOLLAR ON SOMETHING NOW,
SO THAT YOUR PARENTS THINK THAT IT
COSTS $10 TO RUN THE LEMONADE STAND.
SO THE DOLLAR'S A SURPLUS.
THIS IS A SURPLUS.
WE HAVE TO SPEND THAT $4,300
BY THE END OF THE DAY
OR IT'LL BE DEDUCTED
FROM NEXT YEAR'S BUDGET.
WE SHOULD SPEND THIS MONEY ON A
NEW COPIER WHICH WE DESPERATELY NEED.
OKAY, BREAK IT DOWN IN TERMS OF, UM...
OKAY, I--I THINK I'M GETTING IT.
www.1000fr.com presents
Capture:FRM@Summerwind
Sync:FRS@»®¿Õ¹â½£
The Office S05 EP10
GUESS WHAT, EVERYBODY?
CHRISTMAS HAS COME EARLY THIS YEAR.
OSCAR VERY SMARTLY HAS DISCOVERED
AN EXTRA $4,300 IN THE BUDGET.
THANK YOU, OSCAR.
AND I HAVE DECIDED WITH THAT
MONEY I AM GOING TO BUY A NEW--
DRUM ROLL, PLEASE.
CAN ANYBODY GUESS?
- NEW CHAIRS?
- NO.
A NEW COPIER.
UNLESS EVERYBODY CAN
AGREE ON SOMETHING BETTER?
NO, NO, PLEASE. PLEASE DO NOT DO THIS.
YES, MICHAEL, NEW CHAIRS.
THESE CHAIRS ARE TERRIBLE.
WE WERE SUPPOSED TO
GET NEW ONES LAST YEAR.
SO WE ALL AGREE TO GET
NEW CHAIRS THEN. GOOD?
YEAH, HE SAID GOOD. I'M GOOD.
NOW LISTEN, WE ARE A PAPER COMPANY.
HOW CAN WE TAKE PRIDE IN OUR JOBS
IF WE HAVE TO PUT OUR FINE
PAPER IN THIS WRETCHED MACHINE?
OSCAR, NO. THIS IS NOT THE TIME
FOR ONE OF YOUR PRINCIPLED STANDS.
PAM, YOU MAKE MORE COPIES THAN ANYONE.
EXACTLY. THAT SHOULD TELL YOU
HOW TERRIBLE THE CHAIRS ARE.
OKAY.
OKAY, GOOD SUGGESTIONS.
ALL GOOD SUGGESTIONS. UH,
LET'S JUST DECIDE AND AGREE UPON ONE.
I'M WITH PAM. CHAIRS.
ALL RIGHT, SO TEAMS FORMING.
WE SHOULD REALLY HAVE THE
OFFICE'S AIR QUALITY TESTED.
WE HAVE RADON COMING FROM BELOW.
WE HAVE ASBESTOS IN THE CEILINGS.
THESE ARE SILENT KILLERS.
YOU ARE THE SILENT KILLER.
GO BACK TO THE ANNEX.
YOU'LL SEE.
- MICHAEL.
- YES.
I'VE TALKED TO MEREDITH, STANLEY,
AND JIM ABOUT THE CHAIRS.
I KNOW THEY'RE WITH ME ON THIS.
ACTUALLY, I'M GONNA GO WITH COPIER.
WHAT? JIM.
EVER SINCE PAM AND I STARTED DATING,
I JUST FEEL A LITTLE WEIRD ASKING
HER TO MAKE COPIES FOR ME.
SO I MAKE MY OWN COPIES.
AND THAT COPIER SUCKS.
LET ME TELL YOU, I--
BUT YOU KNOW WHAT?
PAM AND I DON'T HAVE
TO AGREE ON EVERYTHING.
JIM, GOOD FOR YOU STANDING
UP TO PAM LIKE THAT.
THE BALLS ON YOU, MAN.
SO MICHAEL, WHAT DO YOU THINK?
WHY ME?
YOU HAVE TO MAKE THE DECISION.
WOW, OKAY. WELL,
I SWALLOWED ALL YOUR IDEAS.
I'M GOING TO DIGEST THEM AND
SEE WHAT COMES OUT THE OTHER END.
DWIGHT, I'M A LITTLE CONCERNED ABOUT
SOME OF THESE DIRECTIONS TO SCHRUTE FARMS.
YEAH, DO TELL.
I MEAN, LIKE, "156 PACES FROM
THE LIGHT RED MAILBOX, MAKE A LEFT."
"WALK UNTIL YOU HEAR THE BEE HIVE."
HOW COULD IT BE MORE CLEAR?
I THINK ANDY MAKES AN EXCELLENT POINT.
OKAY.
BUT MY BIGGEST CONCERN IS THAT
THERE'S ONLY ONE BATHROOM.
WE'LL DIG A TRENCH.
AS LONG AS IT'S DOWNHILL FROM
THE WELL, WE SHOULD BE FINE.
NANA MIMI CANNOT SQUAT OVER SOME TRENCH.
WE'RE GONNA PUT OUT STUMPS. COME ON.
LET'S THREE-WAY THIS LITTLE ISSUE
AND COME TO A SOLUTION BY THE
TIME WE GET TO SCHRUTE FARMS.
HOW'S THAT FOR A PLAN?
WE'RE GETTING MARRIED AT SCHRUTE FARMS,
NO MATTER WHAT.
I HAVE LOOKED AT 12 VENUES.
I HAVE LOST EIGHT DEPOSITS.
AND I HAVE SEEN ANGELA NAKED ZERO TIMES.
I AM NOT LOSING ANOTHER DEPOSIT.
HEY.
SO, UM, I'VE BEEN THINKING ABOUT
THIS WHOLE CHAIR/COPIER THING.
I REALLY THINK YOU SHOULD RECONSIDER.
OH, PAM, I REALLY...
HATE THAT COPIER.
- YEAH, I KNOW.
- YEAH.
BUT I REALLY THINK YOU SHOULD RECONSIDER.
BEESLY, ARE YOU THREATENING ME?
JIM.
JIM, JIM, JIM.
I'M NOT THREATENING YOU.
I LOVE YOU.
BUT YOU SHOULD KNOW
YOU'RE ON VERY DANGEROUS GROUND.
ALL RIGHT.
OKAY.
THIS IS WHERE YOU'LL HAVE
YOUR RECEIVING LINE.
OF COURSE WE'LL CLEAR OUT ALL
THE LIVESTOCK AND HAY INSIDE.
WHAT'S THAT SMELL?
YOU'RE GONNA NEED TO BE MORE SPECIFIC.
MANURE. GET RID OF IT.
MANURE COVERS UP THE SMELL
OF THE SLAUGHTER HOUSE.
DO YOU HAVE TO SLAUGHTER
ON OUR WEDDING DAY?
YOU WANT TO EAT, DON'T YOU?
HONEY, SAY SOMETHING.
DWIGHT, IF WE PAY EXTRA COULD YOU
SLAUGHTER THE ENTREES THE DAY BEFORE?
I'LL CONSIDER IT
SEE?
THAT'S HOW YOU DO IT!
MAKIN' PROGRESS HERE.
DARN!
THERE'S A HOSE OUT BACK.
OKAY.
REMEMBER YOU WERE GONNA GET A NEW CHAIR
AND YOU WERE GONNA GIVE
YOUR OLD CHAIR TO ME.
- REMEMBER THAT?
- YES.
- WELL, THAT NEVER HAPPENED.
- MICHAEL.
I DON'T KNOW. I HAVEN'T DECIDED YET.
I'M JUST GONNA GRAB SOME
LUNCH. WANNA COME WITH?
REALLY?
ABSOLUTELY! YEAH,
THAT WOULD BE AMAZING.
- WHOA, YOU GUYS GOING TO LUNCH?
- ??
- YES.
- MIND IF I JOIN?
- OH, GOD! YEAH!BEST LUNCH EVER!
- ??
LET'S DO IT.
ALL RIGHT! COOL.
- WHERE WE GOING?
- I HAVE NO IDEA.
SO I GUESS THAT'S HOW
THEY'RE GONNA PLAY THIS.
IT IS ON.
SO ON.
LOOK, I REALLY NEED THIS NEW CHAIR.
I MEAN SERIOUSLY.
HOW IS IT POSSIBLE THAT IN FIVE YEARS,
I'VE HAD TWO ENGAGEMENT
RINGS AND ONLY ONE CHAIR?
MICHAEL.
MICHAEL, THAT IS HILARIOUS.
OH, IS SOMEBODY MAKING FUN OF ME?
THE BEST!
GREAT FRIENDS. THANK YOU, MICHAEL.
I GOT YOU SOME TIRAMISU.
NO HARD FEELINGS.
YEAH.
THAT'S COOL.
GOOD STUFF.
YOU LOOK REALLY PRETTY.
THANK YOU.
YEAH.
- MICHAEL.
- YEAH?
HEY! OH, HEY! YOU GOT A SECOND?
I DO.
OH, GOOD.
OH, THAT MUST'VE BEEN SO FUN.
IT WAS FUN. WE HAD A GOOD TIME.
HEY, HAVE I TOLD YOU YOU
LOOK REALLY NICE TODAY?
OH, THANK YOU.
YEAH, IS THAT A NEW TIE?
UM, NO, NOT--
NO, NO, I GOT IT AT TJ MAXX, $4.
THAT IS AMAZING.
YOU THINK THAT'S GOOD.
CHECK OUT THESE PANTS.
$9.
- WHAT?
- $9.
- THE BOYS DEPARTMENT.- NO.
LOOK AT THE ASS.
CHECK OUT THE ASS.
- NO WAY!
- LOOK AT THAT.
YEAH!
SO I GUESS OSCAR AND JIM WERE TALKING
YOUR EAR OFF ABOUT THE NEW COPIER, HUH?
- YES, THEY WERE.
- ??
THEY WERE.
HERE'S WHAT I WAS THINKING.
EVERYONE SITS ON A CHAIR EVERY DAY.
BUT NOT EVERYONE--
SITS ON A COPIER.
OR EVEN USES THE COPIER EVERY DAY.
- YEAH.
- YEAH, RIGHT
VERY VALID.
THAT'S IT.
ALL RIGHT! SEE YOU LATER.
- SEE YA.
- HOT TIE GUY.
WELL...
HAVE YOU MADE A DECISION
ON THE BUTTER SCULPTURE?
NO, I HAVEN'T THOUGHT OF IT.
OKAY, COW,  GOAT, OR SHEEP.
IT'S NOT THAT HARD.
I WOULD LIKE A CAT.
CATS DON'T MAKE BUTTER.
I WOULD LIKE A COW BUTTER
SCULPTURE OF A CAT.
IT DOESN'T MAKE ANY SENSE.
- I'M TELLING YOU
- YES, IT DOES!
- ??
- I WANT A BUTTER SCULPTURE OF A CAT.
COW, GOAT, OR SHEEP.
WHAT IS THIS?
ALL RIGHT, WE'RE ALL ON
THE SAME TEAM. IS IT--
DAMN, WHY IS THAT IN THE KITCHEN?
YOU MIGHT WANT TO CONSIDER
CHANGING TEAMS BECAUSE WE WOULD--
WE WOULD LOVE TO HAVE YOU.
NO, COPIER'S GREAT.
YEAH?
YEAH.
- I HAVE MY COPIES.
- THERE THEY ARE.
AND I HAVE MY ORIGINAL.
YOU GOT IT.
- SO SUCK IT.
- OKAY.
OKAY.
MICHAEL, I BOUGHT YOU A HOT CHOCOLATE.
I HOPE THAT'S OKAY.
OH, THANK YOU, MY DEAR.
WAIT, MICHAEL. LET ME
OPEN THE DOOR FOR YOU.
OH, WELL, CHIVALRY IS NOT DEAD AFTER ALL.
OKAY.
THERE HE IS! THERE HE IS!
HELLO, HELLO. HELLO!
GOOD TO SEE YOU, GOOD TO SEE YOU.
YEAYAH! THERE'S THAT ASS.
HEY, HEY! YEAH, UHN, UHN!
OH, DON'T TAKE IT AWAY!
I ALMOST CHOKED.
HERE'S ANOTHER PLACE.
IT'S BEAUTIFUL.
SO...
WHY DON'T WE TRY THIS OUT?
WE'LL SEE WHAT WOULD HAPPEN.
GIVE IT A LITTLE TEST
DRIVE. WHAT DO YOU SAY?
YOU PRETEND TO BE ANGELA'S FATHER.
YOU WILL PLAY ANGELA, AND
I'LL PRETEND TO BE YOU.
THAT WAY YOU CAN SEE WHAT IT
LOOKS LIKE WHEN YOU'RE UP HERE.
HELLO, I'M ANGELA MARTIN.
- I'M ANDY.
- I WORK WITH DWIGHT.
HE DOESN'T UNDERSTAND
A WORD YOU'RE SAYING.
WHAT?
ALTHOUGH BORN JUST MINUTES FROM
HERE, HE SPEAKS ONLY GERMAN.
CLOSED SOCIETY.
SO NOW AFTER THE READINGS
BY ALL OF YOUR SISTERS,
WE WILL ARRIVE AT THE VOWS. SO CONRAD,
THIS IS A LITTLE TASTE OF
THE CEREMONY, IF YOU WILL.
HE'S EXPLAINING WHY WE'RE
HERE, WHAT WE'RE DOING HERE.
MAKING INTRODUCTIONS.
BLAH BLAH BLAH BLAH.
THEN HE'S GONNA HAVE ANDY
REPEAT A BUNCH OF STUFF.
HE'S GONNA ASK ANDY TO PRODUCE A RING.
I HAVE, UH, NOW JUST
SOME TWINE FOR OUR PURPOSES AND...
YOU WILL PUT THE RING ON HER FINGER.
THEN HE'S GOING TO ASK ANDY,
IF HE WOULD LIKE TO MARRY ANGELA.
AND YOU WILL REPLY "I DO."
AND HE'S GONNA ASK ANGELA IF
SHE WOULD LIKE TO MARRY ANDY.
TO WHICH YOU WILL REPLY...
I DO.
AND THERE WE GO.
OKAY, AND THAT'S JUST
ABOUT IT. MAN AND WIFE.
GOT A CALL ABOUT A PROBLEM UP HERE.
DID SOMEBODY CALL HANK?
HANK, THANK GOD YOU'RE HERE.
THE OFFICE IS AT A CROSSROADS.
SO THERE'S NO SECURITY PROBLEM?
YOU KNOW I HUSTLED UP THE STAIRS.
YES, I NEED YOUR SAGE ADVICE.
AND EVERYONE, WHATEVER HANK DECIDES,
THAT IS THE DECISION.
THAT WILL RESOLVE THIS ISSUE.
YEAH, TAKE AS MANY AS YOU WANT.
THANK YOU, THANK YOU.
YOU KNOW, IT'S NICE AND WARM UP HERE.
YES.
SO WHAT ARE WE TALKING ABOUT?
OKAY, WELL, WE HAVE A SURPLUS.
IMAGINE THAT YOUR PARENTS GIVE
YOU MONEY FOR A LEMONADE STAND--
I KNOW WHAT A SURPLUS IS.
OKAY, GOOD. GOOD.
WELL, HERE'S THE THING.
SOME PEOPLE WANT TO USE THE
SURPLUS TO BUY A NEW COPIER.
OTHER PEOPLE ARE COMPLAINING
ABOUT THE CHAIRS.
- IS THAT THE COPIER?
- IT IS, YES.
WHAT?
I WAS JUST THINKING. LET ME SEE A CHAIR.
- OKAY.
- YOU CAN TRY MINE.
THERE WE GO.
NOT MUCH LUMBAR SUPPORT.
NOW EVERYONE, BEAR IN MIND ONCE AGAIN
THAT WHATEVER HANK SAYS GOES.
HE IS AN IMPARTIAL THIRD PART
ONE THE ONE HAND, THIS COPIER IS VERY OLD.
YOU SHOULD SEE SOME OF
THE NEW COPIERS THEY HAVE.
YOU WOULD NOT BELIEVE WHAT THEY DO.
SO THE COPIER.
- WELL, LET ME FINISH.
- ALL RIGHT, YES.
NOW THE CHAIRS.
THE CHAIRS ARE VERY
WEAK.VERY WEAK CHAIRS.
I COULD NOT SIT ALL DAY IN THIS CHAIR.
WELL, WHAT SHOULD I DO?
LET ME SEE THE COPIER AGAIN.
ALL RIGHT, GET OUT. GET OUT. IT'S--
DWIGHT,
I THOUGHT I KNEW WHAT I WANTED.
AND THEN
BEING HERE WITH YOU AND
THE GERMAN MENNONITE MINISTER,
IT JUST ALL FELT RIGHT.
I MADE A MISTAKE PICKING ANDY.
I KNOW YOU DID.
AND THAT'S WHY I HAVE
TAKEN CARE OF EVERYTHING.
WHAT DO YOU MEAN?
WELL, MONKEY,
HE'S A REAL MINISTER.
AND YOU SAID, "I DO"
AND I SAID, "I DO."
AND ANDY WASN'T SIGNING A RECEIPT.
HE WAS SIGNING OUR MARRIAGE
CERTIFICATE AS-A-WITNESS.
DWIGHT, THAT DOESN'T COUNT!
YES, OF COURSE IT DOES.
NO, IT DOESN'T!
IT DOES IN THE STATE OF PENNSYLVANIA.
- ??
- MRS. SCHRUTE.
WE ARE NOT MARRIED.
WHA--
TAKE THIS THING.
MY--
IT'S NOT MY FAULT YOU
DON'T UNDERSTAND GERMAN.
I'VE BEEN TELLING YOU
TO TAKE IF FOR YEARS!
ARE WE, UH--
WE LEAVING OR WHAT?
MICHAEL.
HEY, DAVID--
I'M SORRY.
I'M SORRY, I'M EATING TIRAMISU.
SOME OF THE CHOCOLATE POWDER
JUST WENT DOWN MY THROAT.
I'M STOPPING NOW.
IS THIS WHY YOU'RE CALLING ME?
NO, NO, NO, NO, NO. NO,
I'M CALLING--
I'M SORRY.
OKAY.
I'M CALLING BECAUSE...
WE HAVE A STUPID BUDGET SURPLUS AND PEOPLE--
EVERYBODY WANTS SOMETHING DIFFERENT.
YOU WANT ME TO WEIGH IN
ON A MINOR BUDGET ISSUE?
NO, NO, NO. I WANT YOU TO MAKE
THE DECISION SO I'M NOT THE BAD GUY.
IF I WERE YOU, I'D JUST RETURN
THE SURPLUS AND TAKE THE BONUS.
THE WHAT NOW?
BRANCH MANAGERS WHO COME IN UNDER
BUDGET GET 15% OF THE SAVINGS.
LIKE A TIP?
$645?
I HATE DISAPPOINTING JUST ONE PERSON.
AND I REALLY HATE DISAPPOINTING EVERYONE.
BUT I LOVE BURLINGTON COAT FACTORY.
YOU GO IN THERE WITH $645,
YOU ARE LITERALLY A KING.
???
OKAY?
SURE--NO, I CAN-- I'LL DOUBLE CHECK.
ALL RIGHT, ATTENTION EVERYONE.
LET ME CALL YOU RIGHT BACK. OKAY.
I HAVE MADE MY DECISION.
WE DO NOT NEED A NEW COPIER.
WE DO NOT NEED NEW CHAIRS.
THIS COPIER...
IS...
WORKING PERFECTLY.
THAT'S THE ORIGINAL.
PAM, WOULD YOU STAND UP FOR A SEC?
SEE HOW RELAXED I AM?
I LIKE THIS CHAIR.
OFFERS GOOD SUPPORT. IT IS
ERKEL-NOMICALLY CORRECT.
IT'S A GOOD CHAIR.
I THINK WE'RE SPOILED BECAUSE WE DON'T
APPRECIATE THE THINGS THAT WE HAVE.
YOU THINK KIDS IN AFRICA HAVE CHAIRS?
NO.
THEY SIT IN BIG PILES OF GARBAGE.
DO YOU THINK THEY HAVE COPIERS?
THEY DON'T HAVE COPIERS.
THEY DON'T EVEN--
THEY DON'T EVEN HAVE PAPER.
AND WE ARE SPOILED BECAUSE WE
THROW OUT PERFECTLY GOOD TIRAMISU
BECAUSE IT HAS A LITTLE TINY HAIR ON IT.
MY POINT IS THIS.
I HAVE SEEN THE LIGHT IN
TERMS OF WHAT WE NEED
AND IT IS NOTHING.
DO YOU KNOW?
DO I KNOW WHAT?
I THINK YOU KNOW.
NO.
KNOW WHAT?
YEAH, KNOW WHAT?
DOES ANYONE HAPPEN TO KNOW
WHAT 15% OF 4,300 IS?
$645.
- MICHAEL'S A GENIUS.
- RIGHT.
WHY DID YOU SAY DOLLARS?
BECAUSE THAT IS HOW MY MIND WORKS.
WHAT'S 15% OF 200?
THANK YOU.
EVERYONE, MICHAEL IS RETURNING THE
SURPLUS SO HE CAN KEEP 15% AS A BONUS.
WAIT, WHAT?
YOU CAN DO THAT?
HEY, MICHAEL,WHAT'S 394 TIMES 5,912?
LET'S SEE.
YOU'RE GONNA GIVE YOURSELF
A BONUS OF $645 INSTEAD OF
GETTING THE ENTIRE OFFICE
SOMETHING IT REALLY NEEDS.
I DON'T NEED $645.
I ALREADY HAVE $645, MORE OR LESS.
- YOU'RE GONNA GET US A COPIER THEN?
- THIS IS STUPID.
- OR CHAIRS.
- SO, SO STUPID.
AND, GOD,
THAT'S MY PHONE.
- I DIDN'T HEAR A PHONE.
-TO BE CONTINUED.
NO, I DON'T--
THIS DOESN'T CHANGE ANYTHING.
I HAVE A VERY IMPORTANT DECISION TO MAKE.
WE NEED A NEW COPIER.
WE NEED NEW CHAIRS.
AND I NEED TO FIGURE OUT A WAY TO KEEP
THIS MONEY WITHOUT HAVING EVERYBODY HATE ME.
HEY, TUNA, CHECK IT OUT.TUNA SANDWICH.
JUST LIKE YOU.
WHAT--
NOW I HAVE TO TAKE CARE OF A LEGAL ISSUE.
WAS THAT HOT OR WHAT?
SO WHAT'S IT GONNA BE?
MICHAEL, YOU HAVE TO MAKE A
DECISION. THE DAY IS ALMOST DONE.
LET ME JUST SAY YOU'VE BEEN PROMISING
ME THIS CHAIR SINCE THE DAY YOU HIRED ME.
YOU ARE A SMART GUY.I KNOW
YOU'LL DO THE RIGHT THING.
YOU THINK IT'S EASY?
IT'S YOUR JOB.
OKAY, YOU KNOW WHAT? WHY DON'T YOU GUYS DE?
I AM GOING TO GET UP AND I'M
GONNA BE OUT IN THE COMMON AREA.
BUT YOU NEED TO DECIDE.
OTHERWISE, I'M TAKING THE BONUS.
ALL RIGHT?
IT IS A CLASSIC MANAGEMENT TACIT.
YOU HAVE TWO SIDES, A DEADLINE.
YOU KNOW THAT NEITHER OF
THEM ARE GONNA CONCEDE.
WHAT YOU DO IS YOU PUT THEM
IN THE ROOM AND YOU JUST
- HEY.
HEY, WE'RE GOING WITH THE CHAIRS.
WHAT?
I JUST FIGURED I'D RATHER HAVE
NEW CHAIRS THAN NOTHING AT ALL.
THANKS, MICHAEL.
GOOD WORK. I'M PROUD OF YOU.
MOTHER--
WHAT DID WE LEARN THIS WEEK?
WELL, ONE, THANKS TO ME,
MY TEAM IS MUCH, MUCH FASTER
AT COMING TO DECISIONS
THAN I THOUGHT THEY WOULD BE.
NUMBER TWO, NEVER BUY A FUR
COAT WITH A CREDIT CARD
UNTIL YOU ABSOLUTELY HAVE
THE MONEY TO PAY FOR IT.
AND THREE, YOU SHOULD NOW THAT
SOME PEOPLE THINK IT'S COOL
TO THROW BUCKETS OF FAKE BLOOD ON YOU
AS YOU ARE WALKING OUT OF
BURLINGTON COAT FACTORY.
TRUCE.
YEAH, I GUESS. I WON.
YOU DID WIN.
You Did Win.
ANYWAY, I'M GONNA NEED THREE COPIES OF
EACH OF THESE, STAPLED AND COLLATED.
TOTALLY KIDDING.
I'M GONNA NEED FOUR.
welcome to www.1000fr.com
www.tvsubtitles.net