Michael,since it is your 15th
anniversary at the company,
I thought it might be Appropriate
To begin the festivities
- With a 15-minute Round
of applause. - I like it.
- Followed by a 15-minute Moment
of silence. - I don't know.
Is it classy enough?
Jim,enough With the classy,okay?
I just feel like After
15 years at this company-
And bravo,by
the way-
That we should celebrate with A
very classy event, A night to rember.
I think you're right.
This party has To have
all the excitement,
Drama,and intrigue Of my time here.
- And of course... classy.
- And classy,yeah.
Michael,You're just agreeing with
him Because he's wearing a tux,
Don't you see What he's doing here?
Last week,dwight sent Out
a memo about the dress cod
So this is me showing him that
I'm taking it very seriously.
Oh,here's one.
A string quartet
Playing classy-cal music.
Mm,you know...
That's good,But it's not classy.
I- i need
something classy,
Like the opening Of a car dealership.
- That's it. Or mr. Peanut.
- Yes!
Mr. Peanut is not classy.
He is- he is a
regular peanut.
He just happens to have a
ca,A monocle,and a top hat.
That's what makes him classy.
Okay,how about this
An ice sculpture Shaped like you,
Covered in Chocolate-covered
strawberries.
You're trying too hard,And
that's just not classy.
See,the thing about classy
Is it's a state of mind.
Well,i'm sorry,i just Don't
know what classy is then.
Okay,let's just Try
this one on for size-
And i apologize,because it's
Right off the top of my head-
An ice sculpture...
Of you,completely
Surrounded by a variety
Of chocolate-covered fruits.
- Strawberries?
- That's inspired.
I said that!
- Not classy.
- Not classy at all.
Declasse.
French! Classy.
- =www. ydy. com/bbs=- Proudly
Presents
- =www. ydy. com/bbs=- Sync:
YTET-¿¨»Ò
The Office
Season 05 Episode 18
Hi,can i help you?
Yeah,i'm charles Miner
to see michael scott.
Sure. Just one
second,please. Have a seaoy.
- Yes?
- Michael,there's a Charles miner here to see you.
Miner? I hardly know her.
Hello? Yh,are you coming out now?
Well,well,well,Who have we here?
It is prince charles miner.
At your service.
Everybody,This is sir charles miner.
And he is the new vp
Fothe northeast region,
So just give it up
For this big guy,right?
Give it up. Here he is.
There he is. Hey,hi.
Hi,everyone. Wow!
Hold that thought!
You know what,i want everybody
To go into the break room,
I have a little surprise For you.
Go ahead. You too.
Dwight,uld you Escort
our guest in there?
Come on. Here we go,don't be shy.
Don't be shy,You're one of us.
Dwight,stall him a little bit.
I'm going to get the fish.
Hey. Yes?
Really wish You would've told me
The new boss Was coming in today.
What? No,i didn't Want
to make everybody nervous.
No,i mean,i could've
Brought a change of clothes.
You look dynamite.
What are you talking about?
Very slick. Okay,let me get the fish.
Originally founded in 1866,
Scranton quickly became One
of pennsylvania's largest
Anthracite Coal ming communities.
Surprise! There nothing in here.
The real surprise Is
in the conference room.
Let's go! Ah! God!
Okay,come on! Come on!
I'll finish it up later,But essentially
What we're
talking about is-
Surprise!
As you can see,i turned The bagels
from o's into c's,For charles.
- Thank you.
- Took me all night.
This is What you did last night?
I met this guy At corporate last week,
And we were just Digging
each other's vibe.
I was totally grooving
on him,And vice-versa.
And besides,the It Two
people to have his job
Were jan and ryan.
The former was my lover,
And the latter my best friend.
So who knows? I do.
It's going to be mental.
It's going to be mta
Oh,my god. He's like
A black george clooney.
Really? I don't see it.
I mean,he's okay.
He's not unattractive.
He's... Hey,how you doing?
I'm jim halpert,from sales.
Just wanted to say if you
Need anything,let me know.
Why are you wearing a tuxedo?
I didn't think you'd notice.
It's funny actually,there's
Another salesman out here,
Dwight schrute,he sent out
This memo as he always does,
And it was about
professionalism In the workplace,
And of course he singled me out.
So i just had toess with him.
Oh,you'd understand It
if you'd read the memo,
Which i should probably get you.
There's probably one In the... drawer.
It was pretty crazy.
But... Not more crazy than wearing
A tux at work,i grant you that.
,i'm going to,uh...
- Your name's jim?
- Jim halpert,yep.
Just going To let you
get back to it. So...
He just had To wear his tux today.
I thought it'd be funny.
Took him 40 minutes To get ready.
All right,let me introduce
You some of the troops.
Accounting,front and center.
Come on up here,I'd like
you to meet somebody.
This is the accounting Department.
Hey,i come From accounting,too.
Oh,nerd alert. This is oscar
martinez. He is latino.
And he just got out of
A long-term relationship
With a man,gil,Who broke his heart.
But he did not bring
Any of that into work.
It did not affect his Job
performance whatsoever.
And i'm very proud of him.
- That's good. It's good to meet you.
- Good.
This little Hell-raiser angela.
She has slept with a bunch Of
different guys in the office.
One over there,In the orange.
Where's the other...?
You know,michael, I don't need
to know Everyone's sexual history.
Well,perfect. Because we have Now arrived
at kevin, And he has no sexual history.
How about i just say hi
To everyone at one time?
Good. Good,good,good.
Everyone,please give
it up For charles miner.
Thank you,michael. And thank
you For the c-shaped bagels.
- Oh,well...
- That's great,that's great.
Above and beyond.
Hey,you know We're in tough times
And we're not Immune to this economy.
That's true. But the goal is to,you
know,Fight our way through this.
Hey. Stanley hudson.
Are there going to be layoffs?
- No,absolutely not.
- Uh,hold on,michael.
Uh,stanley,you know,We
can't make any promises,
But we'll y everything In
our power to avoid that.
Do you have specifics?
Sp- well,michael should've
Filled you in last week.
Well,due to the economy, There's
a lot of Worry going around,
- And i didn't want to
worry- - you didn't tell them?
Well... Why
don't- yeah.
What i told
michael- tot
Is that we are Cutting
3% across the board.
Which means we no longer will
Be matching 401k contributions.
- And all overtime requests Will need To come through The corporate office.
- Fantastic.
- Well,it's not official.
- It is official.
well... It is off
And actually guys,I'm
encouraging branches
To consider a freeze On
discretionary spending.
Such as salary benefits,Et cetera.
No,not- et
cetera,insurance-
- Not salary... petty cash.
- Right.
Supplies,And you
know,parties. Things like that.
Well... What abouyour
party? Oh,well... that.
Okay,okay,you know what?
I think this has been great.
I think this gives us a lot
To think about,doesn't it?
Charles miner,Ladies and gentlemen.
He has a long trip home.
Thank him for coming,We
have to get back to work.
Michael,i'm going To stay for the day.
Oh,no,no,no. You don't have to do that.
I've got this covered.
This was just a Meet
and greet,you don't-
No,it's a little More
involved than that.
I'm going to set up In here,okay?
I am thrilled That
the new boss has taken
Such an active interest In
all of the responsibilities
That i'm supposed to have.
Thrilled.
David,It was my understanding
That i was not going To be managed.
What gave youhat idea?
- It was my understanding.
- I see.
Listen,why- why don't we Just
leave that position vacant?
Truth be told,i think i thrive
Under a lack of accountability.
Look,michael. Charles is very
qualified. Get to know him.
I really think the two
of you Are gonna make a g
But the branch Is still mine?
You're still The branch manager,yes.
And if you need anything else
At all,just let charles know.
- Ask him about the party.
- Oh,right.
David are you cong To my
15th anniversary party?
- I'll give it my best shot-
- no,no,no,the other thing.
Oh,okay. If we hired cirque de
soleil As salaried employees,
Will that help us With
the year-end tax stuff?
Think he hung up?
No.
I just got off the
horn With david wallace,
And he said that you and i
Should try to get To know
each other better. And i agree.
So,what i would Like you to do is,
Tell me something that you've
Never told anybody before.
- No.
- Come on. What's your wife's name?
Where did you work Before you came here?
- Saticoy steel.
- Beautiful.
See,african-americans Have such
a rich history Of unusual names.
No i worked at a company
Called saticoy steel.
Y... st... You're-
you're not from paper?
- No.
- Does david know this?
Yeah,he knows. He just
wants a good manager.
Well that actually,Is
a... excellent segway
Into really what Is my only point.
I- i don't need To
be managed,charles.
And if you want To pick up some tips
Observing here and taking Them to
the other branches, It's all good.
But jan would mostly come
by When she was super horny.
And ryan wouldome by to visit
His parents and do laundry.
So... Are we clear?
That's not how I plan on doing things.
Well,i'll just Bounce that off david
See if it cos back.
I'll tell david What he needs to know.
Sorry. David wants it this way.
- Well,whatever david wants...
- Okay.
Michael scott Calling for david.
Well,just tell him To call me
as asap as possible. Thanks.
Oh,michael. Come on,no.
You have to charm them.
- David wallace's office.
- Hey there,gorgeous. How you doing today?
I'm good,thank you.
How's it hanging?
All right.
Good. Listen,My name is michael scotch,
And i just wanted to say...
That i've got david wallace's
Son in the trunk of my car.
If he doesn't get on This
phone in five seconds-
Idiot,idiot,idiot. What are you doing?
- You've got too-
- god! Oh,my god.
David wallace's office.
Hi,stephanie. It's michael scott again.
I just spoke With michael scotch.
And the son's Going to be returned,
- Everything's fine.
- Michael...
- And i really,Really need to talk to david.
- Please hold.
Charles miner.
Hello? Hello,who is this? Who is this?
I was never given a name.
Oh,my god.
Uh,hi. Can i help you? I
don't think that anyone here-
- Ma'am...
- uh, hey everyone,Lunch is on me today. Here you go.
Wow,that is so unnecessary.
Are you kidding me with this?
On the day that I bring in breakfast?
Hey,man,it's no big deal.
I wish you Had told us sooner.
Because i was going To
go to the vending machine
And get an egg salad.
You still have that option.
- Thanks again,charles.
- You're welcome.
Thank you.
- Nobody thanked
me- - thanks,charles.
- For breakfast,Except charles.
You say,"no more parties,"
And then you spend All
this money on lunch.
I think it's A little hypercritical.
I do this For every branch i go to.
If you do not like
it,Then... i think there are
Some bagels Left over from this morning.
Damnit,stephanie,Put me through to him.
Is that him in the background? David?
David. David. Pick up the phone.
Should i seduce him?
No,no one wants to see that.
- Michael.
- Yep?
I just reized That i
used the 2008 calendar
To do the spreadsheets
For january and february.
I may need to come In
this weekend to fix it.
Do some overtime. You wanna
do some overtime This weekend?
You know what,kevin,I
applaud your initiative.
- Yes,you
may- - uh,no.
Sorry,michael. No,kevin,right?
I'm gonna need you To do
that during office hours.
- Okay.
- Okay. Thank you.
Kevin,this is my branch.
You don't ask charles,You ask me.
I say approved.
That's not the way It's going to work
- Yes,it is.
- No,it is not.
No,it is not.
Okay,so we're On the same page,great.
- Okay,michael...
- No,seriously.
- How old are you?
- Oh,no.
- Okay...
I can tell michael's mood
By which comedy routine
He chooses to do.
The more infantile,Thmore uet he is.
And he just skippedthe ace
Venturatalking butt thing.
He never skips it.
This is bad.
- Five-years-old.
Dude,stop.
Michael,Stop doing that.
Gonna get in A whole mess of trouble.
- I'm going to walk away.
- I'm going to Ik away.
You need to stop doing that.
I'm kidding around! Wow,relax everybody.
It was just a joke. It's fine.
Boy,so touchy.
Ppc,let's continue our morning
Meeting in the conference room.
And then out of that cake
Pops another stripper
Holding a smaller cake
And then an even smaller
Stripper pops out of that one.
What is that Smaller stripper holding?
- A cupcake.
- Nice.
It's cupcakes and
strippers All the way down.
What exactly is the ppc?
Oh,that's The party planning committee.
They snd hours Planning parties.
Excuse me,guys.
- What's going on in here?
- Party planning committee.
Not your concern,charles.
This doesn't seem like a Good
way to spend company time.
Really? Well then,how would
We come up with great ideas
Like jim's. Go ahead.
No,i would like To get
work,actually,please.
What you got,jim?
What is a two-way petting zoo?
You pet the animals,They pet you back.
It's a great idea.
And we have a cake in the
shape Of a bale of hay.
It's really just A regular-shaped cake.
But it's cool,and
it's- hey,guys,you know,
This isn't a good use
Of company time,michael.
You're talking about
My anniversary party,so.
Okay,everyone except for
Michael,go back to your desks.
Yeah,why don't you do
that? Thank you very much.
Yeah,here we go. Mm-kay.
Okay,michael...
I'm dissolving this committee.
- What?
- Yeah.
I mean,come on,This is a work place.
It isn't designed For your vanity.
I've been here for 15 years. *****
You have been here
one day. End of story.
You have no right to cancel
My 15th anniversary part
End of story. End of
story! End of story.
I don't care If i've hurt your feelings
Or you do not Agree with my methods,
But it is over.
Okay,no,no,no,no. You know what?
I'm going to new york!
And i am going To talk to david wallace
I'm going To tell him everything.
And i'm sorry To say you're screwed.
And you know what?
You are gonna be through. And i'm sorry.
- I'm sorry to do that to you.
- Right.
Do you even know How paper is made?
It's not like steel,You
don't put it into a furnace.
If you put paper into a furnace,You
know what would happen? You'd ruin it.
Come in.
- Hey.
All right,charles,I got to be honest,
I think we really got Off
on the wrong foot here.
And truth be told,I'm
a pretty smart guy.
And a hard-worker and a great
Number two for the office.
- Number two?
- Second in command. Toy goal.
Oh,i- i didn't Know
that position existed.
Oh,that's Because at first it was
A made up position for dwight,Just
to make him feel better.
Assistant To the regional manager.
But then he lost that,And
michael gave it to me.
So you're the assistant
To the regional manager?
Assistant regional manager,Yep.
Any responsibilitie Come with it?
Not- not
exactly.
Do you want to keep This made up
position? It's important to you?
All right. I will...
just let you get back To it,okay?
- would you,uh...?
- Yep, - thanks.
Hello,stephanie... Okay,where is he?
Michael.
What are you-
So is this The meeting
you' been all day?
How did you get here,Michael?
I drove.
Okay.
Cancelled my 15th anniversary party.
Just pulled the rug out From under me.
He said,"no figs. "
I've already bought them.
And i don't have A placto store them.
So i feel like i've been sort of boned.
- Michael- - you
talk to him about this?
You've talked To him all day,obviously.
Did you talk to him about this?
Well,i didn't know About
the figs,specifically-
Okay,then i don't get it.
It doesn't make any sense to me.
Because i thought In the new system,
That i was Supposed to talk t
And then charles is
Supposed to talk to you,
Then that will Dilute any need for me
To ever talk to you again.
That's not Exactly the new system.
Clearly,That's what you wanted.
Nope. 15 years...
- I've been here,And i've sacrificed a lot.
- Yes.
I've put Having a family on hold.
We didn't ask you to do that.
And i've never gone Hang-gliding.
And i've never driven my car
To the top of mount washington.
Okay,it was Nice meeting everyone.
All right,and i will See
you in a couple of weeks.
Cool. Excellent.
It was very nice Meeting
you,charles miner.
Okay.
See you.
Bye!
And for my next trick,I will
make my career... Disappear.
I can see Our kids facing obstacles,
Beinha black And half indian,but...
It's so worth it,you guys.
There's just me here.
I am gonna get him To buy
me a prime rib tonight.
I think he left.
What?!
Move!
Hello,charles!? Charles?
- Is that his scarf?
- No!
Charles and kelly? Absolutely not.
He is a sophisticated man.
He does not need to go dumpster
Diving for companionship. Okay?
I don't understand
that,After 15 years...
Of service here,I have to get in the car
And drive to new york
In order to talk to you.
That doesn't seem right to me.
That doesn't seem fair.
And i think...
That i've earned More than that.
You're right. Yes.
I get it. I get it,michael.
Oka here's what i'm gonna do.
We will Move some money around,
And i will personally see to
it That you have your party.
You'll have your figs,I
will be in attendance,
It's gonna be great. How's that?
- I quit.
- What?
You have no idea How high i can fly.
www.tvsubtitles.net