It's 4:30 in the morning.
Do you know where your kids are?
???
If you are ryan's parents
or pam's parents Or my parents,
you do.
They're gonna be in this van.
With me. Who am I?
Nothing to fear.
I am just a 44-Year-Old guy
with a paper route.
Time to make the donuts!
Come on.
Whoa!
No, I promise I won't do it again.
Come on.
De-Nied!
We've been making 5:00 a.M.
Deliveries For a couple weeks now.
Ever since I've gotten clean,
There's something
about fresh morning air that...
just really makes me sick.
Hello! Time to ma the donuts!
Oh, halpert! Whoa!
Boner patrol, arrest that man!
Your donuts make me go nuts!
Hey, pam.
We got the van at a used car lot.
We t "alleluia church
of scranton" in korean.
It was either this or an old school bus
With an owl living in it.
You didn't happen to bring
any coffee, did you, michael?
Milk and sugar.
Oh, awesome. You're a life saver.
Wait, is this just milk and sugar?
That's what I said.
Do you drink this every day?
Every morning.
We're, uh, we're doing okay.
A couple weeks in
and,m, we're having fun.
Uh, yep. We have 20--
- Oh, oh, excuse me.
- ???
Sorry. Sorry, no. It's, uh,
it's a paper company now.
It's not for the church.
http://notabenoid.com/book/2408/8079/
...
The Office S05E23
Okay, who covers bans pet grooming?
Oh, they're my client.
NO. they were your client.
They just called and said
they're switching over
To michael scott paper company.
Shame, jim. I expected more.
In the last month,
We have lost ten major
clients to michael scott.
What are we supposed to do?
- They keep undercutting us on price.
- I don't want to hear excuses.
I want to see improvements.
This is unacceptable.
Hey, boss.
I'd just like to point out
That I have be here
less time than these guys.
Why are you telling me this?
I just think the bar
should be lower for a newbie.
Is this something
you really want to have said?
I don't want to have said that.
But I think it's important
that you know it.
I don't know what to do
to inspire these people.
Okay, maybe it's my fault--
It's not your fault.
Some people just don't
want to be inspired.
I wrote a memo to all departments
Asng them to find ways to save money.
But, uh--
Charles, I got your memo. Thank you.
I want you to know
I'm putting my foot down
When it comes to expense reports.
Waste not, want not.
Uh, well said, an
Been there, done that.
You know what we need?
We need some couches in here.
Michael, we should really consider
Getting a delivery guy.
Oh, you know what you would love?
Isf we built a loft.
Why would I love that?
Can we afford a delivery guy?
Like in a dorm room.
You put your desk underneath,
You have your loft up top.
You can sleep up top.
Yeah, I know what a loft is.
Most dorm rooms don't even have that.
Most do in the magazines.
Let's see what a delivery guy costs.
We should look into that.
Or we just go for the loft.
Hi. Hi.
Would you let charles know
that david is here,
- Sure.
- please?
Jim, hey.
- Hey, david.
- David wallace!
Hello, we've been expecting you,
david wallace.
Charles and I were waiting for you.
There he is.
There he is. How was the trip up?
Uh, a lot better than a month
At the scranton radisson, I'm sure.
Oh, you know,
it hasn't been that bad.
Hasn't been that bad.
These people are the salt
of the earth down here.
You couldn't ask for
a better way to learn a company.
I feel like I should be thanking you.
The conference room is ready
If we want to get started.
You know, I just want
to address everyone first.
Oh, yeah. Take your time.
Stanley, pay attention.
- Hi, everyone.
- Hi.
Hi.
- Look. It's no secret--
- Hi.
Hello. Uh, it is no secret
That michael scott paper has siphoned
off A largchunk of our core business.
And I'm here-- I just
want to reassure everyone
That we think this is
just a temporary setback.
- Right.
- Okay?
Maybe, and I don't know,
If you had just returned michael's call,
None of us would've lost clients.
I've been wondering
that myself lately.
Wee just gonna get started.
We're gonna figure this out.
Rest assured. Jim,
can you come in with us please?
Uh, jim. Hold on.
You know, david,
Uh, dwight's been my guy.
- Okay? Yeah, jim, uh...
- Hmm.
Really? I find that
extraordinarily surprising.
He shows promise.
And jim, I don't-- I--
He's been disappointment.
We'll bring 'em both in.
Okay, great.
Uh, dwight, come on in.
Also jim.
Come along, after thought.
How much can we afford
to pay a delivery guy?
Well, if these numbers
you gave me are correct--
They are correct, sir.
Then u can't afford
to pay him anything.
Okay.
A empt ahumor.
Swing and a miss.
Your prices are too low.
Lowest in town.
Why do you think
staples and dunder mifflin
Can't match your prices?
Corporate greed?
Look, our pricing model is fine.
I reviewed the numbers myself.
Over time with enough volume,
weece profitable.
Yeah, with a fixed cost
pricing model that's correct.
Yeah.
But you need to use a
variable cost pricing model.
Okay, sure.
Right. So...
Why don't you explain
what that is to--
So they can under--
- ???
- Just explain what that is.
Explain what you think that is.
- Okay.
- Just explain that.
As you sell more paper
And your company grows,
So will your costs.
For example, delivery man,
Health care.
Well, we don't--
Business expansion.
Whatever, yeah. So--
At these prices,
the more paper you sell
The less money you'll make.
Our prices are the only thing
Keeping us in business.
They're actually
putting you out of business.
Okay, okay.
Hold on, hold on.
Ty, I would like you to
crunch those numbers again.
It's a program.
There's no such thing--
Just crunch 'em.
Just crunch 'em please.
Crunch.
Did it help?
Hi, jerry. Michael scott.
Well, this is slightly embarrassing.
Um, I'm going to have to...
Ask you to pay me
a little bit more money
For that delivery
we dropped off yesterday.
Yeah. We did.
We got the check.
But we're just going to need
A much, much bigger check.
When a child gets
behind the wheel of a car
And runs into a tree,
You don't blame the child.
He didn't know any better.
You blame the 30-Year-Old woman
Who got in the passenger seat
And said, "drive, kid. I trust you."
Now would corporate approve
a temporary price reduction
For returning customers?
- God, no.
- Stupid.
Yeah, makes us look weak.
I agree. It just--
I say we fill
michael's office with bees.
My apiarist owes me a favor.
Really? Does hdo good work or--
No, jim. I use a bad apiarist.
Fellas, why don't
we take a five-Minute break?
And then we will come back, start fresh,
Sort this out.
Five mites exactly.
Okay.
Hey, dwight. Can I talk to you?
- Sure thing.
- Yeah.
Hey.
I saw you called.
You're just out of business?
We have maybe a month.
I don't know what I'm gonna do.
Oh, yeah, well, don't worry about it.
We'll figure it out. We'll be okay.
That's what michael said.
Oh, yeah, only this
time wewillbe okay.
Idiot. Idiot. Idiot.
- Oh, that's my new "dwight" ring.
- I like it.
- Good, right?
Hello.
Idiot, we're starting back up.
This is dwight, by the way.
Oh, okay.
Don't worry about it.
Did I ever tell you about the day
That steve martin died?
- Steve martin's not dead, michael.
- I know.
But I always thought
That the day that he died
Would be the worst day of my life.
And I was wrong. It's this.
You want to hear something sad?
I would love that.
So jim and I are getting married
And the wedding's really expensive,
So I tried to get a job on the weekends
To earn extra money.
I applied to old navy,
target, and wal-Mart.
None of 'em called me back.
Not even for an interview.
I never went to thailand.
Really?
I went to fort lauderdale.
Was it nice?
Yeah, it was amazing.
There was a great
pad thai place, though.
I love pad thai.
You never had pad thai.
No.
There's a lot I haven't done.
Now, this is the projection
- of over three months.
- ???
We still have the inventory sitting--
- ??
Let me float
something out there, okay?
Can I just say--
- Can I say something?
- ???
- Yeah, yeah.
There is a hive of bees
outside the front door.
We kidnap the queen,
Extract her alarm pheromones,
Place them on a flushable wipe.
Put that in his bathroom.
I can't believe
I'm about to say this, but..
the cheapest option...
Is to make michael an offer.
Yes.
Yes, I was gonna say the same thing.
We should buy him out.
- Oh, but you didn't.
- ??
Oh, man!
If only michael had children.
That's how you really
apply the pressure.
What is wrong with you?
Jim, you're-- You're
pretty close with him.
You think they'd be up
for hearing an offer?
Oh, I don't know.
You know, they've taken
a good deal of clients, so.
I mean, I guess-- I guess
I could go down there
And try to nudgehe in
the right direction.
- You know what?
- ???
Why don't I do it, okay?
Michael adores me.
I'm the man for this job.
Charles, you got my back on this?
No, jim, I think you should go.
Okay, so I'll be back in, um...
Back in a bit.
Hey, can I talk to
you guys for a second?
We're not hiring, jim.
Actually here for something else.
Listen, I can't
make you laugh right now.
You know I love a good guessing game,
But why don't I just
tell you what I'm here for?
Turns out you guys have
made a pretty big dent
In the dunder mifflin sales.
Oh, that's nice.
David wallace has
asked me to come down here
And see if you would be interested
In dundemifflin buying you out.
Seriously?
Are you being serious?
He's bluffing, pam.
Jim, what you donundetand
Is that this company's worthl--
- Oh!
- No--
- We don't have--
- Oh!
See, I'm here to learn as
little information as possible.
All I really need to hear
Is if your incredibly successful company
Would be receptive to a buyout.
Yes.
- Yes.
- Maybe.
Three yes.
I will see you titans of industry
Upstairs.
Yes, well, we're
not only tight-Ends,
We are also quarterbacks.
Missed the last part.
- That's a pun.
- Got it.
Yep!
Oh. Wow.
Okay, so you're not
going to reveal in any way
That we're broke.
Of course not.
That we're having
any problems at all.
- Nope, ne,ope.
- Right.
Just to reiterate, none of us
Is going to say anything
That might indicate we are going broke.
Right. Right.
There is no way in hell
That I am going to say that we're broke.
Oh, I'm really worried I'm gonna say it.
No, michael.
- ??
- A no, man.
You're-- You're fine.
We have to come from
- a position of strength.
- I'm good, I'm good.
Just put it out of your mind.
It is. I'm good.
- Hello.
- Hi.
Michael scott paper company
To see mr. David wallace.
I believe we're expected.
Well, well, well.
How the turntables...
Michael, in order to
expedite these negotiations,
We are prepared to make you
a very generous offer.
And we are prepared
to reject that offer.
Michael, you haven't even heard--
Never accept their first offer.
What is your second offer?
$12,000.
Are you kidding me?
That is insultingly low.
I don't even want to hear
what your first offer was.
What do you hear?
Here's the situation.
Your company is four weeks old.
I know this business.
I know what suppliers are charging.
I know you can't be
making very mucmoney.
I don't know how your prices are so low
But I know it can't keep up that way.
I'm sure you're scared.
Probably in debt.
This is the best offer you're gonna get.
I'll see your situation
and I'll raise you a situation.
Your company is losing
clients left a right.
You have a stockholder meeting coming up
And you're going to
have to explain to them
Why your most profitable branch
is bleeding.
So they may be looking for
a little change in the cfo.
So I don't think I need
to wait out dunder mifflin.
I thk I just have to wait out you.
Okay, now, I don't know
that I can get this.
I do have to go to
the board for approval.
How's about $60,000?
60 thou.
Michael.
- What?
- We'll have to talk--
We're gonna have to talk about this.
Just amongst ourselves.
Okay, yes. Please take the room.
Be right outside.
Take your time.
Oh, my god. Oh, my god.
- $60,000. Are you kidding me?
- We are so rich.
Well, jerry, the one who got away.
May I ask why you're leaving
The michael scott paper company?
Really?
Please hold.
- Charles.
- Dwight.
May I have your attention?
The michael scott
paper company is broke.
What? How'd you hear that?
They've been calling
all of their clients
And begging them to pay more money.
That can only mean one thing.
They're desperate.
Which can only mean one thing.
They're total failures.
- Great work, dwight.
- Quiet, you.
No, I mean, great detective work.
'Cause this must be the first case
You've ever cracked, right?
You don't crack a case.
At has a pejorative connotation.
That's like calling a policeman a cop.
You solve a case, and yes,
I've solved plenty.
So how long can they stay viable?
What are your top five cases?
I'm gonna answer charles first.
Because you've solved zero cases.
Okay, one. Case of the beet bandit.
Missing beets from all over the farm.
No footpris. Inside job.
Mose in socks. Boom, case closed.
Okay, do not go anywhere
near the conference room.
Done.
Because you have embarrassed me
For the last time today.
Got it?
I'm not-- I'm
not following you.
You two are morons.
Got it.
- Wh--
- Get out.
So you've thought it over, yes,
And you accept our offer.
We can finally put
this whole thing behind us?
No.
Can you give us
another minute please?
Yeah.
Oh, okay.
- Michael.
- How could you do this to me, michael?
You just cost me $60,000.
Why are you assuming
you'd get the whole thing?
It's a lot of money, okay.
But we need money coming in every week.
We need jobs.
Wouldn't you rather
have a fishing pole than a fish?
I would rather have 60,000, honestly.
No, michael's right.
Jobs are safer.
Agreed?
Agreed.
- Yeah.
But that's all, okay.
Yeah, discuss these things--
Shut up, shut up.
Hello?
I nt my old job back.
I want my old parking space back.
I want a sebring.
They don't make them anymore.
And I want charles gone.
I am not firing charles.
He's very valuable.
That's very kind of you
to say, david.
I need him gone.
No.
Okay, then I want pam back.
Uh, you already have
a new receptionist--
Sales.
Thank you.
Pam's not a salesperson.
Yes, she is.
At the michael scott
paper company in its heyday.
That's right.
Okay.
Please continue.
And ryan.
Ryan cost dunder mifflin
Hundreds of thousands
of dollars, michael.
- Ryan is--
- You know, david,
I don't care if ryan
murdered his entire family.
He is like a son to me.
Do you realize what
you're asking for here?
You're talking about
salary plus health benefits.
And dental this time.
Insurance, taxes,
social security for three people.
This is a heck of
a lot more than 60 grand.
You're talking about
a multi-Million dollar buyout.
These are our demands.
Your company cannot
be worth that much.
Our company is worth nothing.
That's the difference between you and I.
Business isn't about money to me, david.
If tomrow my company goes under,
I will just start another paper company.
And then another
and another and another.
I have no shortage of company names.
- Michael.
- That's one of 'em!
Yes.
These are our demands.
This is what we want.
Our balls are in your court.
Okay. Deal.
Okay?
Can whave the room please?
Yeah.
Yes! Can you believe it?
- Yes! Yes! Yes!
- Great job!
Right here!
That's what I'm talking about!
There are certain defining moments
in a person's life.
The day he is born.
The day he grows hair.
The day he starts a business.
And the day he sells that business
back to dunder mifflin.
What have I learned from all of this?
It is far too early to tell.
I just know that I am flying high
And I don't even want to think about it.
I just want to enjoy it.
- Hey, guys--
- No, no. You're done.
HWHWHhwhwhWHHWhwhhwhWHHWH!!!
www.tvsubtitles.net