Dunder mifflin.
This is erin.
He's not available right now.
Uh-Huh.
Yes.
Sure, i'll give him the message
when he gets up. Gets back.
Michael had chicken pot pie
for lunch.
Actually,
let me rephrase that.
Michael had anentire
chicken pot pie for lunch.
And-- Let me
be more specific.
Michael ate an entire family-Sized
Chicken pot pie for lunch,
And then he promptly
fell asleep. So
we're all trying to be very quiet
So as to not wake him up before 5:00 p.M.
Which, actually,
should be in about...
ten minutes.
Okay, i'm gonna go in there
And change the computer.
Are you sure
you can change his watch?
I can do it.
What do you need from me?
Normally, i don't condone
leaving early.
But i have an appointment
with the horse doctor.
How that horse became
a doctor, i don't know.
Nah, i'm kidding.
He's just a regular doctor Who shoots your
horse in the head When its leg is broken.
Like clock work.
Ohh.
Oh, no.
Uh-Oh.
- What's so funny?
- You had to be there!
Oh, yay!
Geography joke.
Oh, my-- Oh, wow.
Okay, all right.
Let's all go home.
Come on.
See you all tamale.
Good night.
- See you later.
- Good-Bye, micel!
- Yes!
www.1000fr.com presents
Sync:FRS@ÏºÃ×
the office s5 e26
All right,
you ready for this?
Yeah, we walk around, everyone
sees our faces, And we leave, right?
- Yeah.
- Okay.
Wait, should i have
left the car running?
Oh, don't get us wrong.
We like picnics.
Come on, who doesn't
like a picnic?
Tell 'em at happened
last year.
I had this huge spider
in my baseball mitt.
No, no, that guy
who hit on me.
Oh, right, some drunk guy
hit on pam last year.
Said he was grabbing her
for balance.
Yeah, you don't grab these
Well...
i'm gonna say 30.
40.
Insect repellant, which we clearly need,
Reduces the effectiveness of spf.
Good point,
but thought of that already.
Combination spf/repellant.
- Whoa. Homemade?
- Of course.
You think the epa would ever
allow that much deet?
Rolph is my best friend.
We met in a shoe store.
I heard him
asking for a shoe
That could increase his speed
and not leave any tracks.
Michael, isn't that holly?
We're just friends.
Hey, hey!
Wait a second.
Who let you in here...
is what i wanna know.
Oh, no.
I see they're letting
just anybody in here.
Yeah, that's right.
- All right.
- All right, mm-Hmm.
- Hey.
- Hi.
You rember aj...
my boyfriend?
A little bit.
Uh, i meet a lot of people.
- Hey, michael.
- Hey.
So would you guys
like some lemonade?
Or one of you?
Or both of you.
Either or.
The combinations
are endless.
- Lemonade sounds great.
- Okay.
I'd love an iced tea,
actually.
You can go to hell.
I'm kidding!
Um, sure, i will get you
the best iced tea in the world.
I lied to kevin.
Holly and i
can never be just friends.
I wrote down a list
of bullet points
Why holly and i should
be together,
And i'm going to find
the perfect moment today,
And i'm going to tell her.
Number one:
"Holly, you and i
are soup snakes."
The-- And the reason is...
because, in terms
of the soup, we like to--
That doesn't make any sense.
We're soul mates.
Holly and i are soul mates.
Jim, pam.
- Hey, how are you?
- Hey, charles.
- Nice day, huh?
- Yeah.
Must be nice to get a rest
from all your rest.
I don't get it.
He's not even my boss anymore.
Do you want me
to beat him up for you?
No, i shouldn't have to ask you
To do stuff like that.
You should just do it.
Listen up, everyone! I've gone
overhis lineup very carefully.
We cannot forget the humiliation
we suffered Last year
at the softball game With jim's
whole spider-In-The-Mitt incident.
Right?
Well, i could have died,
so...
i looked it up online
afterwards.
Erin, back row.
Ryan, you move up a w!
Bro-Migo,
You think you could put
erin on my row?
Why?
I don't understand.
If-- No, wait.
W- Wait a minute. I get it.
You want her to set you up
So you can spike it.
Uh...
i' tell you what.
I'm gonna do you one better.
I'm gonna put you next to phyllis.
She's the best setter on the team.
That's--
Sly dog.
Not what i meant.
Come on, folks!
What is up
with you two, holly?
Um, not much.
We're designing a house.
Cl. For who?
For us.
Wow.
I'm designing a chair.
It's part of your pants.
You sit down, you're supported.
I rember
your chair pants idea.
I like that.
Put me down for a pair.
I'm a size 34 waist.
All right, fatty.
I will do it.
You know what?
We should actually rehearse.
Okay, yeah.
You guys are really
gonna do this?
You bet your fat ass we are.
Well, in his infinite wisdom,
?? Llace has authorized us
To put on a little presentation
About the history
of dunder mifflin.
Yep, the old comedyeam
is back together again.
That's right.
Have ya hoyd the news?
Extry, extry!
Read all about it!
Newspapers for sale!
Are you blind?!
Are you blind?
Sir...with the glasses,
Are you literally blind?
I'm concerned
you might be in danger.
These are expensive ray-Bans,
jackass.
Okay, i was just
looking out for you.
You're doing great,
by the way.
Thanks.
I got it.
- kevin, come on!
- Are...you...blind?
- I could have gotten that, idiot! It's not a sledgehammer.
- Can you see things with your eyeballs?
Come on, people.
We need to get our heads in the game.
Let's focus, come on.
You're better than this.
I am better than this.
Phyllis, why are you
sitting on the ground?
We've been out here
for a while.
I don't need this.
Oh, come--
Ryan, come on, man!
- One second.
- W-Wait! Net. Net.
Her hand's on the net.
- So what?
- Rule violation.
Ball is ours.
Give it to me.
Our point!
Okay.
Hey, pam, how you doing?
Hey, do you know if you're
right-Handed or left-Handed?
Or do you even know? What hand
do you use to answer the phone.
Back off, dwight.
Oh, yeah!
Nice hit, pam!
What?
Maybe i played a little
in junior high.
And in high school.
Maybe a little in college.
And went to volleyball camp
most summers.
- ?? Yeah! We win.
- Nice job, beesly.
- We advance to the next round!
Oh, lord in heaven.
Had to be
part of the group.
I brought
some snacky snacks,
In case we get hungry.
Ooh, yes, please.
So what do you have
planned for us today?
- Hmm?
- What?
Do you have a script
for the sketch, or...
um...no.
I just thought
we'd wing it.
That cool?
Crystal cool.
- Hit it, andy!
- Bump, i bumped it!
- Set.
- Don't set it to yourself.
Yeah!
Ow, my ankle!
- What happened?
- I...twisted it.
You weren't even moving.
Okay, sub!
I can play.
Is there a...
meredith here?
Yeah! Man in!
Rolph, did you
not hear me?
I don't hear cheaters,
tramps,
Or women who break
my friend's heart.
Let's go!
We could do a movie...
sort of thing.
- We couldo back to the future.
- Oh!
We have to convince dunder and mifflin
To go back in time...
fix their parents.
Can we get a delorean?
Jaws.
They swim in the ocean,
And they terrorize the whole community.
dun-Der, dun-Der
Dunder, dunder,
dunder, dunder
- We haven't found our great idea yet.
- No. No.
- We're circling it.
- Hmm.
Nicely done. We're still
gonna crush you, though.
- Yes, we are.
- You suckers are goin' down!
They're gonna wipe their asses
with your serves!
- Piss all over your faces!
- Okay, rolph, rolph.
It's true!
Ah, this reminds me of
the h.R. Convention last fall.
Oh, yeah,
with bernie and efrem.
That was hilarious.
- Really, really funny.
- Really funny.
Listen, guys,
one more point,
And we play corporat.
Settle down, gentlemen.
Good game!
Welcome to the 43rd annual
company picnic, everybody.
Thanks for being here.
Now a couple of ployees have
volunteered To entertain us with a song.
Uh, it's a sketch now.
Okay, introducing
scranton's michael scott
Performing with nashua's
holly flax.
I have not seen this.
And now, presenting...
slumdunder mifflinaire!
Are you ready to play
slumdunder mifflinaire?
Yes, i am!
For $100.
Where did dunder
meet mifflinthe
"A," on easy street.
"B," a tour
of dartmouth college.
"C," they never met.
"D," brushing their teeth.
Ohh...i'm thinking.
I'm going to say...
"b,"
tour of dartmouth college.
That is correct!
How did you know that?
I was there!
Aah!
I was a tour guide
at dartmouth college!
Noooo-Ho-Ho!
Nice campus.
Think you'll get in?
Yeah, i'm definitely
gettin' in.
I'm a shoo-In.
I'm robert dunder.
I'm robert mifflin.
Robert mifflin
had a great life.
But unfortunately,
had undiagnosed depression,
Which over nine million
americans suffer from,
And is ??
For $250,
How did he kill himself?
"A," a rope.
"B," a knife.
"C," a gun.
"D," brushing his teeth!
$250...
is more money than i've ever
seen in my life.
I will say
"c," a gun.
He shot himself... in the head.
That is correct!
Yes!
I usually
don't enjoy the theater.
But this is delightful.
The economic downturn
has been difficult recently,
Forcing the closures
of both camden and yonkers,
To be followed soon
By what other branch?
For $500,000,
Is it, "a," scranton?
"B," buffalo?
- "C," utica?
- What?
Or "d," toothbrush?
I will say "b," buffalo!
Final answer!
That is correct!
What is he talking about?
- How did you know that?
- David wallace told me!
David, is this true?
Okay, everyone,
we're at a picnic today.
Are we losing our jobs
or not, david?
- They didn't know?
- I guess not.
I'm sorry, this certainly wasn't the time
or the place To announce thisort of thing.
But there have been talks...
about closing
the buffalo branch.
And...
we're-- We're closing
the buffalo branch.
You've gotta be kidding me!
- Are you serious?
- You've gotta be kidding me!
We're the best branch
in the company!
I can't believe it.
How could you
possibly think
That the right way
to announce a branch closing
Was in a comedy sketch
at the company picnic?
Well...i didn't know
they didn't know.
What about the fact
that they're here today?
- What about that?
- That didn't throw up any alarms?
No, michael need a little bit
for his comedy sketch,
And he thought, "oh, this
would be really funny."
- Thank you.
- Damn it, michael.
I told you that
in confidence.
Now i have to go over and deal
with these employees And their families.
A little boy just walked up to me and said,
"Is my daddy gonna have a job by christmas?"
Well, he'ju thinking
about his own gifts.
Maybe we shouldn't play
due to the circumstances.
Hey, people need volleyball
now more than ever.
How do you figure?
Because if we don't play,
Then the other team wins.
Dwight's right.
Corporate deserves
to get its ass kicked.
Let's do this.
Jim, come on!
Look who just woke up!
Uhh!
I been up for a while!
It's six to six.
It's a nail-Biter.
kav   Seven
Now it's seven-Six. Or is that
too much accounting for you?
Here's an accounting
question for you.
What does one fiance
plus one lover equal?
?? One whore.
Okay, knock it off,
rolph.
What? She's sitting there,
casting aspersions--
Rolph, please.
I am asking nicely!
- Rolph, leave it alone!
- ???
- There you go.
- You got it.
???
Boo-Yah!
Get it!
- I got it!
- Pam!
- You all right?
- Yeah.
No, no, no, i'm fine.
- You sure?
- Yeah.
- easy???
- Oh, whoa, whoa, whoa.
You wanna get that
looked at.
No, no, it's fine.
Just give me a second.
I don't know. You know,
this is a company picnic,
So, technically,
that is a company injury. You know,
safest thing to do
is get that examined. Right, david?
- Yeah.
- All right, you know what?
You're justrying to get rid
of our best player.
Oh, jim, you're putting a volleyball game
In front of your fiancee's health.
No, uh--
Look, seriously.
I can move it fine.
Come on, let's go.
It's our ball. Let's go!
- I don't kw.
- Yeah, i don't think we can
let you play with that foot.
Come on. Tell you what. I spotted a small
hospital A few kilometers south of here.
Get her back as soon
as possible. I'll stall 'em.
I guess that's it
for you, jim.
All right, you know what?
???Come on, all-Black.
We'll be back!
Oh, man!
I'm so mad that pam got hurt!
Argh!
Rrrah!
I'll get it.
Probably shouldn't ve
mentioned buffalo.
Hindsight.
Should have had hindsight.
How do you think it went
before the buffalo thing?
I think it went well.
I think it was good.
There weren't any laughs.
No, it was
a tough audience.
Yeah, but we wrote it Specifically
for this audience.
Believe me, I have seen a lot
of tough audiences in my time,
And that was one of them.
Well, i'm glad we did it.
Me too.
We have a lot of good material
For next year's sketch.
I can't wait.
Yeah, she's with the nurse
right now, So you'll have to stall
No, don't send in
the subs yet.
Dwight, i don't know.
Think of something.
Well, to be safe,
we should do an x-Ray.
How long will that take?
Oh, it shouldn't be too bad.
It's a slow day. So...
no other radiation
this year? No metal plates?
No chance you're pregnant?
I'm sorry, could we just
hurry this up?
I' got a game
to get back to.
Oh, good, because my next question was
Do you have a game to get back to?
What'd you think?
I loved it.
You know, there was a part near the end
That seemed like that went on a little long. But...
well, you guys
should hit the road before...
i close down
another branch.
Okay. So good to see you.
Good to see you.
- Aj.
- Michael.
I didn't find the perfect
moment, Because i think
that today Was about
just having today.
And i think that we
are one of those couples
With a long story
When people ask
how we found each other.
I...
will see her...
every now and then. And...
maybe one year,
she'll be with somebody,
And the
i'll be with somebody.
And it's gonna
take a long time...
and then it's perfect.
I'm in no rush.
- Ha!
- Dwight, come on, now.
It's time to put in the subs.
Yeah, it looks like pam
won't make it back.
- Okay?
- Okay, fine.
All right!
Come on.
Except, you know what?
It's not fine.
How many people need to get hurt
Before we learn a valuable lesson?
One? Two?
Three?
- Four?
- Dwight...
no, no, hear me out.
Five?
- Six?
- Dwight.
Seven. Can i finish, please?
Okay.
Eight?
???H, dwight,
we're so close.
Just buy us
a few more minutes.
Well, they just called me in
for an updat So i'll call you right back.
??
Hey, dwight, uh...
send in the subs.
Ohh.
welcome to www.1000fr.com
www.tvsubtitles.net