Did you know
that in Morocco
It is common to exchange a small gift
When meeting somebody
for the first time?
In Japan, you must always
commit suicide to avoid embarrassment.
In Italy,
You must always wash your hands
after going to the bathroom.
This is considered
to be polite.
Why are you
telling us this?
I am jetting off
on an international business trip.
Where you goin'?
To can-A-Da.
Where is it?
- Canada.
- Okay.
My boss is
sending me abroad
To do a presentation
to an international client.
And I have always
been intrigued
By all things
international--
The women, the pancakes,
The man of mystery--
Meredith,I would like you to pretend
that you are from Abu Dhabi.
Hello.
I am ashamed
at your naked face.
I must cover it
with my jacket.
You are now sexy
in your culture.
www.1000fr.Com presents
Capture:FRM@ив╬х
Sync:FRS@Dwight
The office
Season5 Episode07
Business Trip
- T-Minus...
- 6.5 days.
One more week.
Pam comes back
from New York next week
And everyone here has just been
so excited for me.
And involved.
And intrusive.
And weird.
One more week!
Heh heh.
Do you have your passport?
I have my passport.
Got your per diem?
I have my per diem.
I already know
what I am going to spend this on.
I'm going
to buy a sweater.
Michael, the--
That's for your food.
Well, I'll just--I'll
use different money for that.
I was happy to send Michael
on this trip.
He's been feeling
pretty down since
We had to transfer Holly
up to new Hampshire and--
But this little perk really
seemed to turn him around.
And it's pretty tough
To find somebody who wants
to go up to Winnipeg...
Mid-November.
And business class Air,
Like a five-Star hotel
in the sky,
Nothin' but the best.
Actually, better than
a five-Star hotel
'Cause you get
a big, cushy seat
And you sit
in a row of people.
And to eat, whatever
the mind can imagine.
I think
I am going to have
A filet
with mushroom sauce.
Well, I'm just
glad you're happy,
'Cause, you know,
I felt bad.
Well, that is
all in the past.
And in terms of nightlife,
when you get there,
Just ask the concierge.
They have one of those?
*Let's do this*
Wait, why do you
need three suitcases?
Two are empty
for souvenirs.
- You have your money belt?
- I do.
- It is right here.
- No, no, no, no, no.
You want to wear that puppy right up
on the breastbone like a bra.
No,I don't want
to wear a bra.
Let me help you.
Stop it.
Stop it!
Do you want to get robbed
in a foreign country?
I wash my hands of this.
Okay.
Where's my translator?
- Monsieur.
- There he is.
I'm just bidding
a bon voyage
A la mon petit fianc
Translation:Good-Bye,
my petite fianc
Be good.
- I will try.
- Meaning what?
Meaning I will try
to get other dudes laid.
Yeah, baby!
That's what I'm talkin' about.
That could be you if you
hadn't forgotten french.
Where is my numbers man?
- Here.
- There we go!
Our town car awaits.
It's just a van.
It's not just a van.
Look,I know my way
around a van.
That is just a van.
Dwight, could you
get those, please?
Welcome to cribs--
Business class edition.
Check this out.
Mimosa.
- Ah, sweet!
- Handed it to me.
As i sat down.
This was my hot towel.
It is still wet.
Michael g. Scott,
rollin' like a pimp!
- Take a sip of that.
- Mm-Hmm!
- That good?
- Mmm.
- Don't drink all of it.
- Mmm!
Os--Give some
to oscar.
- That's really good.
- I'm good.
You want one of your own?
I can hook you up.
I'm sorry.
You'll need to keep moving.
Yes, this is Beth.
This is my personal valet
slash flight attendant,
And she will be
helping me this morning.
We need to keep
the aisle clear.
- Yes.
- Oh!
- Get back, get back.
- All right.
Come on!
Get back to the slums!
Oh, boy.
Hey, guys.
Check it out.
My own personal dvd player
and 20 movies.
Andy brought one,too.
- Harry and the hendersons.
- Shh!
Keep it down.
I made
egg salad sandwiches.
Do you want one?
Could you have picked something
stinkier to bring on a plane?
Oh, my god, oscar.
Really--Do you have a bag
of baby poop in there,too,
To share
with everybody?
No,I'll be
ordering my own food,
Thank you very much.
- Hi.
Um,I'd like
to see a menu, please.
Oh,I'm sorry,
there are no meals
On flights
less than two hours.
Oh, okay.
Doesn't matter,
Because I am going
to take a nap.
I think I'm going to use
my complimentary blindfold.
I will don it...
And--Oh!
Look at that.
I can't see
because I am in a--
Gah!
And what would you
like to drink?
Just checkin' out
Where I'm gonna be
pretty soon.
When pam gets back.
Gonna be close quarters.
Gonna be
a lot of tension.
For you.
I'm with Darryl.
This looks like where
I'll probably do
my push-Ups every day.
Is that supposed
to impress me?
No.
Not gonna happen.
He has hurt me
too much and too often
And I am in a healthy
relationship now.
So i'm not gonna flaunt it,
I'm not gonna hurt him,
But that door is closed.
What are we doing?
This is so wrong.
- Yeah. Mmm.
- Mmm. Mmm.
This is nice!
This is nice.
Move in here.
Very sweet.
Ah!
- I'll check us in.
- All right.
- Very cool!
- Very cool.
We are gonna find out where
the action is,
Okay.
My friend.Where's the concierge?
Yes. Wallace said there
would be one of those.
Mmm, bingo.
Follow moi,
bro-Sieur.
Wow!
What about
a nice sushi place?
Maybe a place
with a view?
Oh.
Matsuki.
That's a good one.
Uh, you may walk there
if you wish
Or you may take the number 17 bus
until 9:00.
Other than that,
you can take the taxi
And the number
is right there.
Wow! Wow.
I'm blown away by this.
I, um...
I--Ah!
This is great.
Thank you.
- One final question.
- Um.
Where might you find yourself
on a winnipeg night like tonight?
Oh, the huntsman is good.
- The huntsman.
- Down here.
- The financial district.
- Mm-Hmm.
A concierge is the winnipeg
equivalent of a Geisha.
This is a woman
who has been trained
In the fine art
of fanciness and pleasure.
And when you meet one,
it is intoxicating.
Just what
the doctor ordered.
Can't believe this.
Are you sure?
I just talked to my advisor.
Failing.
Wow. I thought
you were good at flash.
I was,and then
they switched to acrobat
Just as I
was learning quark.
I--I hate computers.
Okay, okay.
It's no big deal.
So you're not
a computer geek.
I have to stay
and retake it.
W--
Wow. Um.
Well...okay.
That means
another 12 weeks.
Can you do another
three months of this?
It's not--
It's not about me.
I mean,
this is your dream.
And you went to new york
to do this.
So when you come back,
You come back
the right way.
Right?
Right.
You okay?
Uh, my cell battery's low,
So I have to let you go.
Okay.
- All right.
Love you. Bye.
Love you, too.
Guys.
She's sittin' there.
Engaging wings.
I'm probably gonna
leave after one drink.
- Let's do this.
- Yeah, with a hot slab of
canadian bacon in your hand.
Excuse me.
Hello.
Concierge marie.
Michael scott.
- Good to see you again.
- Hello.
Good to see you.
Um, this is my associate,
Uh, from Dunder Mifflin.
Uh,Oscar Martinez.
- Nice to meet you.
- Oscar.
Works in accounting.
- This is,uh,Concierge Marie.
- Yes.
Who works at our hotel.
You look, how you say,
radiant tonight.
Thank you.
And it is, how you say,
a beautiful night--
Michael, why?
She's foreign.
I am--
For madame et monsieur.
Oh, thank you.
You're very welcome.
- Thank you, Andy.
- Thank you?
Let me get a picture
of you guys.
Everybody's going
to end up dying someday,
And I think
it's better to die
With some people
that you like--
Like Oscar, and Andy,
and Concierge Marie--
Than to know that
there's somebody out there
That you love
that you're not with.
All right.
I've scoped out the joint.
Those two dudes
are as good as naked.
How do you even
know they're gay?
Come on! It's Dandy Cale
and Foppy Mcgee over there.
Mademoiselle!
Beer me dos long island
iced teas, s'il vous plait.
Bad decision
in a glass.
I don't care
if you're gay, straight,
Engaged--Whatever.
A guy needs intercourse.
You will thank me
when they spank thee.
Don't do this.
- You guys like apples?
- What?
Do you like apples?
Uh, sorry, what--
Well, how do you like
these apples?
All right, on a scale
of one to ten
How hot is that dude?
Is he your boyfriend
or something?
No, but he
could be yours
If you play
your cards right.
Dude. Leave us alone,
all right?
Gentlemen.
What are you doing?
Dude, you struck out.
They're totally stuck-Up.
Here, drink up.
How about this one,
it's Christmas Eve--
Mm-Hmm.
And everything
is closed,
And you need to get
some dry cleaning done.
12:00 midnight.
Where do you go?
What do you do?
Come on.
- What do you do?
- Uh...
Astro Cleaners on st. James place
is the only place that
- is open on that day.
- Unbelievable.Unbelievable!
If you don't
mind me asking--
Anything. You can
ask me anything.
- Okay.
- I'm your wingman.
It's just that
I've sat next to Angela
For a very long,
very long time.
Right-O.
How could anyone
stand that woman?
- What?!
- What do you see in her?
Wh-What do you see
in Angela?
- What do I see in Angela?
- I want to know.
I see through
a hard exterior
To a little jelly
in the middle.
She is teaching me
to be a better person.
And she's working
really hard on that.
And she has the softest
skin I've ever seen
And I can't wait
to have sex with her.
You haven't had sex?
No.
Y--Are you guys waiting
to get married, or?
Honestly,I don't know
what we're waiting for.
Andy, something is
wrong with that woman.
- What is wrong with her?
- I'd like to know.
You should call her
and ask her.
I'd like to know
what's wrong with her.
I should call her
and ask her.
What is wrong with her?
Do it.
It's a--
Call her.
Oh, my god.
Don't call her.
Don't call her, Andy.
Andy, don't call her.
Too late.
Too late, it's dialing.
Now it's ringing.
Hello? Hello?
What is wrong with you?
- Why won't you do Andy?
- What?
That's oscar, and he wants
to know why you won't do me,
And I think it's
a valid question.
- Are you drunk?
- This is Andy Bernard.
I know who this is.
I wanna take you
to sex school.
What?
Who is that, monkey?
Is somebody there?
- Are you drunk?
- I have needs.
We will
discuss this later.
- Naked.
- What?
We'll discuss
it later naked.
I want to see you naked.
Do you want to get
some breakfast or something?
- I'm so tired.
- Okay.
How does everyone
know already?
Know what?
- Pam failed art school.
- Oh, well.
- Doesn't surprise me.
- Excuse me?
Have you seen her painting,Jim?
The building?
There are shadows coming from
two different directions.
- Dwight, stop it.
- Dwight.
What?!
Are there two suns?
- Come on.
- Oh, my god.
Uh, last I checked,
That's not an office building
in the Andromeda Galaxy.
I'm gonna grab
a cup of coffee.
It's totally unrealistic.
No lines
in the parking lot.
Oscar.
Hey.
- That was fun last night.
- Yeah, it was.
You know,
it's true what they say--
Long Island iced teas
are way stronger in Canada.
Hey, um...
Thanks for trying
to hook me up.
You kiddin' me?
It's what I do.
Get the whole
nine 'nards.
I can't believe
we called her up.
Totally.
What--Who?
I'm talking about Angela.
I can't believe we
called her up last night.
We called Angela?
You--You call--
You called her.
That was real?!
I thought I dreamed that.
- Oh, god!
- All right.
Oh, god!
- Okay.
- So bad.
Good morning,
Michael.
Are you ready
for the meeting?
Slept like a baby.
Mmm--This can't
happen again.
This has
to happen again.
Darryl can't
happen again.
Look at me.
Do you want me
to do more push-Ups?
- Yeah.
- Okay.
You have to break up
with Darryl.
I already typed out
a text message for you.
All you have to do
is press "send."
I don't know.
I mean, it's well-Written
and all,I just--
Has to be done.
We'll press
"send" together.
Oh, my god.
He's gonna kill us.
I'd like
to see him try.
Oh! He says it's cool.
He said, "it's cool!"
That's all he wrote?
- That's all he wrote.
- Can I see it?
Didn't you two date
for like a long time?
Mm-Hmm. This is
like a fairy tale!
I'll be honest with you--
We've been talking
with catalyst paper.
Their prices
are better than yours.
Look, people continue
to come back to us
Time and time again
Because they feel
cared for here.
They feel respected and they feel
that their needs matter.
They are treated
like human beings.
Everything okay?
Yes.
Oh, man.
She is so pissed.
- Mmm.
- She's taking us back to first base.
What's first base
with Angela?
I get to kiss
her forehead.
I had a good time
hangin' out this weekend.
I had a good time, too.
Wingman for life.
W.M.F.L.
Thank you.
You up for
a chest bump?
No.
Bro hug?
Back to basics.
I like it.
I had to go
all the way to Canada
To get to know a guy
Who sits 20 feet away from me.
And he's delightful!
Hey!
I just heard you guys
made the sale.
Yeah, we locked him up
for two years.
Good, very good.
See, told you.
Sounds like somebody
had a good trip.
No, actually,
the trip sucked.
Excuse me?
The trip sucked,David.
It blew chunks.
It was terrible.
It was a bad trip.
- What are you talking about?
- I did not like the trip.
Well, starting with
the airport shuttle,
Which was basically
just a van.
- Okay.
- And business class,
Which was basically
just coach.
And the hotel
which sucked big time.
The hotel?
What, m--Okay.
It was not--
It sucked.
I'm sorry to hear
the hotel was bad...
Oh, and thanks for the tip
on the concierge.
That was great.
That was--
That was a--
- Okay.Okay,hey,hey,hey,Michael
- That was a really good choice.
Please.
Let's listen for a second.
No,David,
you listen to me.
Why did you send her away?
That--God.
You knew I liked her
and you just sent her away
And that--
- That was a sucky thing to do,man.
- Michael, sometimes--
That was a really
sucky thing to do.
Sometimes we--
Why have I stayed at Dunder Mifflin
for so long?
Certainly not
because of the paycheck.
'Cause I could be making
more money as a doctor
Or a professional athlete.
I think it's
because they respect me.
A boss that
will not fire you
Even though
you just tell him off
Right to his face
over the phone--
That's respect.
You did it, man.
Day one.
Congrats.
Thanks, man.
I'm coming back
the wrong way.
It's not because of you.
I don't like
graphic design.
That's it.
Stop smiling.
I really didn't like it.
It's just designing
logos and stuff.
And I missed Scranton.
But it is not
because I missed you.
I just really wanted
to come home.
And I know you said to come
home the right way,
But you can't
tell me what to do.
Got it?
I missed you.
I missed you, too.
You're back.
Uh, yeah.
Good.
I need you to make
five copies of these.
I'm not going inside.
All right.
First thing
in the morning, then.
Welcome back.
We're back together
again, baby.
We're back.
They tried to keep us apart,
But they couldn't.
It was like destiny.
I--I realized that,
for whatever reason,
I just couldn't do
better than Kelly.
- Oh!
- Yeah.
www.tvsubtitles.net