At least once a year, i like to bring in
Some of my kevin's famous chili.
The trick is to undercook the onions.
Everybody is going to
get to know each other in the pot.
I'm serious about this stuff.
I'm up the night before pressing garlic
And dicing whole tomatoes.
I toast my own ancho chilies.
Jesus.
It's a recipe passed down
from malones for generations.
It's probably the thing i do best.
www.1000fr.com presents
Sync:╧Бок
the office S05 ep24
Someone is returning!
He started his own company,
and now he's back.
Who could it be?
I'll give you a hint.
He is a man.
A man you have missed
with all your heart.
A man who has ruined
all other men for you.
Who is it?
- Who is it?
It's michael scott.
Hold it up.
Conference room, five minutes.
Well, i guess the first order of business
Is to welcome back me and pam and ryan.
And how about casual friday again, huh?
Reinstituting casual friday?
You all look great.
What i want to do right now
Is try something a little different.
I'm going to throw it out there,
starting with this meeting.
I want you guys to run it.
I want you to say whatever
you want, Take it away.
Your meeting.
Wh-What are you doing?
If there is something That
you would like to say as a group,
Then by all means,
you may say it to me right now.
Okay.
- Yes.
- People are dressed inappropriately.
Take it up with toby.
What i want you to do
Is i want you to look inward.
And i want you to reflect.
And i want you to say something different.
Can you give us a hint?
When i needed salespeople
for my new paper company,
Everyone here turned their back on me.
Am i going to ask them
to beg for forgiveness? No.
Am i going to ask for
a big, crying apology? No.
Am i going to ask them to
slit their wrists for me? No.
I just want a tiny,
microscopic version of that.
Oscar, what were you going to say?
Nothing.
I didn't say anything.
All right.
Do i still have a job here?
Not important.
Okay, all right.
- Yes. Yes, you have a job.
- ??
Frankly, you have a job because ryan and
pam Are starting with us as salesmen.
- Wait, what?
- How is that going to work?
It's going to work very smoothly,
Because pam and ryan are
bringing over a ton of clients
From michael scott paper company and--
You mean the clients you stole from us.
Yeah, aren't we
getting those clients back?
No, you lost those clients.
- I call foul, sir.
- Okay.
You were bought out.
So the company then bought out
all of the stolen clients.
Okay, dwight, let me
explain something to you.
I set the rules and you follow them.
Blindly. Okay?
And if you have a problem with that,
Then you can talk to
our complaint department.
It's a trash can.
Don't fall in love with me, kid.
Boscov's at the steamtown mall?
It sure looked good on the mannequin.
- Well, you have good taste.
- Well, thanks.
I sure wish i had more time
to talk to my clients, though.
What?
Isn't that what you said
to a bunch of my clients
When you were stealing them?
That i didn't have enough time for them?
Oh, i, um...
Close your mouth, sweetie,
you look like a trout.
The man is wearing sandals.
I don't need to see oscar's toes at work.
Gross! I mean he looks like
he just got off the boat!
Can't you just not look at his feet?
Excuse me?
You're so educated, aren't you, toby?
So trained to deal with
a hysterical woman.
I don't want to look at his feet.
Do your job!
Well, i was in the seminary
for a year And dropped out
'Cause i wanted to have sex
with this girl, cathy.
??Followed her to scranton.
Took the first job i could find in h.R.
Later she divorced me.
So no, i wouldn't say
i have a passion for h.R.
- There you are, my friend.
- Oh, thanks, man.
Pamela.
- Thanks, michael.
- Yep.
Fresh hot ink.
"New file system."
Trust me, stanley, You're going to
want to read this memo very carefully.
??I am not changing the way
i do my files.
No. No. This goes for all of you.
Believe me, You are going
to want to heat my words.
When held over heat,
The invisible ink will reveal
That everyone should meet
at the warehouse immediately.
Do not ask me where
i got the invisible ink.
Urine. It was urine.
I'm sorry you're offended by my shoes,
But i'm not going to
drive home to change.
- I could loan you a pair of socks.
- No.
No, they're clean.
I was going to wear them
to volleyball practice later.
I don't think so.
Andrew bernard.
Okay, what are you still
doing at your desk?
What are you still doing not at your desk?
Did you even read the memo?
All my files are now
in reverse alphabetical order--
No, you idiot.
There is a code embedded in the memo.
Listen, you need to
round up all the salesmen,
Except for ryan and pam,
And get them down
to the warehouse pronto.
Oh, it is on like a prawn
who yawns at dawn.
Stop doing rhyming poetry.
Just tell them, please.
God, the simplest thing.
We're in crisis mode here,
do you understand?
The two unqualified so-Called
salespeople Are being favored
Because they all failed together.
And frankly, i'm not convinced that
michael and pam Didn't have
a thing going while they were gone.
Can i address that?
- No, you're too close.
- Okay.
Stanley, how do you feel About
those two taking your clients?
It's not right. I don't like it.
He doesn't like it.
You don't take my clients away
And give them to a secretary.
No offense, jim.
I think she's very pretty.
Her face is okay, but.
Jesus! What-- What are you doing here?
I don't know. I saw a crowd.
I thought there might be a dogfight
- or something--
- Get out!
We need to do something.
I'm thinking maybe a coup
or we take ryan hostage.
- Those sound too harsh.
- No, i'm not saying we do those things.
I'm saying something like those things.
- Of course.
- What is like a hostage?
Excellent question.
We could write a strongly-Worded letter.
Words will never be enough.
Strongly-Painted picture.
- No, pictures are too interpretive.
- Can i just say something?
I know that tempers are high,
But i think the best way to handle this
Might be to just talk to michael directly.
Well, that--
That's a great idea, jim.
Oh, i totally see your point.
Okay, we'll talk to michael directly.
So uh, meeting is over, i guess.
- I'll see everyone upstairs.
- Great, see you upstairs.
Come on.
Now is the time for action.
I'm talking action--
- That was great.
- I know.
- Why are you so mad?
- You look so classy in that picture.
I do? Well--
Where is that bowl?
- Hey, you have a second?
- Michael scott paper company only.
Yeah, i think you're gonna
want to cool it with that,
'Cause it's starting to
upset the other salesmen.
- Okay, well...
- tough.
I will-- No, no.
I'll talk to them when they
all get back from the bathroom.
This is awkward to talk about
But there may or may not be--
But definitely is--
A mutiny forming
in the warehouse right now.
- Against who?
- You.
- Us.
- What?
It's gotta be because
they all want their clients.
The old michael scott might have taken
this, But not the new michael scott.
They are in for a bitter surprise.
I am not to be truffled with.
Six weeks ago, None of these
people wanted to come with me.
You two were the only ones
with the stones to follow.
That was us, right there.
We were something else.
What you gotta do Is you gotta
go down to that warehouse
And you gotta crack some skulls.
Chiklis style.
Yeah, the commish.
Yes, but chiklis shield style.
- Okay.
- Not commish style.
Yeah, yeah. The shield.
It's crazy what's going on
out there today, huh?
I know. Yeah, it's... kinda--
Sometimes it's best just to stay out of it.
That's true. That's right. Yeah.
Want to play a game?
Hey, gang. Where you been?
Lunch.
- Where'd you eat?
- A restaurant.
What'd you have, stanley?
I had a salmon salad.
With water, no ice.
I was going to get a soda,
But the waitress talked me out of it.
Her name was flo, she had black hair.
I had mexican food.
So since you guys already ate,
You won't be eating the stuff That
you brought with you for lunch, will you?
stanley.
Is that egg salad?
- Andy brought some salmon.
- That looks great.
Dwight, is that a meat sandwich?
You guys hungry?
I can eat.
I'm going to have
some of this meat sandwich.
It's pony.
What kind of sauce is on your salmon?
Dijonnaise.
Thanks for going out, guys.
Hey, meredith, can i talk
to you privately for a second?
About what?
Your outfit.
What? What's wrong with my outfit?
You-- You might consider
pulling it down a touch.
It's ri-- It's riding up a little high.
A bunch of prudes.
You know, oscar's
allowed to wear sandals,
But i'm not allowed
to wear open-Toed shoes?
Is that how it goes?
Meredith, your boob is out.
Fine.
No! Meredith, too far!
Damn it, meredith,
where are your panties?
It's casual day.
Happy?
Toby! Toby, toby!
Toby.
No. If you do that, i'm gonna do that.
If you do that, i'm gonna do that.
If you do this, i'm going to do that.
Well, what if i just do this?
You don't want to do that.
I'm just hiding out
until all this stuff blows over.
With creed.
Playing chess. At work.
He's winning.
I feel like i'm describing a dream i had.
I'm sorry you feel that way, mr. Bart.
Is there anything i can do
to make things better?
Give me the phone. Give me the phone.
- Exactly.
- ??That's my client.
- This is your first complaint in ten years.
- ??
- Things have been generally good.
- Give me the phone.
Tell him dwight schrute
wants to talk to him.
- Look, uh, mr. Bart...
- hi, mr. Bart.
- At these prices with this service...
- Hey, it's dwight here.
- Give me the phone.
- You're not gonna find this anywhere else.
- Dwight schrute here. Hey, don't hang up.
- No, no, no. Sir, don't listen.
I know times are tough right now,
And i laud your thriftiness.
- Ryan, hand the phone over.
- Ryan!
Stop flustering me, everybody!
Who let this boy on the phone?
Mr. Bart!
I cannot believe you lost that account.
He was my client for ten years!
You made him lose the account
By screaming at him the entire time.
It's okay, ryan.
You're a secretary! What do you know?
- Okay.
- And you're a temp.
And i'm taking your phone.
- I'm confiscating this.
- Hey, hey, guys.
You know what i want you to do?
Shake hands, get over it.
That was not a shake, dwight.
We want our clients back
or we quit, michael.
Who quits?
Me.
And me.
Me too.
You guys gotta be kidding.
No, we gotta be deadly serious.
We'll start our own paper company.
The schrute-Bernard- Lapin-Vance...
Stanley paper company.
I love it.
I love this idea, and i fully support you.
As a matter of fact, i'm
going to give you some seed money.
There you go. There's
some seed money for you.
And you can take it, no hard feelings.
But if you stay, i want an apology,
And i want a big one.
- You want us to apologize to you?
- Yes, i do.
That's completely backwards.
It's frontwards.
Michael, you thought
you were attacking corporate,
But we were the ones who got hurt.
You should be apologizing to us.
- That's right.
- Right.
Michael, you always said we were a family.
Then you went after us.
No matter how i look at this,
i am in the wrong.
And i have looked at this thing,
Like, a hundred different ways.
From my point of view,
From their point of view...
98 others.
And the bottom line, i am in the wrong.
I'm the bad guy.
I need you to arrange a meeting
Between me and the sales staff
Without ryan and pam knowing.
Gasp.
Are you talking about a secret meeting?
Whatever you guys did earlier.
I don't know the first thing
about secret meetings.
- Just do it, okay?
- I'll do--
- Get 'em there. Get 'em there.
- I'll do the best i can.
Are you kidding me?
- Deceit does not come easy to me.
- Okay, okay, okay.
I really love your outfit.
Thank you so much for saying that.
I can't believe that
toby thinks this is inappropriate.
You look like j-Lo.
So from the bottom of my heart
To the top of my heart, i am sorry.
Are you giving us our clients back?
If we could just
focus and go down the line,
And everyone would say,
"apology accepted,"
I think we would all feel better.
And then we can
break out my gift to you--
Complimentary white chocolate bark.
Nobody likes that stuff except for you.
They wouldn't make it
unless people liked it.
Michael, just give us our clients back.
That's all we care about.
Okay. If i give you your clients back
There won't be enough
clients for pam and ryan,
And i promised both of them
that they were gonna be salespeople.
- So?
- Fine, have your clients.
I can see that's what
you wanted all along.
Okay.
However, i rescind my apology.
- Okay.
- That's fair.
You are not reacting at all as i had hoped.
What'd i tell you about
building forts in my warehouse?
Michael gave all of our clients
Back to their old salespeople,
So now there's not enough
for both me and pam to stay on.
He can only keep one of us
as a salesperson now.
He'll make his decision
by the end of the day.
I think you should get it.
You really grew into it.
You've changed a lot
And you'd be good at it.
If you really think that,
will you tell that to michael?
That would go a long way
coming from you.
Yeah.
Thanks.
So hey, I want to
set you up with my daughter.
Oh, i'm engaged to pam.
I thought you were gay.
Then why would you want to
set me up with your daughter?
I don't know.
Jim. Can i talk to you for a minute?
Sure, let me just finish this turn.
And bingo was his name.
Let's go.
Challenge.
I need your help.
This whole pam/ryan debate
is screwing with my head.
I don't want to be biased,
but i am very close to ryan.
- You know that.
- You're close with pam too.
- she's nice, i guess.
- You know what?
Best thing to do, pros and cons list.
Pro for ryan, he went to business school.
He's my number one choice.
- Well, that's--
- I like his hair.
Cons, ryan.
He defrauded the company.
- He has never made a sale.
- Okay.
- He definitely stole my ipod.
- That sounds pretty biased.
You didn't hear my pros.
Environmentally-Conscious
'Cause his mom drives him
to work every day.
Okay.
Pam, pros. I like her.
I think that she is a fast learner.
Cons, she doesn't always follow through.
Sh-- New york and the whole
art school thing. And roy.
She has a weird voice.
- That's not true.
- I don't need to tell you that.
I think she'd be
a really good salesperson.
I don't think you are
being totally impartial, though,
Because you haven't said
one bad thing about pam.
- And i won't.
- Okay.
So be it, then you've lost credibility.
And i'm going to go
with my gut, and that's ryan.
??
You're right, sometimes
when she is tired,
She can be a little bit shrill.
But that's not a weird voice.
Take it easy.
man!
Honey!
I want you to bring the garbage out.
'Cause i'm not going
to have sex with you
Unless you bring out the garba--
I have a very difficult decision to make.
It's like last week
i was at the video store.
Do i rent devil wears prada again?
Or do i finally get around
to seeing sophie's choice?
It is what you would call
a classic difficult decision.
You don't understand clothing, toby.
You're dressed like
this amorphous blob of khaki.
All right, look, what you gotta understand
Is when you come to work,
you give up certain rights.
Listen up, flenderson.
You're being weak and ineffectual.
I'm cowboying this meeting, okay?
Here are the new rules.
Okay, earth tones only.
Also, women are forbidden
to wear pants.
All right, come on. Sit down, dwight.
- No.
- I'm running this meeting.
- That's debatable.
- It's not.
??It's not. Sit down or i'm writing you up.
where has this guy been?
Casual fridays are cancelled.
Let's just not do it anymore.
- No, it is a solution.
- You're running from the problem.
There's not a single appropriate
outfit In this whole--
Except mine, quite honestly.
Pam, can you come in here, please?
Have a seat.
??
Well, there's no easy way of saying this.
So i think i will just...
drag it out.
- Since the dawn of time there has been--
- Just tell me.
I gave ryan the sales job.
There just weren't enough clients
for the two of you.
So i had to--
- No, okay.Okay, i get it. Yeah.
- I'm sorry. Sorry.
Why are you giggling?
Is this a joke?
Michael, is this--
Did i get the job?
- Yes, you did.
- I did?
- Yep.
- For real, you're not kidding?
- No, you-- No.
- I did?!
No, you're the best person for the job.
- You're going to be great.
- Oh, michael, thank you. Thank you.
Thank you. You will not be sorry.
You should've seen your face.
Oh, man!
that was classic.
I really thought i didn't get it.
- Oh, really?
- Yeah.
- 'Cause you said i didn't.
- Oh, man. That was really good.
- That was really good.
- Oh, what about ryan?
I don't know, i offered
him his temp job back.
We'll see.
He was not happy at all
when i offered him this job,
And then i told him
he didn't get the job, so.
Yeah.
Maybe you shouldn't
fake fire people anymore.
I don't appreciate
you telling me what to do.
So clean out your desk,
you are through here.
Thanks, michael.
What's our receptionist's name?
Erin.
Could you send her in?
Michael wants to see you.
- Hello.
- Hi.
Have a seat.
This is very difficult to say,
But no one here likes you in the office
And we are going to have to let you go.
Hank, would you come up here, please?
Hank is our security guard.
- Oh, i can go.
- He will be ushering you out.
Oh, your face!
- Is-- Do the people--
- No, i'm kidding. No, you're not--
You're not fired. Yet.
Do they not like me, though?
- I don't know, actually.
- Okay.
welcome to www.1000fr.com
www.tvsubtitles.net